[
    {
        "index": 0,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " Possibly a reference to the Blarney Stone, the saying \"kiss me, I'm Irish\" is traditionally associated with what holiday?",
        "answers": [
            "Labor Day",
            "St. Patrick's Day",
            "Independence Day",
            "Bono's Birthday"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " St. Patrick's Day"
    },
    {
        "index": 1,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " Often called the largest living thing on earth due to its trunk volume, California's \"General Sherman\" is  275-foot tall what?",
        "answers": [
            "bear",
            "tree",
            "mushroom",
            "iceberg"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " tree"
    },
    {
        "index": 2,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " A specialty license plate featuring the image of a lobster is offered by which of these U.S. states?",
        "answers": [
            "Maine",
            "Kansas",
            "Oklahoma",
            "Tennessee"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Maine"
    },
    {
        "index": 3,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " First spotted on the wall of a British pub, \"Kissing Coppers\" is a Bansky artwork that depicts two amorous what?",
        "answers": [
            "bus drivers",
            "veterinarians",
            "chefs",
            "police officers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " police officers"
    },
    {
        "index": 4,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In which section of the Philadelphia Zoo can visitors see a red kangaroo?",
        "answers": [
            "African Plains",
            "Big Cat Falls",
            "Outback Outpost",
            "Bird Valley"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Outback Outpost"
    },
    {
        "index": 5,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " The breakout star of TV's \"The Mandalorian\" was a tiny, adorable Star Wars character called \"The Child,\" popularly known to audiences as what?",
        "answers": [
            "Baby Yoda",
            "Baby Darth",
            "Baby R2",
            "Baby Chewie"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Baby Yoda"
    },
    {
        "index": 6,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " According to the National Weather Service, hail sizes range from 1/4 inch in diameter, or \"pea size,\" to 4 1/2 inches in diameter, the size of a what?",
        "answers": [
            "golf ball",
            "chicken egg",
            "softball",
            "human head"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " softball"
    },
    {
        "index": 7,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " Besides Antarctica, what is the only continent that has never hosted a Summer or Winter Olympics?",
        "answers": [
            "South America",
            "Africa",
            "Australia",
            "Europe"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Africa"
    },
    {
        "index": 8,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " What singer co-writes many of her songs with her brother who is known professionally as Finneas?",
        "answers": [
            "Selena Gomez",
            "Camila Cabello",
            "Billie Eilish",
            "Ariana Grande"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Billie Eilish"
    },
    {
        "index": 9,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " Which of these historic places employs a full-time Ravenmaster to care for the flock of ravens that live on the landmark?",
        "answers": [
            "Palace of Versailles",
            "Great Pyramids of Giza",
            "The Colosseum",
            "Tower of London"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Tower of London"
    },
    {
        "index": 10,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " In 2020, a Washington Post article argued that what classic American literary work features \"the most famous act of social distancing\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Heart of Darkness",
            "The Scarlet Letter",
            "Walden",
            "On the Road"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Walden"
    },
    {
        "index": 11,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "125,000",
        "question": " With more than 230 million followers, the most popular Instagram account in the world belongs to an athlete in what sport?",
        "answers": [
            "cricket",
            "basketball",
            "boxing",
            "soccer"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " soccer"
    },
    {
        "index": 12,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "250,000",
        "question": " Oddly similar to the line \"I see dead people\" from \"The Sixth Sense,\" the line \"All I see are dead people\" appears in what other Bruce Willis film?",
        "answers": [
            "Armageddon",
            "12 Monkeys",
            "The Fifth Element",
            "The Jackal"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 12 Monkeys"
    },
    {
        "index": 13,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " Which of these recent movies chronicles the final years of a notorious gangster?",
        "answers": [
            "Dolittle",
            "Capone",
            "Onward",
            "Sonic the Underboss"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Capone"
    },
    {
        "index": 14,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " A total lunar eclipse is also called a \"Blood Moon\" because the Moon appears to turn what color?",
        "answers": [
            "blue",
            "green",
            "red",
            "silver"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " red"
    },
    {
        "index": 15,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " Like two peas in a pod, a broom is often sold in a set that comes with what other household item?",
        "answers": [
            "iron",
            "bottle opener",
            "dustpan",
            "toothbrush"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dustpan"
    },
    {
        "index": 16,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " During a particularly cold winter in Florence, Italy, it is said that Michelangelo built perhaps the world's greatest what?",
        "answers": [
            "sand castle",
            "birdhouse",
            "paper kite",
            "snowman"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " snowman"
    },
    {
        "index": 17,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which company's delivery trucks warn would-be thieves that \"Drivers do not carry burritos\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Chipotle",
            "Arby's",
            "Subway",
            "Dairy Queen"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Chipotle"
    },
    {
        "index": 18,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " At the start of a chess game, there are four of all but which of these pieces on the board?",
        "answers": [
            "knights",
            "bishops",
            "queens",
            "rooks"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " queens"
    },
    {
        "index": 19,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " Always the romantic, Mike Tyson has admitted that he cries every time he watches what sappy movie starring Ryan Gosling and Rachel McAdams?",
        "answers": [
            "Serendipity",
            "The Proposal",
            "10 Things I Hate About You",
            "The Notebook"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Notebook"
    },
    {
        "index": 20,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " @HMSeye is the Twitter handle of what department at Harvard Medical School?",
        "answers": [
            "neurology",
            "ophthalmology",
            "dermatology",
            "radiology"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ophthalmology"
    },
    {
        "index": 21,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " On a Season Four episode of \"Seinfeld,\" George explains that if he ever became an adult film star he would take what stage name?",
        "answers": [
            "Squeaky Springs",
            "Butt Reynolds",
            "Alan Thick",
            "Buck Naked"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Buck Naked"
    },
    {
        "index": 22,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " The only post office in the U.S. that still receives mail delivered by mule is in the Native American village of Supai, which is located where?",
        "answers": [
            "Marfa, Texas",
            "Grand Canyon",
            "Pike National Forest",
            "Aleutian Islands"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Grand Canyon"
    },
    {
        "index": 23,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " According to a common history myth, Marie Antoinette uttered the famous line \"Let them eat cake\" in response to being told what?",
        "answers": [
            "her army was refusing to fight",
            "her subjects had no bread",
            "her daughters were to be married",
            "France and Austria were at war"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " her subjects had no bread"
    },
    {
        "index": 24,
        "date": "3/21/2021",
        "prize": "125,000",
        "question": " Primarily occurring in the central and eastern U.S., a derecho is a type of rare storm characterized by what?",
        "answers": [
            "wall of strong wind",
            "rapid snowfall",
            "spiral-shaped air current",
            "dust cloud"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " wall of strong wind"
    },
    {
        "index": 25,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " In 1849, thousands of settlers rushed to California after the discovery of what?",
        "answers": [
            "gold",
            "soap",
            "ink",
            "avocado toast"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " gold"
    },
    {
        "index": 26,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " Which of these tennis greats once won the Australian Open while roughly eight weeks pregnant?",
        "answers": [
            "Andy Murray",
            "Serena Williams",
            "Roger Federer",
            "John McEnroe"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Serena Williams"
    },
    {
        "index": 27,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " What David Bowie song was fittingly released in 1969 just a few days before the first moon landing?",
        "answers": [
            "Rebel Rebel",
            "Let's Dance",
            "Space Oddity",
            "Suffragette City"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Space Oddity"
    },
    {
        "index": 28,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these iconic landmarks can be seen on the cover of a Fodor's travel guide to London?",
        "answers": [
            "Taj Mahal",
            "Mount Rushmore",
            "Machu Picchu",
            "Tower Bridge"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Tower Bridge"
    },
    {
        "index": 29,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of these apt taglines was once the slogan for Planters?",
        "answers": [
            "Let's Taco 'Bout It",
            "Relax. Go Nuts.",
            "Bean There, Done That.",
            "We're Kind of a Big Dill."
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Relax. Go Nuts."
    },
    {
        "index": 30,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Likely making censors wince as the 2020 Emmy nominations were announced, what TV show was mentioned on air three times before racking up 15 total noms?",
        "answers": [
            "Better Call Saul",
            "The Goldbergs",
            "Schitt's Creek",
            "Stranger Things"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Schitt's Creek"
    },
    {
        "index": 31,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " On the human body, the gluteal cleft is more commonly known as what?",
        "answers": [
            "Adam's apple",
            "earlobe",
            "armpit",
            "butt crack"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " butt crack"
    },
    {
        "index": 32,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " To the delight of her colleagues, Elena Kagan was able to get a fro-yo machine installed in the cafeteria of what esteemed institution?",
        "answers": [
            "the Pentagon",
            "the U.S. Capitol",
            "the U.S. Supreme Court",
            "West Point"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the U.S. Supreme Court"
    },
    {
        "index": 33,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " Named for the film's most famous quote, the 2020 book \"Alright, Alright, Alright\" bills itself as \"the definitive oral history\" of what cult classic?",
        "answers": [
            "Dazed and Confused",
            "The Big Lebowski",
            "Heathers",
            "Starship Troopers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Dazed and Confused"
    },
    {
        "index": 34,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " On Wikipedia, a search for \"da da da DUM\" redirects users to the page for what classical work?",
        "answers": [
            "Mozart's The Magic Flute",
            "Handel's Messiah",
            "Beethoven's 5th Symphony",
            "Tchaikovsky's The Nutcracker Suite"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Beethoven's 5th Symphony"
    },
    {
        "index": 35,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " Which of the following statements is true about the names of four of the U.S.'s twenty most populous cities?",
        "answers": [
            "they start with \"San\"",
            "they end in \"land\"",
            "they start with \"New\"",
            "they end in \"City\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " they start with \"San\""
    },
    {
        "index": 36,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "125,000",
        "question": " The spot where Francis Crick and James Watson announced their 1953 discovery, The Eagle pub in Cambridge, England honors the duo today by offering an ale called what?",
        "answers": [
            "Black Hole",
            "Penicillin",
            "DNA",
            "Titanic"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " DNA"
    },
    {
        "index": 37,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " In August of 2020, what inhospitable U.S. location reached a scorching 130 degrees Fahrenheit?",
        "answers": [
            "Niagara Falls",
            "Death Valley",
            "Central Park",
            "the DMV"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Death Valley"
    },
    {
        "index": 38,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " Including minifigures of Ross, Chandler, Monica, Joey, Rachel and Phoebe, \"Central Perk\" is a 1,079-piece Lego set that pays tribute to what sitcom?",
        "answers": [
            "The Big Bang Theory",
            "Home Improvement",
            "Friends",
            "Who's the Boss"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Friends"
    },
    {
        "index": 39,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " One of the three major muscle types in humans, cardiac muscle can only be found in what part of the body?",
        "answers": [
            "heart",
            "liver",
            "eyes",
            "brain"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " heart"
    },
    {
        "index": 40,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these boats is typically the smallest?",
        "answers": [
            "schooner",
            "dinghy",
            "barge",
            "aircraft carrier"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dinghy"
    },
    {
        "index": 41,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of these kids' games involves one person chasing another person around in a circle?",
        "answers": [
            "hopscotch",
            "dodgeball",
            "Red rover",
            "duck, duck, goose"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " duck, duck, goose"
    },
    {
        "index": 42,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " NoBunPlease.com is a website devoted to which of these trendy wellness topics?",
        "answers": [
            "meditation",
            "ketogenic dieting",
            "goat yoga",
            "light therapy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ketogenic dieting"
    },
    {
        "index": 43,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " In one episode of his 2020 web series \"Reunited Apart\" Josh Gad discusses what classic film with Bill Murray, Dan Aykroyd and Sigourney Weaver?",
        "answers": [
            "Back to the Future",
            "Home Alone",
            "Ghostbusters",
            "Ferris Bueller's Day Off"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Ghostbusters"
    },
    {
        "index": 44,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " On its final departure from Sydney in 2020, what airline's last Boeing 747 followed a flight path that, fittingly, traced the shape of a kangaroo?",
        "answers": [
            "Lufthansa",
            "Qantas",
            "El Al",
            "KLM"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Qantas"
    },
    {
        "index": 45,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " In the National Baseball Hall of Fame, the inductee whose last name comes first alphabetically has what first name?",
        "answers": [
            "Yogi",
            "Wade",
            "Sparky",
            "Hank"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Hank"
    },
    {
        "index": 46,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " When Oscar the Grouch's pet worm took a trip to space, Tony Bennett appeared on \"Sesame Street\" and crooned what playful song?",
        "answers": [
            "Slimey to the Moon",
            "Mr. Bertjangles",
            "That's Elmore",
            "My Funny Snuffleupagus"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Slimey to the Moon"
    },
    {
        "index": 47,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " Designer Christian Louboutin was reportedly inspired to create his shoes' signature red soles after watching his assistant do what?",
        "answers": [
            "eat a strawberry",
            "polish her nails",
            "arrange flowers",
            "apply lipstick"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " polish her nails"
    },
    {
        "index": 48,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "125,000",
        "question": " The location of Malik 'Phife Dawg' Taylor Way, Linden Boulevard and 192nd Street in Queens, NY is the site of a mural honoring what hip-hop group?",
        "answers": [
            "De La Soul",
            "Run-DMC",
            "A Tribe Called Quest",
            "The Beastie Boys"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " A Tribe Called Quest"
    },
    {
        "index": 49,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "250,000",
        "question": " Named after the Greek goddess of the hunt, what NASA program aims to land the first woman on the moon by 2024?",
        "answers": [
            "Artemis",
            "Hera",
            "Aphrodite",
            "Athena"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Artemis"
    },
    {
        "index": 50,
        "date": "3/14/2021",
        "prize": "500,000",
        "question": " A gangster cliche for \"going to jail,\" the phrase \"up the river\" originally referred to a prison up what river?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Ohio River",
            "Hudson River",
            "St. Lawrence River",
            "Rio Grande"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Hudson River"
    },
    {
        "index": 51,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " Which of these recent movies is based on a fairy tale by the Brothers Grimm?",
        "answers": [
            "Gretel & Hansel",
            "Richard Jewell",
            "Midway",
            "Cinderella: Day of the Soldado"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Gretel & Hansel"
    },
    {
        "index": 52,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " What was the answer to the 2019 New York Times crossword clue that read \"Good name for a girl born on December 24\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Hayley",
            "Kim",
            "Eve",
            "Jennifer"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Eve"
    },
    {
        "index": 53,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " Which of these items in your medicine cabinet often comes with instructions for both oral and rectal use?",
        "answers": [
            "cotton swab",
            "thermometer",
            "tongue depressor",
            "tweezers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " thermometer"
    },
    {
        "index": 54,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Long before it was a global enterprise, the founders of Yahoo! gave their directory the folksy name \"Jerry and David's Guide to the\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "solar system",
            "World Wide Web",
            "publishing industry",
            "U.S. Constitution"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " World Wide Web"
    },
    {
        "index": 55,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " After receiving a letter in 1968 that lamented the lack of diversity among his beloved characters, Charles Schulz introduced Franklin in what comic strip?",
        "answers": [
            "Blondie",
            "Dennis the Menace",
            "Peanuts",
            "Marmaduke"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Peanuts"
    },
    {
        "index": 56,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " What fruit is described by ModernFarmer.com as \"the adorable little nephew of the orange family\"?",
        "answers": [
            "plum",
            "clementine",
            "apricot",
            "fig"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " clementine"
    },
    {
        "index": 57,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " Because they mainly eat eucalyptus leaves, what animals are said to smell like cough drops?",
        "answers": [
            "koalas",
            "penguins",
            "hyenas",
            "alligators"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " koalas"
    },
    {
        "index": 58,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " The title of Alex Trebek's 2020 memoir features what fitting catchphrase?",
        "answers": [
            "Come On Down!",
            "The Answer Is...",
            "I'd Like to Buy a Vowel",
            "No Whammies!"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Answer Is..."
    },
    {
        "index": 59,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " Which country's capital city is one of the few in the world whose name contains all five vowels",
        "answers": [
            "Hungary",
            "Denmark",
            "Argentina",
            "Mexico"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Argentina"
    },
    {
        "index": 60,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " An old school guy with an old school vocabulary, Joe Biden had which of these phrases painted across his 2020 campaign tour bus?",
        "answers": [
            "No Poppycock!",
            "No Hokum!",
            "No Claptrap!",
            "No Malarkey!"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " No Malarkey!"
    },
    {
        "index": 61,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " Which of the following has never been a flavor of Ben & Jerry's ice cream?",
        "answers": [
            "Honey, I'm Home",
            "Go Fudge Yourself",
            "Economic Crunch",
            "Marsha Marsha Marshmallow"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Go Fudge Yourself"
    },
    {
        "index": 62,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " Because it can permanently burn our retina, you should never stare directly at what?",
        "answers": [
            "the sun",
            "the ocean",
            "the moon",
            "the Wendy's Baconator"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the sun"
    },
    {
        "index": 63,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " Unsurprisingly, what former president was the first-ever guest on \"The Michelle Obama Podcast\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Jimmy Carter",
            "George W. Bush",
            "Barack Obama",
            "Bill Clinton"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Barack Obama"
    },
    {
        "index": 64,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " Which of the following is not a standard setting on a blender?",
        "answers": [
            "chop",
            "liquefy",
            "annihilate",
            "puree"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " annihilate"
    },
    {
        "index": 65,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Bands found wrapped around the teeth of mummies are believed to be ancient precursors of what modern medical implement?",
        "answers": [
            "eyeglasses",
            "braces",
            "hearing aid",
            "pacemaker"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " braces"
    },
    {
        "index": 66,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of these retail names is an example of alliteration?",
        "answers": [
            "CVS",
            "Toys \"R\" Us",
            "OfficeMax",
            "Bed Bath & Beyond"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Bed Bath & Beyond"
    },
    {
        "index": 67,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " An event that informed his life's work, which of these historic men incurred an eye injury at the age of three that caused him to go blind?",
        "answers": [
            "Louis Pasteur",
            "Henry Heimlich",
            "Louis Braille",
            "Edwin Hubble"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Louis Braille"
    },
    {
        "index": 68,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " In a \"memoir\" titled \"Before You Leap,\" what beloved kids' character reveals that he was born one of 2,353 brothers and sisters?",
        "answers": [
            "Kermit the Frog",
            "Snoopy",
            "Thomas the Tank Engine",
            "Barney"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Kermit the Frog"
    },
    {
        "index": 69,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " To honor their homegrown son Guy Fieri, residents of Columbus, Ohio have started a petition to rename the city what?",
        "answers": [
            "Dee-lish City",
            "Flavortown",
            "Frialator Springs",
            "Garlic Knot Junction"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Flavortown"
    },
    {
        "index": 70,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " In \"Emoji Dick,\" an all-emoji edition of \"Moby Dick,\" what is the first emoji used in the translation of the novel's famous first line?",
        "answers": [
            "prayer hands",
            "heart",
            "telephone",
            "smiley face"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " telephone"
    },
    {
        "index": 71,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " A doll modeled after Muslim American athlete Ibtihaj Muhammad is the first Barbie to wear a what?",
        "answers": [
            "sari",
            "hijab",
            "dastar",
            "sheitel"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " hijab"
    },
    {
        "index": 72,
        "date": "3/7/2021",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " In which of these movies does Leonardo DiCaprio portray a fictional character and not a real-life person?",
        "answers": [
            "The Wolf of Wall Street",
            "The Revenant",
            "Catch Me If You Can",
            "Once Upon a Time in Hollywood"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Once Upon a Time in Hollywood"
    },
    {
        "index": 73,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " Which of these recent movies has two car brands in its title?",
        "answers": [
            "Bad Boys for Life",
            "The Invisible Man",
            "Ford v Ferrari",
            "Star Wars: The Rise of Volvo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Ford v Ferrari"
    },
    {
        "index": 74,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " Given the right soil conditions, what animal is known to tunnel underground at a speed of fifteen feet per hour?",
        "answers": [
            "mole",
            "skunk",
            "raccoon",
            "coyote"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " mole"
    },
    {
        "index": 75,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " As its name suggests, which of the Great Lakes holds more water than all of the other Great Lakes combined?",
        "answers": [
            "Lake Erie",
            "Lake Superior",
            "Lake Ontario",
            "Lake Huron"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Lake Superior"
    },
    {
        "index": 76,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " A radio channel on SriusXM, \"On Broadway\" plays what type of music?",
        "answers": [
            "Southern gospel",
            "heavy metal",
            "country",
            "show tunes"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " show tunes"
    },
    {
        "index": 77,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " The 2020 bestseller \"You Never Forget Your First\" is a biography of what U.S. president?",
        "answers": [
            "George Washington",
            "Thomas Jefferson",
            "Abraham Lincoln",
            "Theodore Roosevelt"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " George Washington"
    },
    {
        "index": 78,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " \"Lamb shanks were velvety soft in 40 minutes\" is a sentence appearing in a New York Times review of what small kitchen appliance?",
        "answers": [
            "Mr. Coffee",
            "Instant Pot",
            "Sodastream",
            "Vitamix"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Instant Pot"
    },
    {
        "index": 79,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " \"30 Years of LOL\" is the tagline for what longtime ABC show?",
        "answers": [
            "The Bachelor",
            "Shark Tank",
            "America's Funniest Home Videos",
            "20/20"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " America's Funniest Home Videos"
    },
    {
        "index": 80,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " To protect the health and safety of players, the 2019-2020 NBA season restart required athletes to live and compete within a single location widely known as the what?",
        "answers": [
            "NBA vault",
            "NBA bubble",
            "NBA fortress",
            "NBA fishbowl"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " NBA bubble"
    },
    {
        "index": 81,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " What country sends Canada thousands of tulip bulbs every year as a thank you gift for protecting its royal family during World War II?",
        "answers": [
            "Austria",
            "Denmark",
            "Portugal",
            "The Netherlands"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "index": 82,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " What Disney film's villain has a look that was said to be inspired by the drag queen Divine?",
        "answers": [
            "The Little Mermaid",
            "The Lion King",
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
            "Aladdin"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Little Mermaid"
    },
    {
        "index": 83,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " Meaning \"to make every possible effort,\" the term \"pull out all the stops\" comes from a technique used when playing what instrument?",
        "answers": [
            "violin",
            "guitar",
            "organ",
            "saxophone"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " organ"
    },
    {
        "index": 84,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "125,000",
        "question": " Prince Harry and Meghan Markle have a black lab named \"Pula,\" also the name for the official currency of what country where they fell in love?",
        "answers": [
            "Haiti",
            "Botswana",
            "Hungary",
            "South Africa"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Botswana"
    },
    {
        "index": 85,
        "date": "1/13/2021",
        "prize": "250,000",
        "question": " Who was Mitch McConnell referring to when he said, \"Nevertheless, she persisted,\" a line that has since become a rallying cry of the women's movement?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Hillary Clinton",
            "Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez",
            "Kamala Harris",
            "Elizabeth Warren"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Elizabeth Warren"
    },
    {
        "index": 86,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " On average, the human body has seven billion billion billion what?",
        "answers": [
            "bones",
            "eyelashes",
            "atoms",
            "ill-advised lower back tattoos"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " atoms"
    },
    {
        "index": 87,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " Which of these U.S. attractions boasts a popular souvenir shop called MouseGear?",
        "answers": [
            "Graceland",
            "Walt Disney World",
            "National Air & Space Museum",
            "Metropolitan Museum of Art"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Walt Disney World"
    },
    {
        "index": 88,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " Won by Arnold Schwarzenegger seven times, Mr. Olympia is a title awarded at an annual competition between whom?",
        "answers": [
            "bartenders",
            "figure skaters",
            "scuba divers",
            "bodybuilders"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bodybuilders"
    },
    {
        "index": 89,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Competitors squeal, grunt and snuffle at an annual contest in France to crown the \"world's best\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "pig imitator",
            "birdhouse builder",
            "grocery bagger",
            "butter churner"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " pig imitator"
    },
    {
        "index": 90,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " During the Revolutionary War, British soliders were known by what colorful nickname?",
        "answers": [
            "redcoats",
            "blackbeards",
            "yellowbellies",
            "blueboots"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " redcoats"
    },
    {
        "index": 91,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Thanks to its extra adhesive footpads, which of these animals can walk up a wall and across a ceiling?",
        "answers": [
            "antelope",
            "penguin",
            "gecko",
            "chicken"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " gecko"
    },
    {
        "index": 92,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " The aptly-titled 2020 film \"Radioactive\" tells the story of Marie Curie, a winner of the Nobel prize for which of the following?",
        "answers": [
            "literature",
            "economics",
            "peace",
            "chemistry"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " chemistry"
    },
    {
        "index": 93,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " Not to be outdone by Pennsylvania's Punxsutawey Phill, Ohio also has a weather-predicting groundhog with which of these fitting names?",
        "answers": [
            "Dairyland Donald",
            "Buckeye Chuck",
            "Hoosier Howie",
            "Bluegrass Gus"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Buckeye Chuck"
    },
    {
        "index": 94,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " In 2020, when an 8-year-old named Corona was getting bullied because of his name, Tom Hanks sent him a vintage Corona, a classic brand of what?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "typewriter",
            "record player",
            "telephone",
            "camera"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " typewriter"
    },
    {
        "index": 95,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " Especially popular during election season, the website FiveThirtyeight.com has a name inspired by what?",
        "answers": [
            "number of U.S. Congressional districts",
            "area code of Washington, D.C.",
            "number of electors in the Electoral College",
            "number of days in the election cycle"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " number of electors in the Electoral College"
    },
    {
        "index": 96,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Known to millions for her soothing inflection, Canadian mindfulness instructor Tamara Levitt is the \"voice\" of what popular app?",
        "answers": [
            "Venmo",
            "OpenTable",
            "Skype",
            "Calm"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Calm"
    },
    {
        "index": 97,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " Which planet is depicted on a jokey T-shirt that reads, \"If you like it put a ring on it\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Saturn",
            "Venus",
            "Mercury",
            "Mars"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Saturn"
    },
    {
        "index": 98,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " In 2020, scientists identified a wooded area near Marlborough, England, as the likely source of giant slabs used in what famous landmark?",
        "answers": [
            "The Colosseum",
            "Stonehenge",
            "Taj Mahal",
            "Machu Picchu"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Stonehenge"
    },
    {
        "index": 99,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " In the last decade, five of the ten Academy Awards for Best Director have gone to someone born in what country?",
        "answers": [
            "South Korea",
            "France",
            "Taiwan",
            "Mexico"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Mexico"
    },
    {
        "index": 100,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " Though we now use it more broadly, the word \"chops\" was once specifically used to mean a \"high skill level\" in reference to whom?",
        "answers": [
            "chefs",
            "jazz musicians",
            "newspaper reporters",
            "barbers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " jazz musicians"
    },
    {
        "index": 101,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " For the past five years, the Nathan's Famous Hot Dog Eating Contest has been won by a man with what last name?",
        "answers": [
            "Curry",
            "Bacon",
            "Chestnut",
            "Frank"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Chestnut"
    },
    {
        "index": 102,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "125,000",
        "question": " Which of the following is recognizable for its three four-pointed geometric shapes called \"hypocycloids\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Pittsburgh Steelers helmet",
            "Canadian flag",
            "Starbucks logo",
            "Rolls-Royce hood ornament"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Pittsburgh Steelers helmet"
    },
    {
        "index": 103,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "250,000",
        "question": " When the U.S. mint was established in 1792, legend has it that the first coins it produced were made from what?",
        "answers": [
            "Alexander Hamilton's gold inkwell",
            "Ben Franklin's pewter beer steins",
            "Martha Washington's silverware",
            "Thomas Jefferson's copper sink"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Martha Washington's silverware"
    },
    {
        "index": 104,
        "date": "1/3/2021",
        "prize": "500,000",
        "question": " Of the fifteen tallest buildings in the world, more than half are in what country?",
        "answers": [
            "Saudi Arabia",
            "China",
            "United Arab Emirates",
            "Malaysia"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " China"
    },
    {
        "index": 105,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " What common physical trait takes is name from a bible story set in the Garden of Eden?",
        "answers": [
            "widow's peak",
            "Adam's apple",
            "pigeon-toed",
            "Noah's armpit"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Adam's apple"
    },
    {
        "index": 106,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " Which of these animals cannot jump?",
        "answers": [
            "kangaroo",
            "rabbit",
            "elephant",
            "frog"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " elephant"
    },
    {
        "index": 107,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " At a state fair when she was ten years old, what did Amelia Earhart ironically dismiss as \"not at all interesting\"?",
        "answers": [
            "automobile",
            "tractor",
            "bicycle",
            "airplane"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " airplane"
    },
    {
        "index": 108,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Children who eat their entire dinner are said to belong to what exclusive \"organization\"?",
        "answers": [
            "The Clean Plate Club",
            "The Silver Spoon Society",
            "The Order of the Fork",
            "The Butter Knife League"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Clean Plate Club"
    },
    {
        "index": 109,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Cindy Crawford once said, \"If I was designing my face from scratch I don't know if I would have designed it with the\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "cleft chin",
            "unibrow",
            "mole",
            "buck teeth"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " mole"
    },
    {
        "index": 110,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " According to Travel+Leisure magazine, what is \"the only state in the U.S. where seeing the northern lights is highly likely\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Florida",
            "Alaska",
            "Rhode Island",
            "Nevada"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Alaska"
    },
    {
        "index": 111,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " Which of these movies is a sequel?",
        "answers": [
            "The Sixth Sense",
            "8 Mile",
            "102 Dalmatians",
            "Apollo 13"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 102 Dalmatians"
    },
    {
        "index": 112,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " Elton John's rise to stardom is chronicled in what 2019 movie?",
        "answers": [
            "Rocketman",
            "Hustlers",
            "Shazam!",
            "Someone Wasted My Time Tonight"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Rocketman"
    },
    {
        "index": 113,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " In 2020, the U.S. Postal Service began putting paw print stickers on some malboes to warn mail carriers about what?",
        "answers": [
            "traffic",
            "dogs",
            "bad weather",
            "high voltage"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dogs"
    },
    {
        "index": 114,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " According to the U.S. Coast Guard, which of these states is not home to a lighthouse?",
        "answers": [
            "North Carolina",
            "South Dakota",
            "Rhode Island",
            "New Jersey"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " South Dakota"
    },
    {
        "index": 115,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Never stated in the original nursery rhyme, Lewis Carroll's \"Through the Looking-Glass\" was likely the first to identify what character as an egg?",
        "answers": [
            "the Mad Hatter",
            "Tweedledee",
            "the Red Queen",
            "Humpty Dumpty"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Humpty Dumpty"
    },
    {
        "index": 116,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " What medical equipment can be seen in the logo of the American Society of Acupuncturists?",
        "answers": [
            "forceps",
            "tongue depressors",
            "needles",
            "scalpels"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " needles"
    },
    {
        "index": 117,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " What is the last name of the politician whose official presidential campaign website in 2020 was peteforamerica.com?",
        "answers": [
            "Sanders",
            "Booker",
            "Buttigieg",
            "Bloomberg"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Buttigieg"
    },
    {
        "index": 118,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " \"To Spin or Not to Spin\"? is the title of an economics paper analyzing the perfect strategy for playing what game show's \"Showcase Showdown\"?",
        "answers": [
            "The Price is Right",
            "The"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Price is Right"
    },
    {
        "index": 119,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " Where on a golf course would a golfer typically use a club engraved with an \"S\"?",
        "answers": [
            "tee box",
            "fairway",
            "bunker",
            "putting green"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "bunker"
    },
    {
        "index": 120,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " Famously shouted at the end of the movie \"Se&en,\" what is the answer to Brad Pitt's frantic question, \"What's in the box?!\"",
        "answers": [
            "a note",
            "a head",
            "a photograph",
            "a bomb"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "a photograph"
    },
    {
        "index": 121,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " How do you spell the name of the third largest city in Ohio?",
        "answers": [
            "C-I-N-N-C-I-N-A-T-I",
            "C-I-N-C-I-N-N-A-T-I",
            "C-I-N-C-I-N-N-A-T-T-I",
            "C-I-N-N-C-I-N-A-T-T-I"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " C-I-N-C-I-N-N-A-T-I"
    },
    {
        "index": 122,
        "date": "11/15/2020",
        "prize": "125,000",
        "question": " The author of what children's book was inspired to write his classic work after meeting a girl in the hospital who just had her appendix removed?",
        "answers": [
            "Matilda",
            "Blueberries for Sal",
            "Madeline",
            "The Velveteen Rabbit"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Madeline"
    },
    {
        "index": 123,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "100",
        "question": " 1200 President Clinton Avenue in Little Rock, Arkansas is the address of a library and museum dedicated to a man named what?",
        "answers": [
            "Lyndon",
            "Ronald",
            "Bill",
            "Linda"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Bill"
    },
    {
        "index": 124,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "200",
        "question": " Just as it sounds, Who Gives A Crap is a brand of what?",
        "answers": [
            "toothpaste",
            "soap",
            "shampoo",
            "toilet paper"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " toilet paper"
    },
    {
        "index": 125,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "300",
        "question": " Eating too many carrots may cause carotenemia, a condition in which the skin turns what color due to excessive beta-carotene levels?",
        "answers": [
            "blue",
            "purple",
            "orange",
            "green"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " orange"
    },
    {
        "index": 126,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " \"Leapling\" is a nickname for a person who was born on what date?",
        "answers": [
            "January 1st",
            "February 29th",
            "April 20th",
            "December 25th"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " February 29th"
    },
    {
        "index": 127,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " The Old Farmer's Almanac provides instructions to hikers for locating the North Star in an entry entitled, \"How to Find Your Way Without a\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "thermometer",
            "compass",
            "pen knife",
            "hatchet"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " compass"
    },
    {
        "index": 128,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of these formidably named people is the only one who raps with Cardi B in a hit 2020 song?",
        "answers": [
            "Ivan the Terrible",
            "Richard the Lionheart",
            "Megan Thee Stallion",
            "Vlad the Impaler"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Megan Thee Stallion"
    },
    {
        "index": 129,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " Though silence is not an official rule, at which of these sporting events are spectators traditionally expected to remain quiet?",
        "answers": [
            "Wimbledon",
            "the World Series",
            "Tour de France",
            "Boston Marathon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Wimbledon"
    },
    {
        "index": 130,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " Director Wes Craven has said that his childhood bully Fred Kruger inspired the name of the villain in what classic slasher film?",
        "answers": [
            "A Nightmare on Elm Street",
            "Friday the 13th",
            "Halloween",
            "Scream"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " A Nightmare on Elm Street"
    },
    {
        "index": 131,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " After a 1997 eruption covered its capital in forty feet of volcanic debris, the island of Montserrat is often referred to as a modern day what?",
        "answers": [
            "Alexandria",
            "Constantinople",
            "Athens",
            "Pompeii"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Pompeii"
    },
    {
        "index": 132,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " Which of the following is a customary thing to say after witnessing an act of sternutation?",
        "answers": [
            "Make a wish",
            "Bless you",
            "Knock on wood",
            "Congratulations"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Bless you"
    },
    {
        "index": 133,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " On summer evenings, people flock to the Congress Avenue Bridge in Austin, Texas to see more than one million what?",
        "answers": [
            "armadillos",
            "gophers",
            "rattlesnakes",
            "bats"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bats"
    },
    {
        "index": 134,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "125,000",
        "question": " Although the term would not be popular for years, what movie characters have been called \"Inventors of the Selfie\" for the Polaroid they take of themselves in their film?",
        "answers": [
            "Harold & Kumar",
            "Bill & Ted",
            "Thelma & Louise",
            "Romy & Michele"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Thelma & Louise"
    },
    {
        "index": 135,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of these government agencies employs a Chief of Disguise responsible for creating things like wigs and fake noses?",
        "answers": [
            "NASA",
            "EPA",
            "IRS",
            "CIA"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " CIA"
    },
    {
        "index": 136,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "4000",
        "question": " What big screen comedy memorably features Melissa McCarthy sitting in a sink screaming, \"It's coming out of me like lava!\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Pitch Perfect",
            "Bridesmaids",
            "Ocean's 8",
            "Bad Moms"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Bridesmaids"
    },
    {
        "index": 137,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "8000",
        "question": " Typing in which of these URLs redirects you to the Apple website?",
        "answers": [
            "newton.com",
            "edison.com",
            "einstein.com",
            "darwin.com"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " newton.com"
    },
    {
        "index": 138,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "16,000",
        "question": " At the top of each episode, host Sean Evans typically refers to his hit Web series \"Hot Ones\" as \"the show with hot questions, and even hotter\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "gossip",
            "coffee",
            "tunes",
            "wings"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " wings"
    },
    {
        "index": 139,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "32,000",
        "question": " What prestigious award has a pretty racy description on its official website, boasting that its medal depicts \"a husky, bare-chested printer at work\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Nobel Prize",
            "Medal of Honor",
            "Pulitzer Prize",
            "Tony Award"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Pulitzer Prize"
    },
    {
        "index": 140,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "64,000",
        "question": " Which of the following is Joe Biden's middle name, and not the name of a comic book character?",
        "answers": [
            "Cypher",
            "Robinette",
            "Morbius",
            "Slyde"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Robinette"
    },
    {
        "index": 141,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "125,000",
        "question": " In 2020, the New York Post reported that some users of a popular erectile dysfunction drug were experiencing which of these strange side effects?",
        "answers": [
            "blue vision",
            "cured baldness",
            "urge to gamble",
            "an Italian accent"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " blue vision"
    },
    {
        "index": 142,
        "date": "11/8/2020",
        "prize": "250,000",
        "question": " For over thirty years, Queen Elizabeth II has favored what shade of nail polish by Essie?",
        "answers": [
            "Ballet Slippers",
            "Lady Like",
            "Everything's Rosy",
            "Lovie Dovie"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Ballet Slippers"
    },
    {
        "index": 143,
        "date": "5/31/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Offering a six-figure salary, but also extremely high-stress, what occupation topped Time's list of \"High-Paying Jobs You Don't Want to Have\"?",
        "answers": [
            "web designer",
            "air traffic controller",
            "philanthropist",
            "game show host"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " air traffic controller"
    },
    {
        "index": 144,
        "date": "5/31/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Game designer Leslie Scott created the prototype for which game using wooden blocks that her family bought from a local sawmill while living in Ghana in the '70s?",
        "answers": [
            "football",
            "Go Fish",
            "Jenga",
            "tag"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Jenga"
    },
    {
        "index": 145,
        "date": "5/31/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Most likely because they're less common than the others, a recent study found that cars of what color tend to depreciate in value the least over time?",
        "answers": [
            "white",
            "yellow",
            "silver",
            "black"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " yellow"
    },
    {
        "index": 146,
        "date": "5/31/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Though Jay Leno reclaimed his old job shortly afterward, which current late-night star hosted NBC's \"Tonight Show\" for about 8 months in 2009 and 2010?",
        "answers": [
            "Stephen Colbert",
            "Samantha Bee",
            "Conan O'Brien",
            "Bill Maher"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Conan O'Brien"
    },
    {
        "index": 147,
        "date": "5/24/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " If you know your away around a cyclic, a collective, a throttle and yaw pedals, you're ready to operate the four main controls of a what?",
        "answers": [
            "motorcycle",
            "Segway scooter",
            "helicopter",
            "train"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "helicopter"
    },
    {
        "index": 148,
        "date": "5/24/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Which of these famous movie quotes is NOT the final line spoken in its respective film?",
        "answers": [
            "\"The horror, the horror...\"",
            "\"Frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn.\"",
            "\"The truth is...I am Iron Man.\"",
            "\"It was beauty killed the beast!\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": "\"Frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn.\""
    },
    {
        "index": 149,
        "date": "5/24/2019",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " By definition, clabbered milk is milk that has what?",
        "answers": [
            "been brought to a boil",
            "soured and thickened",
            "been genetically modified",
            "had its fat reduced"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "soured and thickened"
    },
    {
        "index": 150,
        "date": "5/24/2019",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " While the U.S. has hosted the most Summer and Winter Olympics with a total of 8, which country has thus far hosted the second-most with 5?",
        "answers": [
            "Japan",
            "Italy",
            "Canada",
            "France"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "index": 151,
        "date": "5/24/2019",
        "prize": "100,000",
        "question": " Considered one of the worst albums ever, a 1974 record consisting only of between-song banter from live shows was called \"Having Fun With\" whom \"On Stage\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Elvis",
            "Dylan",
            "The Doors",
            "Streisand"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Elvis"
    },
    {
        "index": 152,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In 2018, a Texas brewery called The Collective Brewing Project released a specialty beer infused with the flavor of what beloved treat associated with Easter?",
        "answers": [
            "fruitcake",
            "turkey giblets",
            "hot dogs",
            "Peeps"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Peeps"
    },
    {
        "index": 153,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of the following does NOT appear on MensJournal.com's list of \"The Best Types of Cardio Workouts for Weight Loss\"?",
        "answers": [
            "swimming",
            "sprinting",
            "opening and closing the refrigerator door",
            "rowing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " opening and closing the refrigerator door"
    },
    {
        "index": 154,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of these things does Meat Loaf specifically say that he WOULD do for love in his hit song \"I'd Do Anything For Love (But I Won't Do That\")?",
        "answers": [
            "run right into hell and back",
            "wear matching Christmas sweaters",
            "go on one of those lame couples retreats",
            "hold your purse while you try on swimsuits"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " run right into hell and back"
    },
    {
        "index": 155,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " When cameras aren't allowed in a courtroom, TV news broadcasts commonly use what to show viewers what took place?",
        "answers": [
            "puppet show",
            "improv troupe",
            "child actors",
            "artist's sketch"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " artist's sketch"
    },
    {
        "index": 156,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Though it might seem like a nice gesture, Mindy Kaling says bringing what to a party is a slightly hostile act, as you have to drop everything and arrange them?",
        "answers": [
            "cut flowers",
            "folding chairs",
            "random pieces of silverware",
            "bowling trophies"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cut flowers"
    },
    {
        "index": 157,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In 2017, Jeffrey C. Hall, Michael Rosbash and Michael W. Young won a Nobel Prize in Medicine for their research on what well-known body mechanism?",
        "answers": [
            "biological clock",
            "biological scissors",
            "biological lint brush",
            "biological travel mug"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " biological clock"
    },
    {
        "index": 158,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Set in the 1980s (like the famous TV show with Crockett and Tubbs), the video game \"Grand Theft Auto",
        "answers": [
            "Boise, ID",
            "Miami, FL",
            "Fargo, ND",
            "Salt Lake City, UT"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Miami, FL"
    },
    {
        "index": 159,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Meaning \"to the man,\" which of these Latin phrases refers to an argument where you ignore the facts and just attack your opponent's character?",
        "answers": [
            "ad nauseam",
            "ad hominem",
            "ad hoc",
            "ad infinitum"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ad hominem"
    },
    {
        "index": 160,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Starring Molly Ringwald in the title role and Joey Bishop as her grandfather, what 1990 movie features a member of both the Brat Pack AND the Rat Pack?",
        "answers": [
            "A Fish Called Wanda",
            "Betsy's Wedding",
            "Curly Sue",
            "Roxanne"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Betsy's Wedding"
    },
    {
        "index": 161,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Who's missing from this sequence of recent British Prime Ministers, listed in chronological order",
        "answers": [
            "Boris Johnson",
            "Stephen Harper",
            "Malcom Turnbull",
            "Gordon Brown"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Gordon Brown"
    },
    {
        "index": 162,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " While many believe he's buried near his birthplace on the island of Zanzibar, what music star's final resting place is still unknown to this day?",
        "answers": [
            "John Lennon",
            "Jimi Hendrix",
            "Tupac Shakur",
            "Freddie Mercury"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Freddie Mercury"
    },
    {
        "index": 163,
        "date": "5/17/2019",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " When spelled out in full, which of these pairs of computer terms have a word in common?",
        "answers": [
            "HTTP and PDF",
            "GIF and JPEG",
            "PDF and GIF",
            "JPEG and IP address"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " PDF and GIF"
    },
    {
        "index": 164,
        "date": "5/10/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " According to modern business slang, if you're a member of the \"Unicorn Club,\" what have you done?",
        "answers": [
            "caught a unicorn",
            "successfully bred a unicorn",
            "been granted three wishes by a unicorn",
            "founded a start-up worth over $1 billion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " founded a start-up worth over $1 billion"
    },
    {
        "index": 165,
        "date": "5/10/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " What New York Mets outfielder has a first and last name that are both also names of U.S. state capitals?",
        "answers": [
            "Austin Jackson",
            "Madison Bumgarner",
            "Juan Pierre",
            "Jordan Montgomery"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Austin Jackson"
    },
    {
        "index": 166,
        "date": "5/10/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " The mainlands of New Zealand, Iceland and Ireland (supposedly thanks to Saint Patrick) are thought to have no native species of which of these creatures?",
        "answers": [
            "butterflies",
            "snakes",
            "spiders",
            "cows"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "snakes"
    },
    {
        "index": 167,
        "date": "5/10/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " In 2017, what rocker closed out the final show of his 40th anniversary tour with \"American Girl,\" just a week before his death at age 66?",
        "answers": [
            "John Mellencamp",
            "Eric Clapton",
            "Bob Seger",
            "Tom Petty"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Tom Petty"
    },
    {
        "index": 168,
        "date": "5/10/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Similar in meaning to the American phrase \"I couldn't care less,\" what is the literal translation of the German idiom \"Das is mir Wurst\"?",
        "answers": [
            "my concern flew away",
            "you're making me sleepy",
            "it's sausage to me",
            "I have real problems"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "it's sausage to me"
    },
    {
        "index": 169,
        "date": "5/3/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " As opposed to being listed according to their star power, actors in the end credits of movies are commonly listed in order of what?",
        "answers": [
            "when they first appeared in the film",
            "how nice they were to the crew",
            "how many times they've been divorced",
            "how many chin-ups they can do"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " when they first appeared in the film"
    },
    {
        "index": 170,
        "date": "5/3/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Doused during a key victory in 1984, the Chicago Bears' Mike Ditka is said to have been the first coach to get the now-common celebratory \"shower\" of what beverage?",
        "answers": [
            "hot coffee",
            "wheatgrass juice",
            "Gatorade",
            "pinot grigio"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Gatorade"
    },
    {
        "index": 171,
        "date": "5/3/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Though it's certainly a dream for many, according to The Independent, which of these is NOT one of the most common things to happen in dreams?",
        "answers": [
            "falling",
            "being naked in public",
            "getting chased",
            "winning"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " winning"
    },
    {
        "index": 172,
        "date": "5/3/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Though no one is sure of its rules (as it hasn't been played in 1,500 years), the ancient Chinese game of liubo is thought to have used a 14-sided die, called a what?",
        "answers": [
            "tetrahedron",
            "tetradecahedron",
            "tetracontagon",
            "tetrahectagon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "tetradecahedron"
    },
    {
        "index": 173,
        "date": "5/3/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " A land of linked deserts, which of the following countries contains no permanent rivers or lakes?",
        "answers": [
            "Ethiopia",
            "Iran",
            "Saudi Arabia",
            "Egypt"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Saudi Arabia"
    },
    {
        "index": 174,
        "date": "5/3/2019",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Formerly known as JoAnne Chesimard, the godmother of what rapper was a key member of the Black Panthers, and the 1st woman to be on the FBI's most wanted list?",
        "answers": [
            "The Notorious B.I.G.",
            "Snoop Dogg",
            "Dr. Dre",
            "Tupac Shakur"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Tupac Shakur"
    },
    {
        "index": 175,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " What Looney Tunes character is often seen on 18-whelers' mud flaps, above the phrase \"Back Off\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Sylvester the Cat",
            "Yosemite Sam",
            "Tweety Bird",
            "Porky Pig"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Yosemite Sam"
    },
    {
        "index": 176,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In many species of ants, after mating, the female sheds her wings, and the male unfortunately does what?",
        "answers": [
            "brags about it on Facebook",
            "tells her \"This doesn't mean we're a thing.\"",
            "gets down on five knees and proposes",
            "dies"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dies"
    },
    {
        "index": 177,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " To reduce waste, Seattle recently banned what common restaurant items that are typically only used once and then thrown away?",
        "answers": [
            "wooden bread baskets",
            "plastic straws",
            "glass salt shakers",
            "metal cash registers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " plastic straws"
    },
    {
        "index": 178,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " According to a famous quote by Robert Louis Stevenson, what is \"perhaps the only profession for which no preparation is thought necessary\"?",
        "answers": [
            "cardiology",
            "structural engineering",
            "politics",
            "circus performing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " politics"
    },
    {
        "index": 179,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Which of the following is NOT a recommended step in putting out a grease fire in the kitchen, as it flings the grease out of the pan and shoots fire everywhere?",
        "answers": [
            "putting baking soda on it",
            "dumping water on it",
            "covering it with a lid or cookie sheet",
            "turning off the heat source"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dumping water on it"
    },
    {
        "index": 180,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which of these words was inspired by the name of a Germanic tribe, infamous for its merciless destruction of public buildings?",
        "answers": [
            "hedonism",
            "anarchism",
            "vandalism",
            "terrorism"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " vandalism"
    },
    {
        "index": 181,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " A nod to a song in the previous film, what movie sequel released in 1987 was advertised with the tagline, \"The heat's back on!\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Beverly Hills Cop II",
            "Ghostbusters II",
            "Crocodile Dundee II",
            "Staying Alive"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Beverly Hills Cop II"
    },
    {
        "index": 182,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Which of the following does NOT correctly list the currency in which that year's official Summer Olympic coins were struck?",
        "answers": [
            "1992 = Pesetas",
            "2004 = Dollars",
            "2008 = Yuan",
            "2012 = Pounds"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 2004 = Dollars"
    },
    {
        "index": 183,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " It took three months to make Meghan Markle's wedding dress, which was designed by Clare Waight Keller, the artistic director for what famous fashion house?",
        "answers": [
            "Dolce & Gabbana",
            "Prada",
            "Givenchy",
            "Chanel"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Givenchy"
    },
    {
        "index": 184,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these is NOT a common thing people do to get hot soup to cool down before they eat it?",
        "answers": [
            "wait a few minutes",
            "drop an ice cube in it",
            "blow on it",
            "FedEx it to Alaska and back"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " FedEx it to Alaska and back"
    },
    {
        "index": 185,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Spoken by Alexander Graham Bell to his assistant in 1876, the first words said over the telphone were, \"Mr. Watson - come here -\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "\"You gotta watch this YouTube video!\"",
            "\"I'm worried about this mole.\"",
            "\"I want to see you.\"",
            "\"Look at this sick tattoo I got!\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"I want to see you.\""
    },
    {
        "index": 186,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which word can be combined with \"Colors,\" \"Squirrel\" and \"Buttress\" to form familiar terms?",
        "answers": [
            "trying",
            "flying",
            "crying",
            "denying"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " flying"
    },
    {
        "index": 187,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " New York and Paris have had them for years, but in 2018, with female-only audiences in attendance, what conservative country held its first-ever Fashion Week?",
        "answers": [
            "Sweden",
            "Saudi Arabia",
            "United Kingdom",
            "Brazil"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Saudi Arabia"
    },
    {
        "index": 188,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Moose, the Jack Russell terrier who played the role of Eddie, is said to have gotten more fan mail than any of his human co-stars on what '90s sitcom?",
        "answers": [
            "Friends",
            "Seinfeld",
            "Frasier",
            "Cheers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Frasier"
    },
    {
        "index": 189,
        "date": "4/26/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Calling itself America's first solar-powered town, Babcock Ranch is located in which state that's also home to the Disney-planned community of Celebration?",
        "answers": [
            "California",
            "Florida",
            "Texas",
            "Arizona"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Florida"
    },
    {
        "index": 190,
        "date": "4/19/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " The Daily Meal says to keep your reheated leftover pizza from turning into a soggy, rubbery mess, you should put it in the microwave with what?",
        "answers": [
            "mug of water",
            "metal fork",
            "metal spoon",
            "metal knife"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " mug of water"
    },
    {
        "index": 191,
        "date": "4/19/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Each year, Peter Carl Fabergé used to make one of his famous jeweled eggs as a gift for Russian Czar Alexander III's wife, fittingly presenting it to her on what holiday?",
        "answers": [
            "Easter",
            "Columbus Day",
            "Martin Luther King, Jr.'s Birthday",
            "Black Friday"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Easter"
    },
    {
        "index": 192,
        "date": "4/19/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of these words is mentioned repeatedly in the film \"Mary Poppins,\" but never uttered once in the original book by P.L. Travers?",
        "answers": [
            "the",
            "and",
            "Mary",
            "supercalifragilisticexpialidocious"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " supercalifragilisticexpialidocious"
    },
    {
        "index": 193,
        "date": "4/19/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " If today is Sábado and your Spanish-speaking friend says \"Hasta mañana!,\" what day should you expect to see them next?",
        "answers": [
            "Lunes",
            "Martes",
            "Jueves",
            "Domingo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Domingo"
    },
    {
        "index": 194,
        "date": "4/19/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " A person who suffers from misophonia would find which of these annoying habits especially annoying?",
        "answers": [
            "nose-picking",
            "chronic tardiness",
            "chewing food loudly",
            "leaving trash around"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " chewing food loudly"
    },
    {
        "index": 195,
        "date": "4/19/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Thanks to his British heritage, what former \"SNL\" cast member holds the title of Baron, and was once a sitting member of the House of Lords?",
        "answers": [
            "Mike Myers",
            "Kevin Nealon",
            "Christopher Guest",
            "Norm Macdonald"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Christopher Guest"
    },
    {
        "index": 196,
        "date": "4/19/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " On a clear day, you can see five states from atop the Empire State Building",
        "answers": [
            "Rhode Island and Delaware",
            "Vermont and New Hampshire",
            "Pennsylvania and Massachusetts",
            "Ohio and Pennsylvania"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Pennsylvania and Massachusetts"
    },
    {
        "index": 197,
        "date": "4/12/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " After displaying a warning screen, an iPhone will shut itself down until the situation normalizes in which of these cases?",
        "answers": [
            "it's in extreme heat or extreme cold",
            "it considers your selfie unflattering",
            "you're texting someone too soon after a date",
            "Siri's drunk"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " it's in extreme heat or extreme cold"
    },
    {
        "index": 198,
        "date": "4/12/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Traditionally sitting to the conductor's left and serving as their liaison to the other musicians, what term is commonly used to refer to a symphony's first-chair violinist?",
        "answers": [
            "concertmaster",
            "dungeon master",
            "View-master",
            "Thighmaster"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " concertmaster"
    },
    {
        "index": 199,
        "date": "4/12/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Hoping to save the planet by changing eating habits, what non-profit campaign was launched by Paul, Mary and Stella McCartney in 2009?",
        "answers": [
            "Meat Free Monday",
            "Waffle Wednesday",
            "Seasoned Curly Fry Friday",
            "Snausages Saturday"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Meat Free Monday"
    },
    {
        "index": 200,
        "date": "4/12/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Currently boasting about 60,000 objects in its collection, which Smithsonian museum's earliest offerings included an exhibit of traditional Chinese kites?",
        "answers": [
            "National Air and Space Museum",
            "National Postal Museum",
            "National Museum of the American Indian",
            "National Portrait Gallery"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " National Air and Space Museum"
    },
    {
        "index": 201,
        "date": "4/12/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " What famous collection of poetry did Walt Whitman first publish anonymously in 1855?",
        "answers": [
            "Grains of Sand",
            "Leaves of Grass",
            "Needles of Pine",
            "Shards of Pottery"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Leaves of Grass"
    },
    {
        "index": 202,
        "date": "4/12/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " The number of consonants in the English alphabet (including \"Y\") divided by the number of toes a rhino has on each foot equals the total number of what?",
        "answers": [
            "baseball players in a batting order",
            "\"Jurassic Park\" movies",
            "Deadly sins",
            "sides on a stop sign"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " deadly sins"
    },
    {
        "index": 203,
        "date": "4/12/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Connecting Grächen and Zermatt, what's said to the world's longest pedestrian suspension bridge --1,620 ft. long and 28 stories in the air -- opened in 2017, where?",
        "answers": [
            "Norway",
            "Ukraine",
            "Switzerland",
            "Portugal"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Switzerland"
    },
    {
        "index": 204,
        "date": "4/12/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " In Homer's \"The Odyssey,\" what sorceress of Greek mythology at one point turns Odysseus' men into swine?",
        "answers": [
            "Athena",
            "Circe",
            "Artemis",
            "Medea"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Circe"
    },
    {
        "index": 205,
        "date": "4/12/2019",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Choosing it himself as all presidents do, what is Donald Trump's Secret Service code name?",
        "answers": [
            "Magnate",
            "Mogul",
            "Maximus",
            "Money"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Mogul"
    },
    {
        "index": 206,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " A person who is in trouble is commonly said to be which of the following?",
        "answers": [
            "in a pickle",
            "in a chicken wing",
            "in a jelly donut",
            "in a BLT with extra mayo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " in a pickle"
    },
    {
        "index": 207,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " You can type your name into MissingMoney.com to see if a state is holding unclaimed cash that's due to you -- from all but which of these sources?",
        "answers": [
            "bank accounts and safe deposit boxes",
            "insurance policies and trust funds",
            "stocks, bonds and mutual funds",
            "the cushions of your old couches"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the cushions of your old couches"
    },
    {
        "index": 208,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of the following words is NOT represented by the initials in the name of the motor club AAA?",
        "answers": [
            "American",
            "Annoying",
            "Automobile",
            "Association"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Annoying"
    },
    {
        "index": 209,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Fittingly, Bolivia, Chile, Colombia and Ecuador all recognize what as their national bird?",
        "answers": [
            "Andean condor",
            "Appalachian robin",
            "Himalayan vulture",
            "Alpine swift"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Andean condor"
    },
    {
        "index": 210,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " A co-founder of the classic rock group Steely Dan, which famous Walter passed away in 2017?",
        "answers": [
            "Walter Becker",
            "Walter Matthau",
            "Walter Cronkite",
            "Walter Mondale"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Walter Becker"
    },
    {
        "index": 211,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " The sun goddess Amaterasu Omikami, or \"the great divinity illuminating heaven,\" is the most important deity of what most widely practiced religion in Japan?",
        "answers": [
            "Taoism",
            "Confucianism",
            "Shinto",
            "Jainism"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Shinto"
    },
    {
        "index": 212,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In a famous Britney Spears song, what lyric comes immediately after the line, \"Oops!...I did it again\"?",
        "answers": [
            "I mistook Jesse Eisenberg for Michael Cera",
            "I went in the pool right after I ate",
            "I transported stolen goods over state lines",
            "I played with your heart"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " I played with your heart"
    },
    {
        "index": 213,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Money-saving expert Jeff Yeager suggests that when there's no safe, travelers put their money in an empty what, as hotel thieves generally don't steal toiletries?",
        "answers": [
            "ice bucket",
            "stick of deodorant",
            "bureau drawer",
            "trash can"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " stick of deodorant"
    },
    {
        "index": 214,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " The second hand of a clock travels at approximately what speed?",
        "answers": [
            "78 rpm",
            "45 rpm",
            "33 1/3 rpm",
            "1 rpm"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 1 rpm"
    },
    {
        "index": 215,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " A fierce real-life rivalry between Cadbury and Rowntree inspired the fictional corporate rivalry in what classic children's novel?",
        "answers": [
            "The Phantom Tollbooth",
            "Black Beauty",
            "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory",
            "The Lion, The Witch and the Wardrobe"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Charlie and the Chocolate Factory"
    },
    {
        "index": 216,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " \"Himno Istmeño,\" or \"Isthmus Hymn,\" is what country's national anthem?",
        "answers": [
            "Portugal",
            "Dominican Republic",
            "Chile",
            "Panama"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Panama"
    },
    {
        "index": 217,
        "date": "3/15/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " In 2018, Stacey Cunningham made history when she became the first woman to preside over wht finance-related institution in its 226-year history?",
        "answers": [
            "New York Stock Exchange",
            "The Wall Street Journal",
            "Goldman Sachs",
            "U.S. Federal Reserve"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " New York Stock Exchange"
    },
    {
        "index": 218,
        "date": "3/8/2019",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " There are 9 U.N. member countries whose names start with the letter \"L.\" Which continent has the most?",
        "answers": [
            "Africa",
            "Asia",
            "Europe",
            "South America"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Europe"
    },
    {
        "index": 219,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to the magazine, August 10, 1968 was the first time what appeared on the cover of what?",
        "answers": [
            "a good house on Good Housekeeping",
            "a wire on Wired",
            "a fancy cat on Cat Fancy",
            "one of the Rolling Stones on Rolling Stone"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " one of the Rolling Stones on Rolling Stone"
    },
    {
        "index": 220,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these well-known tales is NOT typically found in the story collection \"The Thousand and One Nights\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Aladdin and the Wonderful Lamp",
            "The Seven Voyages of Sinbad",
            "Ali Baba & the Forty Thieves",
            "Fifty Shades of Grey"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Fifty Shades of Grey"
    },
    {
        "index": 221,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to a survey conducted by Acceleration Partners, once the bills and rent are paid, North Americans are most likely to spend their discretionary income dollars on what?",
        "answers": [
            "ant farms",
            "technology",
            "calligraphy classes",
            "berets"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " technology"
    },
    {
        "index": 222,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Making for a combined total of 14, the big toe typically has two what, while the other toes each have three?",
        "answers": [
            "bones",
            "toenails",
            "hairs",
            "bunions"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bones"
    },
    {
        "index": 223,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Replacing the backbreaking work previously done with a scythe, Edwin Budding is credited with inventing the world's first what in 1830?",
        "answers": [
            "vacuum cleaner",
            "dishwasher",
            "lawn mower",
            "jackhammer"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " lawn mower"
    },
    {
        "index": 224,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Known for his roles as a taxi dispatcher, \"Batman\" nemesis and edgy sitcom dad, in 2018 what actor was honored with his own day in Asbury Park, New Jersey?",
        "answers": [
            "Ray Liotta",
            "Joe Pesci",
            "Danny DeVito",
            "John Travolta"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Danny DeVito"
    },
    {
        "index": 225,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " It's Millionaire Poetry Time! If you're visiting New Orleans/and want to fill your gut/order étouffée/best described as what?",
        "answers": [
            "rich chocolate dessert",
            "Creole-style coffee drink",
            "spicy beef sandwich",
            "crawfish stew over rice"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " crawfish stew over rice"
    },
    {
        "index": 226,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " The Chunnel opened, Nelson Mandela was inaugurated president of South Africa, and Ace of Base saw \"The Sign\" hit #1 in May of what year?",
        "answers": [
            "1984",
            "1989",
            "1994",
            "1999"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 1994"
    },
    {
        "index": 227,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " According to U.S. federal weather data, which state holds the record for the widest range between its all-time high and low temperatures",
        "answers": [
            "California",
            "Montana",
            "New York",
            "South Carolina"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Montana"
    },
    {
        "index": 228,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Used to describe quiet and peaceful days, the word \"halcyon\" is derived from the Greek name for a mythical type of what creature?",
        "answers": [
            "horse",
            "bird",
            "deer",
            "cat"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bird"
    },
    {
        "index": 229,
        "date": "3/1/2019",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " Which of these denominations of old British money was worth the least?",
        "answers": [
            "guinea",
            "farthing",
            "halfpenny",
            "florin"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " farthing"
    },
    {
        "index": 230,
        "date": "2/22/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " \"Where do you get your protein from?\", \"But what about bacon?\", and \"Then what do you eat?\" are all on TheKitchn.com's list of thiNgs not to say to whom?",
        "answers": [
            "vegans",
            "valets",
            "ventriloquists",
            "vice presidents"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " vegans"
    },
    {
        "index": 231,
        "date": "2/22/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Bjork, Keith Urban and Annie Lennox are some of the performers who've had to cancel concerts due to \"Singer's Nodes,\" which are polyps found where?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "between the toes",
            "on the vocal cords",
            "on the back of the wrist",
            "behind the knees"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " on the vocal cords"
    },
    {
        "index": 232,
        "date": "2/22/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " When she won the Miss America Pageant in 1945, Bess Myerson became the first - and to date, only - winner who was what?",
        "answers": [
            "Jewish",
            "over 120 years old",
            "over 8 feet tall",
            "a U.S. citizen"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Jewish"
    },
    {
        "index": 233,
        "date": "2/22/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " In government slang, unwanted but un-fireable civil servants are often warehoused in non-essential agencies that are referred to by what avian term?",
        "answers": [
            "apple orchards",
            "turkey farms",
            "cabbage patches",
            "lemming ranches"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " turkey farms"
    },
    {
        "index": 234,
        "date": "2/22/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " If you filled in the blanks in the titles of the following famous TV shows, which blank would have the second-highest number?",
        "answers": [
            "\"_____ Jump Street\"",
            "\"Beverly Hills, ______\"",
            "\"_____ Broke Girls\"",
            "\"_____ Rock\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"_____ Rock\""
    },
    {
        "index": 235,
        "date": "2/22/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " First opening in 1923, what stadium is the only facility in the world to have hosted two Summer Olympic Games (and might host a third in 2028)?",
        "answers": [
            "Lambeau Field",
            "Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum",
            "Soldier Field",
            "Giants Stadium"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum"
    },
    {
        "index": 236,
        "date": "2/22/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Ultimately falling back to Earth with the rain, the dust from what desert travels across the Atlantic Ocean to provide vital nutrients for the Amazon rainforest?",
        "answers": [
            "Mojave Desert",
            "Patagonian Desert",
            "Sahara Desert",
            "Gobi Desert"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Sahara Desert"
    },
    {
        "index": 237,
        "date": "2/15/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " The name of the candy bar Twix is said to be a stylized mash-up of which two words?",
        "answers": [
            "twin + sticks",
            "twist + Brexit",
            "twinkle + beatniks",
            "twelve + LEGO bricks"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "twin + sticks"
    },
    {
        "index": 238,
        "date": "2/15/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Credited with saving countless lives, what inexpensive, single battery-operated household device did Duane P. Pearsall pioneer in the mid-1960s?",
        "answers": [
            "TV remote",
            "back massager",
            "travel alarm clock",
            "smoke detector"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "smoke detector"
    },
    {
        "index": 239,
        "date": "2/15/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " As you can tell from its \"root\" word, someone who suffers from hyperdontia has an excessive number of what?",
        "answers": [
            "teeth",
            "fingers",
            "organs",
            "vertebrae"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "teeth"
    },
    {
        "index": 240,
        "date": "2/15/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " The city of Vladivostock is the last stop on which famous rail line?",
        "answers": [
            "The Trans-Siberian Railroad",
            "The Darjeeling Limited",
            "The Orient Express",
            "The Rocky Mountaineer"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "The Trans-Siberian Railroad"
    },
    {
        "index": 241,
        "date": "2/15/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " If Snow White's seven dwarfs stood in alphabetical order according to their names in the 1937 Disney movie, which one would be right in the middle at #4?",
        "answers": [
            "Dopey",
            "Grumpy",
            "Happy",
            "Sleepy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Grumpy"
    },
    {
        "index": 242,
        "date": "2/15/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " By definition, which of these things is true about a food that's been \"desiccated\"?",
        "answers": [
            "it's spicy",
            "it's dried out",
            "it's without its peel or skin",
            "it's sliced into strips"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " it's dried out"
    },
    {
        "index": 243,
        "date": "2/8/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In a famous scene in the classic movie \"A Christmas Story,\" what does Schwartz \"triple dog dare\" Flick to do?",
        "answers": [
            "drink puddle water",
            "throw a rock at a window",
            "sled down a steep hill",
            "stick his tongue to a pole"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " stick his tongue to a pole"
    },
    {
        "index": 244,
        "date": "2/8/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " With a name meaning \"earth pig\" in Afrikaans, what one-of-a-kind animal is the only surviving member of its order, family and genus?",
        "answers": [
            "porcupine",
            "armadillo",
            "platypus",
            "aardvark"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "aardvark"
    },
    {
        "index": 245,
        "date": "2/8/2019",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Not including Mexico and Canada, what foreign nation lies closest to the U.S.?",
        "answers": [
            "Cuba",
            "the Bahamas",
            "Russia",
            "the Dominican Republic"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "index": 246,
        "date": "2/8/2019",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " Because it contains a special amino acid that stimulates the enzymes that break down alcohol, which of these is often touted as a hangover cure?",
        "answers": [
            "orange juice",
            "pork",
            "asparagus",
            "popcorn"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "asparagus"
    },
    {
        "index": 247,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In recipes, what does the \"AP\" stand for in the phrase \"AP flour\"?",
        "answers": [
            "all-purpose",
            "amazingly pricey",
            "avocado-pigeon",
            "awful product"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " all-purpose"
    },
    {
        "index": 248,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Due to its extremely violent content, whose TV broadcasts are typically preceded by a \"viewer discretion advised\" warning?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Scripps National Spelling Bee",
            "PGA Tour",
            "UFC",
            "Antiques Roadshow"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " UFC"
    },
    {
        "index": 249,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " From her 1965 duet \"I Got You Babe\" to \"Believe\" 34  years later in 1999, who has the record for the longest time between their first and last #1 hits on the Billboard Hot 100?",
        "answers": [
            "Dolly Parton",
            "Stevie Nicks",
            "Cher",
            "Diana Ross"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Cher"
    },
    {
        "index": 250,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " The popular Russian social media site Ok.ru was originally called Odnoklassniki, since (as you might guess from its name) it helps users reconnect with whom?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "oddballs",
            "oddballs with no class",
            "former classmates",
            "people named Nicky"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " former classmates"
    },
    {
        "index": 251,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " In 2017, what state you don't usually associate with alcohol consumption adopted the strictest drunk driving law in the U.S., lowering the BAC [Chris said \"blood alcohol content\"] limit from 0.08 to 0.05?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Virginia",
            "Texas",
            "Utah",
            "Florida"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Utah"
    },
    {
        "index": 252,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Of all the 3-letter words that begin with \"I\" in the Official Scrabble Players Dictionary, the one that comes last alphabetically is defined how?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "an ornamental climbing plant",
            "a mischievous child",
            "to annoy",
            "a subatomic particle"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " an ornamental climbing plant"
    },
    {
        "index": 253,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " With federal resources not what they used to be, in 1993 the Smithsonian Institution began asking visitors to do what, for the first time in its 147-year history?",
        "answers": [
            "feed tour guides scraps from their lunches",
            "handle locking the place up at night",
            "donate money",
            "bring their own dinosaur bones"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " donate money"
    },
    {
        "index": 254,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " If milk is heated to 280 degrees for 2 seconds, then rapidly cooled, it will be 99.9% free of bacteria because it's just been what?",
        "answers": [
            "ultra-pasteurized",
            "totes-dehydrated",
            "pickled to the 10th power",
            "supermega-offended"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ultra-pasteurized"
    },
    {
        "index": 255,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of the following is not one of the three supernatural beings found in the classic 1962 book (and 2018 movie) \"A Wrinkle in Time\"?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Mrs. Who",
            "Mrs. Which",
            "Mrs. Whatsit",
            "Mrs. Whaaasuuuuup?"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Mrs. Whaaasuuuuup?"
    },
    {
        "index": 256,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Though it hopefully doesn't just constantly repeat the word \"Nevermore\" as it does in Edgar Alla Poe's famous poem, which of these birds can be trained to talk?",
        "answers": [
            "hummingbird",
            "bald eagle",
            "raven",
            "falcon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " raven"
    },
    {
        "index": 257,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " The first documented baby to have been born in Antarctica, Emilio Palma had a mother from what country -- the closest to Antarctica of these four?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Argentina",
            "Colombia",
            "Peru",
            "Venezuela"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Argentina"
    },
    {
        "index": 258,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " As the sole person who's at least 21 years old, as of today, which of these celebrities is the only one who could legally play blackjack here in a Las Vegas casino?",
        "answers": [
            "Jaden Smith",
            "Elle Fanning",
            "Malia Obama",
            "Kendall Jenner"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Kendall Jenner"
    },
    {
        "index": 259,
        "date": "2/1/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Which of these people is the most likely to be described as \"risible\"?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "mountain climber",
            "stand-up comedian",
            "police officer",
            "chef"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " stand-up comedian"
    },
    {
        "index": 260,
        "date": "1/25/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Even when it's viewed from a telescope millions of miles away, what does Britannica claim is \"arguably the most sublime object in the solar system\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Chris Hemsworth",
            "Saturn",
            "a Big Mac",
            "the new 2019 Dodge Grand Caravan"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Saturn"
    },
    {
        "index": 261,
        "date": "1/25/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to the Bureau of Labor Statistics, the average American spends 62% of their money on just three things. Which of these is NOT one of them?",
        "answers": [
            "housing",
            "transportation",
            "bail",
            "food"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bail"
    },
    {
        "index": 262,
        "date": "1/25/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of these is NOT the name of one of history's most powerful ruling empires?",
        "answers": [
            "Persian Empire",
            "Holy Roman Empire",
            "Ottoman Empire",
            "Galactic Empire"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Galactic Empire"
    },
    {
        "index": 263,
        "date": "1/25/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " With his \"Achy Breaky Song\" in 1993 and \"Party in the CIA\" in 2011, \"Weird Al\" Yankovic parodied both a father and daughter with what last name?",
        "answers": [
            "Sinatra",
            "Tyler",
            "Cyrus",
            "Cole"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Cyrus"
    },
    {
        "index": 264,
        "date": "1/25/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Due to the nature of the footwork involved, what sport's shoes commonly feature spikes in the heel?",
        "answers": [
            "bowling",
            "high jump",
            "beach volleyball",
            "wrestling"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " high jump"
    },
    {
        "index": 265,
        "date": "1/25/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Both a type of rice cake, banh chung and banh day are traditionally eaten during Tet, the New Year's celebration in what country?",
        "answers": [
            "China",
            "Vietnam",
            "Thailand",
            "South Korea"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Vietnam"
    },
    {
        "index": 266,
        "date": "1/25/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " In the world of musical instruments, sustin, una corda and sostenuto are the names of the three standard what?",
        "answers": [
            "valves on a trumpet",
            "holes on a flute",
            "sides of a triangle",
            "pedals on a grand piano"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " pedals on a grand piano"
    },
    {
        "index": 267,
        "date": "1/18/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " According to the 19th-century German philosophr Arthur Schopenhauer, the two foes of human happiness are what and what?",
        "answers": [
            "the DMV and the IRS",
            "spotty WiFi and bad cable reception",
            "pain and boredom",
            "itchy sweaters and smooth jazz"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " pain and boredom"
    },
    {
        "index": 268,
        "date": "1/18/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Popular at college parties, the drinking game that involves flipping a red, plastic SOLO brand drinking vessel so it lands face down on a table is aptly called what?",
        "answers": [
            "Flip Cup",
            "Plate Toss",
            "Spoon Jousting",
            "Battle of the Forks"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Flip Cup"
    },
    {
        "index": 269,
        "date": "1/18/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Located in Kentucky, the United States Bullion Depository is more commonly called what?",
        "answers": [
            "Library of Congress",
            "Fort Knox",
            "Ellis Island",
            "Hoover Dam"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Fort Knox"
    },
    {
        "index": 270,
        "date": "1/18/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Though it later had to be changed because the first part was copyrighted by a mop company, which of these was the original name of a famous cartoon character?",
        "answers": [
            "Winnie-the-Shoe",
            "Mugs Bunny",
            "Spongeboy Squarepants",
            "Mini Cooper Mouse"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Spongeboy Squarepants"
    },
    {
        "index": 271,
        "date": "1/18/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Hemoglobin, a protein that transports oxygen to the tissues of the body, is found in which type of blood cells?",
        "answers": [
            "red blood cells",
            "white blood cells",
            "blue blood cells",
            "green blood cells"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " red blood cells"
    },
    {
        "index": 272,
        "date": "1/18/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " While \"Don't Fear the Reaper\" is famous thanks to a popular \"SNL\" sketch, \"Low Rider,\" \"Drive My Car,\" and \"Honky Tonk Women\" all also prominently use what instrument?",
        "answers": [
            "kettle drum",
            "sitar",
            "cowbell",
            "didgeridoo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cowbell"
    },
    {
        "index": 273,
        "date": "1/18/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " The site of the famous invasion on D-Day, the French region of Normandy is situated in which part of the country?",
        "answers": [
            "northwestern",
            "northeastern",
            "southwestern",
            "southeastern"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " northwestern"
    },
    {
        "index": 274,
        "date": "1/18/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Hate the cold? You might want to visit what country, which has never had a recorded temperature below 65 degrees Fahrenheit?",
        "answers": [
            "Singapore",
            "Italy",
            "Australia",
            "Iran"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Singapore"
    },
    {
        "index": 275,
        "date": "1/18/2019",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Developed in 1824 by 15-year-old Louis Braille, the Braille syste consists of over 60 characters, each made up of between one and how many raised dots?",
        "answers": [
            "4",
            "5",
            "6",
            "7"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 6"
    },
    {
        "index": 276,
        "date": "1/11/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which element's name fittingly comes from Greek roots meaning \"water creator\"?",
        "answers": [
            "nitrogen",
            "chlorine",
            "hydrogen",
            "fluorine"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " hydrogen"
    },
    {
        "index": 277,
        "date": "1/11/2019",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " According to USA Today, all but which of the following are signs that your electronic device has been hacked?",
        "answers": [
            "it slows down",
            "it suddenly restarts",
            "Siri now speaks with a Russian accent",
            "your programs and apps crash"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Siri now speaks with a Russian accent"
    },
    {
        "index": 278,
        "date": "1/11/2019",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " An homage to the everyday American, which of these is an uplifting piece of patriotic music composed by Aaron Copland in 1942?",
        "answers": [
            "\"Fanfare for the Common Man\"",
            "\"Ballad of the Mouth-Breathers\"",
            "\"Flyover Country Serenade\"",
            "\"The Joe Six-Pack Polka\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"Fanfare for the Common Man\""
    },
    {
        "index": 279,
        "date": "1/11/2019",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " By definition, a \"visceral\" reaction is one you feel in which part of the body?",
        "answers": [
            "feet",
            "elbow",
            "gut",
            "teeth"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " gut"
    },
    {
        "index": 280,
        "date": "1/11/2019",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Later saying she wanted to turn her divorce \"into a positive,\" in 2014 who famously used the term \"conscious uncoupling\" when announcing her split from Chris Martin?",
        "answers": [
            "Jennifer Aniston",
            "Reese Witherspoon",
            "Jennifer Garner",
            "Gwyneth Paltrow"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Gwyneth Paltrow"
    },
    {
        "index": 281,
        "date": "1/11/2019",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " In addition to English, which U.S. state recognizes 20 different official languages, including Eyak, Holikachuk and Inupiaq?",
        "answers": [
            "Louisiana",
            "Hawaii",
            "New Mexico",
            "Alaska"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Alaska"
    },
    {
        "index": 282,
        "date": "1/11/2019",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Touted for their nutritional value, what does Merriam-Webster say is the proper pronunciation of the tropical berries that in English are spelled \"a-c-a-i\"?",
        "answers": [
            "ah-sah-EE",
            "ack-EYE",
            "ah-KAH-ee",
            "atch-EYE"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ah-sah-EE"
    },
    {
        "index": 283,
        "date": "1/11/2019",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " What director came up with the idea for 2018's Best Picture Oscar winner after being denied permission to remake \"The Creature From The Black Lagoon?\"",
        "answers": [
            "Alejandro Inarritu",
            "Alfonso Curaron",
            "Guillermo del Toro",
            "Denis Villeneuve"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Guillermo del Toro"
    },
    {
        "index": 284,
        "date": "1/11/2019",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Three of the following are the initials of title characters from Charles Dickens novels. Which one is NOT?",
        "answers": [
            "JE",
            "ED",
            "OT",
            "DC"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " JE"
    },
    {
        "index": 285,
        "date": "12/14/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of the following is NOT a type of bird?",
        "answers": [
            "shoebill",
            "spoonbill",
            "hornbill",
            "creditcardbill"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " creditcardbill"
    },
    {
        "index": 286,
        "date": "12/14/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In the Bible, a young Esau famously trades what to his brother Jacob for a bowl of lentil stew?",
        "answers": [
            "his Sony PlayStation",
            "his birthright",
            "his Paw Patrol pajamas",
            "his Old Testament action figures"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " his birthright"
    },
    {
        "index": 287,
        "date": "12/14/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Designer Patricia Field created so many iconic outfits - including the tutu seen in the opening credits - \"fashion\" has been called the \"5th character\" of what TV show?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "According to Jim",
            "Prison Break",
            "Sex and the City",
            "Naked and Afraid"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Sex and the City"
    },
    {
        "index": 288,
        "date": "12/14/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " \"Yo,\" \"eg,\" \"je,\" \"ja\" and \"jeg\" are all ways to say what first-person pronoun in various European languages?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "they",
            "I",
            "it",
            "he"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " I"
    },
    {
        "index": 289,
        "date": "12/14/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Between August 9th, 1974 and December 19th, 1974, the United States did not have which of the following?",
        "answers": [
            "a vice president",
            "a citizen over 100 years old",
            "telephone service",
            "a military"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a vice president"
    },
    {
        "index": 290,
        "date": "12/14/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Which of these famous \"Parks\" is located the farthest west?",
        "answers": [
            "Central Park",
            "Fenway Park",
            "Paisley Park",
            "Belmont Park"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Paisley Park"
    },
    {
        "index": 291,
        "date": "12/14/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Which of these actors played both a major character in Aaron Sorkin's 1995 film \"The American President\" and a regular character on his TV series \"The West Wing\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Annette Bening",
            "Rob Lowe",
            "Martin Sheen",
            "Bradley Whitford"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Martin Sheen"
    },
    {
        "index": 292,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In the Marvel comic books starring the Norse god Thor, which of these is NOT one of the mythological Ten Realms conected by the tree Yggdrasil?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Niffleheim",
            "Jotunheim",
            "Svartalheim",
            "downtown Anaheim"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " downtown Anaheim"
    },
    {
        "index": 293,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In his Grammy-winning hit \"Humble and Kind,\" Tim McGraw gives a child some life advice, including all but which of these admonitions?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "don't lie",
            "don't cheat",
            "don't steal",
            "don't intimidate a federal witness"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " don't intimidate a federal witness"
    },
    {
        "index": 294,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " A padded, angled bench resembling the front of a pulpit is used to perform what fittingly-named weight training exercise that strengthens the biceps?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "bartender lifts",
            "preacher curls",
            "dry cleaner presses",
            "dentist squats"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " preacher curls"
    },
    {
        "index": 295,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " To determine the length of something using only pocket change, just remember that the diameter of a quarter is roughly equal to which measurement?",
        "answers": [
            "one inch",
            "one food",
            "one yard",
            "one mile"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " one inch"
    },
    {
        "index": 296,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Complete this lyric from a classic Cole Porter song",
        "answers": [
            "poop on people at the beach",
            "sting someone and die",
            "make dogs itchy while reading Kirkegaard",
            "fall in love"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " fall in love"
    },
    {
        "index": 297,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In 2017, Today.com said \"Taco Bell's R&D department is either run by stoners or 13-year-olds\" after its U.S. testing of the Chocladilla, a tortilla stuffed with what?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "crushed Cap'n Crunch",
            "shredded Twizzlers",
            "melted Kit Kats or Twix",
            "smushed Twinkies"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " melted Kit Kats or Twix"
    },
    {
        "index": 298,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Vulture.com lists \"A '90s actress you almost forgot about\"; \"a failing family business\" and \"a town with a dumb name\" among its \"10 Essentials of Any\" what?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Hallmark Christmas movie",
            "Saturday morning cartoon",
            "ESPN sports broadcast",
            "National Geographic documentary"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Hallmark Christmas movie"
    },
    {
        "index": 299,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Apparently interested in other kinds of exploration, what author of \"2001",
        "answers": [
            "Philip K. Dick",
            "Arthur C. Clarke",
            "Ray Bradbury",
            "Aldous Huxley"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Arthur C. Clarke"
    },
    {
        "index": 300,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Not counting the spaces between them, how many total stripes appear on a typical pair of Adidas' iconic Superstar sneakers?",
        "answers": [
            "8",
            "12",
            "16",
            "20"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 12"
    },
    {
        "index": 301,
        "date": "11/23/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Aiding in the absorption and digestion of fats, the yellow or greenish fluid known as bile is initially produced by what body part?",
        "answers": [
            "kidneys",
            "liver",
            "appendix",
            "pancreas"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " liver"
    },
    {
        "index": 302,
        "date": "12/7/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Befitting its nickname, \"The Emerald Isle of the Caribbean,\" Montserrat's passport stamp features a big green what?",
        "answers": [
            "dollar sign",
            "shamrock",
            "zucchini",
            "Christmas sweater"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " shamrock"
    },
    {
        "index": 303,
        "date": "12/7/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Stam Train Maury, Frisco Jack and Connecticut Slim are a few of the legendary vagabonds celebrated at what Britt, IA landmark?",
        "answers": [
            "National Prospector Museum",
            "National Farmer Museum",
            "National Inventor Museum",
            "National Hobo Museum"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "National Hobo Museum"
    },
    {
        "index": 304,
        "date": "12/7/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " On MSNBC, the stylized version of the title of the political talk show \"Hardball with Chris Matthews\" features what two letters appropriately colored red and blue, respectively?",
        "answers": [
            "H and A",
            "R and D",
            "B and A",
            "L and L"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "R and D"
    },
    {
        "index": 305,
        "date": "12/7/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Born in 1564 like the famous astronomer, what great Renaissance mind is said to allude to Galileo's discovery of Jupiter's moons in his play \"Cymbeline\"?",
        "answers": [
            "John Milton",
            "Voltaire",
            "William Shakespeare",
            "Martin Luther"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "William Shakespeare"
    },
    {
        "index": 306,
        "date": "12/7/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Contrary to popular belief, National Geographic confirms that you can't completely sink in ordinary quicksand, due to your body's relatively lower what?",
        "answers": [
            "density",
            "volume",
            "mass",
            "surface area"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "density"
    },
    {
        "index": 307,
        "date": "12/7/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Receiving the awards in 1969 and 1977, respectively, who is the only Best Actress Oscar winner to also win an Oscar for Best Original Song?",
        "answers": [
            "Julie Andrews",
            "Barbra Streisand",
            "Liza Minnelli",
            "Cher"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Barbra Streisand"
    },
    {
        "index": 308,
        "date": "11/30/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to a quip by Republican icon Ronald Reagan, \"I'm from\" where \"and I'm here to help\" are the nine most terrifying words in the English language?",
        "answers": [
            "The Red Cross",
            "the government",
            "the future",
            "the auto club"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the government"
    },
    {
        "index": 309,
        "date": "11/30/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " E.M. Forster wrote an acclaimed 1908 novel titled \"A Room With a\" what - a feature that many Las Vegas visitors would enjoy?",
        "answers": [
            "view",
            "sweet minibar",
            "coin-operated vibrating bed",
            "hair dryer that actually works"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " view"
    },
    {
        "index": 310,
        "date": "11/30/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In 2018, after neighbors reported hearing voices shouting next door, German police arrived to find a man arguing with his girlfriend's pet what?",
        "answers": [
            "goldfish",
            "parrot",
            "turtle",
            "hamster"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " parrot"
    },
    {
        "index": 311,
        "date": "11/30/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Introduced to the candy market in 1938, a Nestle Crunch bar gets its \"crunch\" from what ingredient?",
        "answers": [
            "crisped rice",
            "barbecue potato chips",
            "carrots",
            "shards of glass"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " crisped rice"
    },
    {
        "index": 312,
        "date": "11/30/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " In a 1913 Harper's Weekly article about government transparency, Justice Louis Brandeis famously wrote, \"Sunlight is said to the best of...\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "furniture polishes",
            "disinfectants",
            "dishwasher detergents",
            "carpet cleaners"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " disinfectants"
    },
    {
        "index": 313,
        "date": "11/30/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " The main difference between DayQuil and NyQuil is that DayQuil does not contain what ingredient that causes drowsiness?",
        "answers": [
            "acetaminophen",
            "an antihistamine",
            "eucalyptus oil",
            "citric acid"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "an antihistamine"
    },
    {
        "index": 314,
        "date": "11/30/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Ineligible to be called \"Princess\" as she has no royal heritage, Meghan Markle was given what tongue-twisting title when she married Prince Harry?",
        "answers": [
            "The Duchess of Sussex",
            "The Marchioness of Merseyside",
            "The Baroness of Bedfordshire",
            "The Viscountess of Worcestershire"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "The Duchess of Sussex"
    },
    {
        "index": 315,
        "date": "11/30/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Traditionally, in what order are the three events of a triathlon held, going from first to last?",
        "answers": [
            "swim, bike, run",
            "run, swim, bike",
            "run, bike, swim",
            "bike, swim, run"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "swim, bike, run"
    },
    {
        "index": 316,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Of the 80-plus men to sail from Spain aboard Christopher Columbus' ships the Niña, Pinta and Santa Maria, nearly one in four were named what?",
        "answers": [
            "Jayden",
            "Max",
            "Juan",
            "Skyler"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Juan"
    },
    {
        "index": 317,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " With only about 1,400 accepted each year, most U.S. Air Force Academy applicants must be nominated by either a member of Congress or whom?",
        "answers": [
            "their 6th grade volleyball coach",
            "a third cousin on their mother's side",
            "the Vice President of the United States",
            "one of the actors in \"Top Gun\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the Vice President of the United States"
    },
    {
        "index": 318,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Musicians like Bob Dylan and Bruce Springsteen often use a hands-free neck device called a holder or rack so they can play what simultaneously with the guitar?",
        "answers": [
            "the harmonica",
            "the triangle",
            "the maracas",
            "ping-pong"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the harmonica"
    },
    {
        "index": 319,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In the wake of a slew of fashion designers pledging to stop using it, in 2018 San Francisco became the first major U.S. city to officially ban the sale of what?",
        "answers": [
            "real animal fur",
            "deodorant",
            "birth control",
            "mayonnaise"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " real animal fur"
    },
    {
        "index": 320,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Which of these is not a type of massage, nor a brand of car NOR another word for harakiri, but rather a puzzle where you insert numbers into a grid?",
        "answers": [
            "subaru",
            "shiatsu",
            "seppuku",
            "sudoku"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " sudoku"
    },
    {
        "index": 321,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which of the following pairs of countries are farthest from each other?",
        "answers": [
            "Afghanistan & Pakistan",
            "Czech Republic & Central African Republic",
            "Uruguay & Paraguay",
            "Australia & Austria"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Australia & Austria"
    },
    {
        "index": 322,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Which pair of \"H\" names are the first name of boxing great \"Macho\" Camacho and a great Trojan warrior of myth, respectively?",
        "answers": [
            "Hórace and Horace",
            "Héctor and Hector",
            "Hérmes and Hermes",
            "Hómer and Homer"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Héctor and Hector"
    },
    {
        "index": 323,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Which of the following contains all seven of the letters commonly used to form Roman numerals?",
        "answers": [
            "MILD MILL",
            "DID I MIMIC DILL",
            "VIVID VIM",
            "MIX CIVIL LID"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " MIX CIVIL LID"
    },
    {
        "index": 324,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Rarely occurring in the continental U.S., but prevalent in Latin America, Puerto Rico and parts of Asia, dengue is transmitted by what?",
        "answers": [
            "mosquitoes",
            "unclean drinking water",
            "kissing",
            "dog bites"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " mosquitoes"
    },
    {
        "index": 325,
        "date": "11/9/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " In \"Anchorman,\" what fictional TV station is home to legendary newscaster Ron Burgundy?",
        "answers": [
            "KVWN",
            "KBBL",
            "WPBH",
            "WQHG"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " KVWN"
    },
    {
        "index": 326,
        "date": "11/2/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " To protect its brand, instead of selling off its older signature brown trucks, what company simply repaints them white and uses them for internal tasks?",
        "answers": [
            "Domino's",
            "UPS",
            "U-Haul",
            "Good Humor"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "UPS"
    },
    {
        "index": 327,
        "date": "11/2/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Because many dogs get scared and run away the night before, what is generally considered the busiest day of the year at dog shelters?",
        "answers": [
            "February 15th",
            "April 16th",
            "July 5th",
            "December 26th"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "July 5th"
    },
    {
        "index": 328,
        "date": "11/2/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " In the same way that Donald Duck has Huey, Dewey and Louie, Mickey Mouse has two what, named Morty and Ferdie?",
        "answers": [
            "grandfathers",
            "lawyers",
            "nephews",
            "mechanics"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "nephews"
    },
    {
        "index": 329,
        "date": "11/2/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " According to the official MLB rules in Spanish, first base is called \"primera.\" All but which of these are the Spanish words for the other three bases?",
        "answers": [
            "segunda",
            "plato",
            "tercera",
            "pelota"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "pelota"
    },
    {
        "index": 330,
        "date": "11/2/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Bill of Rights nerds know that \"probable cause\" is a phrase found in which amendent to the Constitution?",
        "answers": [
            "first",
            "fourth",
            "fifth",
            "ninth"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "fourth"
    },
    {
        "index": 331,
        "date": "11/2/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " A Russian estate where a specific type of fruit is grown provides the setting for what last play written by Anton Chekhov?",
        "answers": [
            "The Strawberry Garden",
            "The Cherry Orchard",
            "The Cranberry Bog",
            "The Orange Grove"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "The Cherry Orchard"
    },
    {
        "index": 332,
        "date": "11/2/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Currently, the longest non-stop flight originating in the U.S. is the 8,700-mile United Airlines jaunt from LAX to Changi Airport, the main airport in which country?",
        "answers": [
            "The Philippines",
            "Vietnam",
            "China",
            "Singapore"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Singapore"
    },
    {
        "index": 333,
        "date": "11/2/2018",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " The largest crowd in TX history to assemble for a one-day event, an estimated 400K people gathered in San Antonio in September 1987 to see whom?",
        "answers": [
            "Michael Jackson",
            "President Ronald Reagan",
            "Queen Elizabeth II",
            "Pope John Paul II"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Pope John Paul II"
    },
    {
        "index": 334,
        "date": "11/2/2018",
        "prize": "100,000",
        "question": " All but which of the following are true of Tony the Tiger as he currently appears on boxes of Kellogg's Frosted Flakes?",
        "answers": [
            "the \"whites\" of his eyes are yellow",
            "his whiskers are orange",
            "his ears are black and white",
            "the tip of his nose is blue"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "his whiskers are orange"
    },
    {
        "index": 335,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Although commonly known as the Eros statue, the winged cherub atop a famed Piccadilly Circus fountain in London actually depicts Eros' brother - who?",
        "answers": [
            "Lyle",
            "Kevin",
            "Anteros",
            "Randy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Anteros"
    },
    {
        "index": 336,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " What is the official state dance of Hawaii?",
        "answers": [
            "the Hokey Pokey",
            "the Robot",
            "the Hula",
            "the \"Thriller\" dance"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the Hula"
    },
    {
        "index": 337,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Who of the following is NOT known for wearing the letter \"A\" on his or her clothing?",
        "answers": [
            "Captain America",
            "Alvin the Chipmunk",
            "Hester Prynn in \"The Scarlet Letter\"",
            "Adam from the Bible"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Adam from the Bible"
    },
    {
        "index": 338,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " According to do-it-yourselfer website BobVila.com, if you want your candles to last longer, you should put them in what for a while?",
        "answers": [
            "the freezer",
            "the oven",
            "the blender",
            "the DVD player"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the freezer"
    },
    {
        "index": 339,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Rhyming with a hairstyle associated with good ol' boys, a bald head with long hair in the back is commonly called wht?",
        "answers": [
            "headlocks",
            "skullet",
            "fuzz cut",
            "fauxhawk"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " skullet"
    },
    {
        "index": 340,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " The mascot for the NFL team of which of these cities is a horse named Miles?",
        "answers": [
            "Cincinnati",
            "Buffalo",
            "Baltimore",
            "Denver"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Denver"
    },
    {
        "index": 341,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Thirty-five years after his infamous crime, who was released back into society in 2016, under orders to live with his mother in her Virginia home for at least a year?",
        "answers": [
            "Ted Bundy",
            "John Hinkley",
            "David Berkowitz",
            "Bernhard Goetz"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " John Hinkley"
    },
    {
        "index": 342,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " In April 2018, who set a new record for solo female artists by having 13 hits on the Billboard Hot 100 simultaneously, including \"I Like It\" and \"Finesse\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Dua Lipa",
            "Cardi B",
            "Camila Cabello",
            "Nicki Minaj"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Cardi B"
    },
    {
        "index": 343,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " The name of what South American country's capital roughly translates to English as \"I see a mountain\".",
        "answers": [
            "Peru",
            "Venezuela",
            "Chile",
            "Uruguay"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Uruguay"
    },
    {
        "index": 344,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " While most of the world drives on the right, all but which of these countries still drive on the left, as they were once ruled by the British?",
        "answers": [
            "Trinidad & Tobago",
            "Malaysia",
            "Mongolia",
            "Uganda"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Mongolia"
    },
    {
        "index": 345,
        "date": "10/26/2018",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " Which of these pairs of celebrities were both born in the same year?",
        "answers": [
            "Tom Cruise & Tom Hanks",
            "Naomi Watts & Cameron Diaz",
            "Beyonce & Britney Spears",
            "Rihanna & Miley Cyrus"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Beyonce & Britney Spears"
    },
    {
        "index": 346,
        "date": "10/19/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Of all the 50 U.S. states, there is only one that gets its name from what?",
        "answers": [
            "a Native American word",
            "a European royal",
            "a Spanish word",
            "a U.S. president"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "a U.S. president"
    },
    {
        "index": 347,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Letting celebs like Anne Hathaway and Mike Tyson show off a hidden talent, which recurring \"Tonight Show\" bit was spun off as its own show in 2015?",
        "answers": [
            "Stupid Human Tricks",
            "Lip Sync Battle",
            "Mean Tweets",
            "Your Moment of Zen"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Lip Sync Battle"
    },
    {
        "index": 348,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Though it's now banned, in which of these competitions have participants often been known to hit opponents over the head with metal folding chairs?",
        "answers": [
            "Wimbledon",
            "The Masters",
            "WrestleMania",
            "Scripps National Spelling Bee"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " WrestleMania"
    },
    {
        "index": 349,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Dubbed his \"Annus Mirabilis,\" the year 1905 saw Albert Einstein publish 4 papers that set the stage for modern physics. Which of these concepts did he NOT address?",
        "answers": [
            "photoelectric effect",
            "bed head",
            "Brownian motion",
            "special relativity"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bed head"
    },
    {
        "index": 350,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of the following is a government ruled by the wealthy--NOT, as its name might imply, by a cartoon dog?",
        "answers": [
            "Droopyocracy",
            "Snoopyocracy",
            "Scoobyocracy",
            "Plutocracy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Plutocracy"
    },
    {
        "index": 351,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Used by some performers to calm stage fright, what fruit's high levels of potassium help it to act as a natural beta blocker for anxiety?",
        "answers": [
            "apple",
            "banana",
            "strawberry",
            "watermelon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " banana"
    },
    {
        "index": 352,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Winner of the 2018 Pulitzer Prize for Biography, \"Prairie Fires\" by Caroline Fraser tells the story of what celebrated American author of YA novels?",
        "answers": [
            "Louisa May Alcott",
            "Beverly Cleary",
            "Judy Blume",
            "Laura Ingalls Wilder"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Laura Ingalls Wilder"
    },
    {
        "index": 353,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Roughly translating to English as \"Rest in peace,\" the abbreviation R.I.P. actually stands for what Latin phrase?",
        "answers": [
            "rex iuvant patrona",
            "requiescat in pace",
            "res ipsa publica",
            "reductio infinitum prospice"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " requiescat in pace"
    },
    {
        "index": 354,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Performed by the show's house band, The Roots, the opening theme song for \"The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon\" features which set of repetitive lyrics?",
        "answers": [
            "\"Hey, hey, hey, hey\"",
            "\"Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah\"",
            "\"Doo, doo, doo, doo\"",
            "\"Oh, oh, oh, oh\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"Hey, hey, hey, hey\""
    },
    {
        "index": 355,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Fittingly, United Airlies Flight 888 travels from San Francisco to what city about 12 hours away, where 8 is considered a lucky number?",
        "answers": [
            "Barcelona",
            "New Delhi",
            "Beijing",
            "Dubai"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Beijing"
    },
    {
        "index": 356,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Given that it's 160 feet wide, if something is truly the size of a football field (including its two 10-yard end zones), how many square feet is it?",
        "answers": [
            "19,200 sq. ft.",
            "48,000 sq. ft.",
            "57,600 sq. ft.",
            "89,600 sq. ft."
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 57,600 sq. ft."
    },
    {
        "index": 357,
        "date": "10/12/2018",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " In what part or parts of your body would you find your limbal rings?",
        "answers": [
            "brain",
            "eyes",
            "small intestine",
            "knees"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " eyes"
    },
    {
        "index": 358,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " For a brief time, what candies were also released in a soft, chewable version called Dweebs?",
        "answers": [
            "Nerds",
            "Life Savers",
            "Jolly Ranchers",
            "Smarties"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Nerds"
    },
    {
        "index": 359,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " To combat \"screen addiction,\" in 2018 France passed a law prohibiting students from taking out their what in the classroom?",
        "answers": [
            "retainer",
            "pet snake",
            "smartphone",
            "appendix"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " smartphone"
    },
    {
        "index": 360,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Someone driving in which of these famous places would be most likely to get caught in a \"bison jam\" -- a traffic jam caused by a herd of bison crossing the road?",
        "answers": [
            "French Quarter in New ORleans",
            "Times Square",
            "Yellowstone National Park",
            "Las Vegas Strip"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Yellowstone National Park"
    },
    {
        "index": 361,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Putting \"Bermuda\" in front of all but which of these words creates the name of a familiar term?",
        "answers": [
            "onion",
            "shorts",
            "grass",
            "trapezoid"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " trapezoid"
    },
    {
        "index": 362,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " The only one not to have its own Olympic event, what swimming stroke is often used by lifeguards because it allows them to tow a person with them?",
        "answers": [
            "butterfly",
            "sidestroke",
            "breaststroke",
            "backstroke"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " sidestroke"
    },
    {
        "index": 363,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Considering she played the character Mystique in \"X-Men,\" it's fitting that Rebeca Romijn hosted the GSN game show \"Skin Wars,\" which was what type of competition?",
        "answers": [
            "body piercing",
            "tanning",
            "plastic surgery",
            "body painting"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " body painting"
    },
    {
        "index": 364,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " If you were enjoying a meal of fingerlings with a side of fingerlings, which two things would most likely be on your plate?",
        "answers": [
            "sausage and broccoli",
            "fish and potatoes",
            "chicken and brussels sprouts",
            "pork ribs and squash"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " fish and potatoes"
    },
    {
        "index": 365,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " A remnant of the Spanish Colonial era, Intramuros is a 450-year-old walled city located in the center of what cosmopolitan Asian capital?",
        "answers": [
            "Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia",
            "Bangkok, Thailand",
            "Seoul, South Korea",
            "Manila, Philippines"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Manila, Philippines"
    },
    {
        "index": 366,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Based solely on the face value of the lettered tiles, which of these statements about spelling out numbers with Scrabble tiles is true?",
        "answers": [
            "SEVEN is worth 7 points",
            "EIGHT is worth 8 points",
            "TWELVE is worth 12 points",
            "SIXTEEN is worth 16 points"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " TWELVE is worth 12 points"
    },
    {
        "index": 367,
        "date": "10/5/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Before her short-lived career as a calypso performer, what woman became, at 16, the first African American female to work as a San Francisco cable car conductor?",
        "answers": [
            "Whoopi Goldberg",
            "Maya Angelou",
            "Robin Roberts",
            "Alice Walker"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Maya Angelou"
    },
    {
        "index": 368,
        "date": "9/28/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In early 2018, Donald Trump revealed that his re-election campaign slogan for 2020 would be what?",
        "answers": [
            "Keep America Great!",
            "Keep South America Great!",
            "Keep Miss America Great!",
            "Keep America Ferrera Great!"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Keep America Great!"
    },
    {
        "index": 369,
        "date": "9/28/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " A phrase popularized by a 1653 book on the pastime, what often-relaxing activity has been called \"the contemplative man's recreation\"?",
        "answers": [
            "drag racing",
            "fishing",
            "bungee jumping",
            "MMA fighting"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " fishing"
    },
    {
        "index": 370,
        "date": "9/28/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Fittingly, what classic song by Rodgers and Hammerstein is featured in commercials for the genetic testing company, 23andMe?",
        "answers": [
            "Getting to Know You",
            "Climb Ev'ry Mountain",
            "Shall We Dance?",
            "Oklahoma"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Getting to Know You"
    },
    {
        "index": 371,
        "date": "9/28/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " The main train depot in the cities of Los Angeles, Chicago, Washington, D.C., Denver and Portland, OR is in each case known by what name?",
        "answers": [
            "Independence Station",
            "Centennial Station",
            "Union Station",
            "Liberty Station"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Union Station"
    },
    {
        "index": 372,
        "date": "9/28/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " A common ritual after a meal in Italy, the \"passeggiata\" is a traditional what?",
        "answers": [
            "prayer",
            "nap",
            "stroll",
            "drink"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "stroll"
    },
    {
        "index": 373,
        "date": "9/28/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Of all the numbers from 1 to 100, which requires the most letters to depict in Roman numerals -- a total of 8?",
        "answers": [
            "39",
            "48",
            "88",
            "99"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "88"
    },
    {
        "index": 374,
        "date": "9/28/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " The experimental and controversial medical fad known as parabiosis claims to slow or reverse the aging process through what method?",
        "answers": [
            "all citrus diet",
            "18 hours of sleep per day",
            "exposure to extreme cold",
            "blood transfusions from the young"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "blood transfusions from the young"
    },
    {
        "index": 375,
        "date": "9/28/2018",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " Which of these films' last line of spoken dialogue is \"Heil Hitler\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Schindler's List",
            "Inglorious Basterds",
            "Saving Private Ryan",
            "The Pianist"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Schindler's List"
    },
    {
        "index": 376,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Trained to handle speeds of up to 233 mph, only a handful of people currently hold a FIA Super License, which allows them to drive a what?",
        "answers": [
            "golf cart",
            "John Deere tractor",
            "Little Tykes Cozy Coupe",
            "Formula One race car"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Formula One race car"
    },
    {
        "index": 377,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In the Christmas carol \"We Wish You a Merry Christmas\", the carolers declare that they won't leave until they get some what--and a cup of good cheer?",
        "answers": [
            "figgy pudding",
            "chili cheese fries",
            "low-fat Greek yogurt",
            "grits"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " figgy pudding"
    },
    {
        "index": 378,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Because it contains the traditional 'okina, which of the following do many consider the proper way to spell the name of a certain U.S. state?",
        "answers": [
            "Hawai'i",
            "Penn'sylvania",
            "Illinoi's",
            "F'lorida"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Hawai'i"
    },
    {
        "index": 379,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " What classic Australian sitcom of the 1960s revolved around a young boy, his park ranger father, and a plucky, mischievous marsupial?",
        "answers": [
            "Leave it to Penguin",
            "Welcome Back, Mountain Lion",
            "My Mother the Andean Condor",
            "Skippy the Bush Kangaroo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Skippy the Bush Kangaroo"
    },
    {
        "index": 380,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which two words best complete this statement? A polarized _____ is one where the \"neutral\" _____ is wider than the \"hot\" one.",
        "answers": [
            "fruit/seed",
            "hurricane/eye",
            "plug/prong",
            "planet/ring"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " plug/prong"
    },
    {
        "index": 381,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " What actress in \"The Wolf of Wall Street\" initially lied to her parents about her nude scenes, claiming it was her head attached to someone else's body?",
        "answers": [
            "Emma Stone",
            "Jennifer Lawrence",
            "Amy Adams",
            "Margot Robbie"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Margot Robbie"
    },
    {
        "index": 382,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In the 1963 landmark Supreme Court case Gideon v. Wainwright, the court ruled that states must provide what to a defendant who can't afford to pay for their own?",
        "answers": [
            "an attorney",
            "a personal trainer",
            "an English butler",
            "Super Bowl tickets"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " an attorney"
    },
    {
        "index": 383,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In the days of vaudeville, the patrons who sat in the cheapest seats and ate the cheapest snacks were often referred to as the what?",
        "answers": [
            "caviar crew",
            "filet mignon squad",
            "peanut gallery",
            "foie gras brigade"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " peanut gallery"
    },
    {
        "index": 384,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of the following did NOT make Fortune.com's list of \"The 50 Greatest Business Rivalries of All Time\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Duracell vs. Energizer",
            "Nike vs. Reebok",
            "Hertz vs. Avis",
            "RitzCarlton vs. EconoLodge"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " RitzCarlton vs. EconoLodge"
    },
    {
        "index": 385,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Saying the stories they told were \"painful\" and \"one-sided\", in 2017 Washington D.C.'s National Cathedral removed its stained-glass windows honoring whom?",
        "answers": [
            "Neil Armstrong & Buzz Aldrin",
            "John Lennon & Paul McCartney",
            "Robert E. Lee & Stonewall Jackson",
            "Babe Ruth & Lou Gehrig"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Robert E. Lee & Stonewall Jackson"
    },
    {
        "index": 386,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which specific shade of blue does Merriam-Webster define as \"the blue color of the clear sky\"?",
        "answers": [
            "azure",
            "cobalt blue",
            "navy blue",
            "sapphire"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " azure"
    },
    {
        "index": 387,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Baechu, meaning \"Napa cabbage,\" is a common ingredient in what food, whose varieties include a cubed radish version called Kkakdugi?",
        "answers": [
            "poke",
            "kimchi",
            "baba ghanoush",
            "wonton soup"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " kimchi"
    },
    {
        "index": 388,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " According to the Philadelphia Inquirer, Rocky Balboa's pet what were played by the same animals in both 1976's \"Rocky\" and 2006's \"Rocky Balboa\"?",
        "answers": [
            "rabbits",
            "turtles",
            "goldfish",
            "parakeets"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " turtles"
    },
    {
        "index": 389,
        "date": "9/21/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Which of these Native Americans is actually fictional, created by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow for his epic poem \"Song of Hiawatha\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Tecumseh",
            "Cochise",
            "Minnehaha",
            "Squanto"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Minnehaha"
    },
    {
        "index": 390,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In Greek mythology, which of these was NOT one of the men romantically linked with Helen of Troy?",
        "answers": [
            "Menelaus",
            "Paris",
            "Deiphobus",
            "Leonardo DiCaprio"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Leonardo DiCaprio"
    },
    {
        "index": 391,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In the legendary 1950 Japanese film \"Rashomon,\" differing eyewitness accounts of a murder are presented by all but which of these characters?",
        "answers": [
            "the bandit",
            "the woodcutter",
            "the wife",
            "the Cowardly Lion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the Cowardly Lion"
    },
    {
        "index": 392,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " According to poet Maya Angelou, \"People will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "spot you at the gym",
            "help you move a couch",
            "water your plants for two weeks",
            "feel"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " feel"
    },
    {
        "index": 393,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In the produce section, a \"pluot\" is a cultivated hybrid of which of the following and an apricot?",
        "answers": [
            "plum",
            "placekicker",
            "plucked chicken",
            "plaid sport coat"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " plum"
    },
    {
        "index": 394,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to Wired.com, what common involuntary reaction to stubbing your toe (that can't be shown on TV) actually helps alleviate the pain you feel afterward?",
        "answers": [
            "yawning",
            "smiling",
            "swearing",
            "sneezing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " swearing"
    },
    {
        "index": 395,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Paying homage to the major midwestern city where he grew up and started following his dreams, Kanye West's third-born child with Kim Kardashian is named what?",
        "answers": [
            "Chicago",
            "Miami",
            "Seattle",
            "Tucumcari"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Chicago"
    },
    {
        "index": 396,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Famous for his homespun wit, college coach Abe Lemons once said of what sport, \"All you have to do is just tell them to stay to the left and hurry back\"?",
        "answers": [
            "weightlifting",
            "gymnastics",
            "wrestling",
            "track"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " track"
    },
    {
        "index": 397,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Making sense when you think about it, which type of building's name is derived from the group of Greek goddesses who preside over the arts?",
        "answers": [
            "amphitheater",
            "library",
            "cinema",
            "museum"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " museum"
    },
    {
        "index": 398,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " What type of piercing is known as either a Monroe or a Madonna, depending on whether it's on the left or right side?",
        "answers": [
            "ear",
            "nostril",
            "eyelid",
            "upper lip"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " upper lip"
    },
    {
        "index": 399,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " What country's second-largest city is named for Mount Royal, which sits right smack in the middle of that city?",
        "answers": [
            "Mexico",
            "France",
            "Canada",
            "Switzerland"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Canada"
    },
    {
        "index": 400,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of the following is about 95% water?",
        "answers": [
            "a jellyfish",
            "a jelly doughnut",
            "petroleum jelly",
            "a Jelly Belly"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a jellyfish"
    },
    {
        "index": 401,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " According to Brittanica, in the world of horror fiction, it's generally accepted that the best way to stop a zombie is to destroy its what?",
        "answers": [
            "brain",
            "self-confidence",
            "credit score",
            "rental car"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " brain"
    },
    {
        "index": 402,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of these is an official state holiday observed each June in a particularly historical part of Massachusetts?",
        "answers": [
            "Faith Hill Day",
            "Bunker Hill Day",
            "Benny Hill Day",
            "Jonah Hill Day"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Bunker Hill Day"
    },
    {
        "index": 403,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Fittingly, the French term for love at first sight, \"coup de foudre,\" translates literally to which weather phenomenon?",
        "answers": [
            "bolt of lightning",
            "downpour of rain",
            "flurry of snow",
            "shower of hail"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bolt of lightning"
    },
    {
        "index": 404,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " In the growing alternative health world, what 9-letter \"e\" word is often used to describe the oils extracted from plants like lavender and eucalyptus?",
        "answers": [
            "essential",
            "effervescent",
            "educated",
            "exclusive"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " essential"
    },
    {
        "index": 405,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " The groundbreaking mathematical paper known as the Clayton-McKellar-Winn theorem was co-authored by a former star of what classic TV show?",
        "answers": [
            "Laverne & Shirley",
            "Three's Company",
            "The Wonder Years",
            "Family Ties"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Wonder Years"
    },
    {
        "index": 406,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Deriving its name from an Inuit word, an anorak is what type of apparel?",
        "answers": [
            "boot",
            "hat",
            "jacket",
            "mitten"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " jacket"
    },
    {
        "index": 407,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " As it brings in about half of the company's revenue, McDonald's former CFO once said, \"We are not technically in the food business. We are in the\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "toy business",
            "farming business",
            "recycling business",
            "real estate business"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " real estate business"
    },
    {
        "index": 408,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Which of these is the capital of the African nation of Chad and NOT the name of a character in the movie \"Black Panther\"?",
        "answers": [
            "N'Djamena",
            "T'Challa",
            "N'Jadaka",
            "W'Kabi"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " N'Djamena"
    },
    {
        "index": 409,
        "date": "9/14/2018",
        "prize": "100,000",
        "question": " While all six of the others have them regularly, there has NOT been a volcanic eruption on which continent since Mt. Gambier blew 5,000 years ago?",
        "answers": [
            "Antarctica",
            "Africa",
            "Australia",
            "South America"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Australia"
    },
    {
        "index": 410,
        "date": "6/1/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " A person with \"situs inversus\" might place his hand on the right-hand side of his chest when saying the Pledge of Allegiance, since his what are laterally inverted?",
        "answers": [
            "nostrils",
            "vertebrae",
            "organs",
            "digits"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " organs"
    },
    {
        "index": 411,
        "date": "6/1/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Famous for their platform shoes and choreographed dances, what was the name of the '90s girl group behind hits like \"Wannabe\"?",
        "answers": [
            "The Spice Girls",
            "The Seasonings Sisters",
            "The Savory Singers",
            "The Condiment Clan"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Spice Girls"
    },
    {
        "index": 412,
        "date": "6/1/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Because being away from the job makes it hard to hide embezzlement, the FDIC strongly suggests that who be forced to take two-week vacations?",
        "answers": [
            "dog groomers",
            "bankers",
            "New Yorker cartoonists",
            "monks"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bankers"
    },
    {
        "index": 413,
        "date": "6/1/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " You may smell like a baby koala the next time you catch a cold, because the Australian Koala Foundation says that due to their diet, they smell like what?",
        "answers": [
            "DayQuil",
            "eucalyptus cough drops",
            "vitamin C tablets",
            "Vicks VapoRub"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " eucalyptus cough drops"
    },
    {
        "index": 414,
        "date": "6/1/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " A recent Off-Broadway \"remix\", or hip-hop version, of what Shakespeare play featuring the two-faced Iago was advertised with the slogan \"Moor Money, Moor Problems\"?",
        "answers": [
            "A Midsummer Night's Dream",
            "Romeo & Juliet",
            "Othello",
            "The Tempest"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Othello"
    },
    {
        "index": 415,
        "date": "6/1/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " On what retro sitcom does actress Wendi McLendon-Covey often wear actual 1980s sweaters and pantsuits mailed in by the show creator's mother?",
        "answers": [
            "Fresh Off The Boat",
            "New Girl",
            "The Goldbergs",
            "Brooklyn Nine-Nine"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Goldbergs"
    },
    {
        "index": 416,
        "date": "6/1/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " What do the capitals of Nevada, Missouri, Oklahoma and Utah all have in common?",
        "answers": [
            "they were founded in the 20th century",
            "they have populations under 100,000",
            "they're all located at the same latitude",
            "their names end in \"City\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " their names end in \"City\""
    },
    {
        "index": 417,
        "date": "6/1/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " FatSecret.com says if you're on a low-carb diet, you'll want to avoid which fruit, which packs a whopping 34 grams of carbohydrates in 1 cup of slices?",
        "answers": [
            "pear",
            "banana",
            "apple",
            "pineapple"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " banana"
    },
    {
        "index": 418,
        "date": "6/1/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " When MLB's Red Sox and Cubs won World Series after droughts of 86 and 108 years, what front office executive was credited with breaking two legendary curses?",
        "answers": [
            "Brian Sabean",
            "Sandy Alderson",
            "Billy Beane",
            "Theo Epstein"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Theo Epstein"
    },
    {
        "index": 419,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In a popular idiom, a person behaving like they've won an election before the votes have even been cast is said to be doing what?",
        "answers": [
            "fluffing the pillows",
            "measuring the drapes",
            "beating the rings",
            "defrosting the fridge"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " measuring the drapes"
    },
    {
        "index": 420,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " What storage area in a car's dashboard is named for a once-common article of clothing that has since fallen out of fashion?",
        "answers": [
            "corset tray",
            "top hat hatch",
            "monocle holder",
            "glove compartment"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " glove compartment"
    },
    {
        "index": 421,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Honoring puck-pushing legends like Mae Hall and Lucy Perkins, St. Petersburg, Florida, hosts the Hall of Fame of what senior-friendly sport?",
        "answers": [
            "Greco-Roman wrestling",
            "shuffleboard",
            "ski jumping",
            "bull riding"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " shuffleboard"
    },
    {
        "index": 422,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In 2017, Keanu Reeves reunited with his \"Matrix\" co-star Laurence Fishburne in what sequel to a 2014 surprise hit action thriller?",
        "answers": [
            "Speed 3: Where's the Fire",
            "John Wick: Chapter 2",
            "Bill & Ted's Gnarly Midlife Crisis",
            "A Very Point Break Christmas"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " John Wick: Chapter 2"
    },
    {
        "index": 423,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Thanks to brands like Audi, BASF and Siemens, which of these finished first in a recent survey ranking the world's most reputable labels?",
        "answers": [
            "Made in Finland",
            "Made in Germany",
            "Made in the Netherlands",
            "Made in France"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Made in Germany"
    },
    {
        "index": 424,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " The source of a fierce rivalry between the two states, the state quarters of Ohio and North Carolina both feature what?",
        "answers": [
            "an airplane",
            "a peach pie",
            "a river",
            "Ronald Reagan"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " an airplane"
    },
    {
        "index": 425,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " What popular band from the \"emo\" genre, whose unusual name was inspired by another band's lyric, is known for hits like \"I Write Sins Not Tragedies\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Delirium! at the Karaoke Bar",
            "Anxiety! at the Roller Skating Rink",
            "Panic! at the Disco",
            "Hysteria! at the Laser Tag Arena"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Panic! at the Disco"
    },
    {
        "index": 426,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " \"Hypophysis\" is the technical term for what internal organ that's part of the body's endocrine system?",
        "answers": [
            "gall bladder",
            "spleen",
            "duodenum",
            "pituitary gland"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " pituitary gland"
    },
    {
        "index": 427,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Going on to run for president in 2004, in 1992 what Illinois attorney became the first African-American woman to be elected to the U.S. Senate?",
        "answers": [
            "Shirley Chisholm",
            "Jeannette Rankin",
            "Carol Moseley Braun",
            "Kamala Harris"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Carol Moseley Braun"
    },
    {
        "index": 428,
        "date": "5/25/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Which of the following was the first man-made structure to stand over 1,000 feet tall?",
        "answers": [
            "Eiffel Tower",
            "Empire State Building",
            "Chrysler Building",
            "Golden Gate Bridge"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Chrysler Building"
    },
    {
        "index": 429,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "1,000",
        "question": " What grocery store brand donates all profits after taxes to various charities?",
        "answers": [
            "Stouffer's",
            "Newman's Own",
            "Pepperidge Farm",
            "Sargento"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Newman's Own"
    },
    {
        "index": 430,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Symbolizing the hope for good fortune on voyages, a ship's christening ceremony traditionally involves a bottle of what being smashed over the hull?",
        "answers": [
            "suntan lotion",
            "champagne",
            "ketchup",
            "body glitter"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " champagne"
    },
    {
        "index": 431,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Hong Kong's leading stock market index is known as the \"Hang...\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "Tough",
            "Over",
            "Seng",
            "A right at the corner"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Seng"
    },
    {
        "index": 432,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Known to some as \"The King of Tears,\" Nashville legend Bobby Braddock wrote or co-wrote all but which of the following songs?",
        "answers": [
            "Hard Times",
            "D-I-V-O-R-C-E",
            "He Stopped Loving Her Today",
            "What Does the Fox Say?"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " What Does the Fox Say?"
    },
    {
        "index": 433,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Which of these is the artistic-sounding name of a famously scenic desert located in Arizona?",
        "answers": [
            "Ceramic Desert",
            "Painted Desert",
            "Chiseled Desert",
            "Woven Desert"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Painted Desert"
    },
    {
        "index": 434,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " \"Animal Farm,\" \"Infinite Jest\" and \"The Hunger Games\" all appear on the Wikipedia page entitled \"List of\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "Dystopian Literature",
            "Novels with Talking Animals",
            "Books Longer Than 1,000 Pages",
            "Stories About Archery"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Dystopian Literature"
    },
    {
        "index": 435,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " It's thought that Kevin Spacey's character on \"House of Cards\" is named after what AL politician who declined the chance to run as Woodrow Wilson's vice president?",
        "answers": [
            "Davison Palmer",
            "Oscar Underwood",
            "Mortimer Kirkman",
            "James Bartlet"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Oscar Underwood"
    },
    {
        "index": 436,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " While most people in his line of work use one, the legendary conductor Leopold Stokowski preferred to do his job without what?",
        "answers": [
            "a baton",
            "a starter pistol",
            "a ventriloquist dummy",
            "a parachute"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a baton"
    },
    {
        "index": 437,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Back when cannons were on wheels on warships, an unsecured one could roll around and injure sailors, inspiring what term for a dangerously uncontrollable thing?",
        "answers": [
            "loose cannon",
            "wacky cannon",
            "confetti cannon",
            "Nick Cannon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " loose cannon"
    },
    {
        "index": 438,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " When Denny's closed for Christmas in 1998, ending its 24-hour service for the first time ever, many managers discovered they needed to buy what?",
        "answers": [
            "door locks",
            "cash registers",
            "dumpsters",
            "salt shakers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " door locks"
    },
    {
        "index": 439,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " While the overall leader of the Tour de France wears a yellow jersey, the winner of the mountain stages wears the \"maillot a pois rouges,\" a white jersey with what?",
        "answers": [
            "green diamonds",
            "red dots",
            "blue flowers",
            "black stripes"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " red dots"
    },
    {
        "index": 440,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Based on a movie, what Broadway musical's numbers include \"Ohmigod You Guys,\" \"Bend and Snap\" and \"The Harvard Variations\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Hairspray",
            "Sister Act",
            "Newsies",
            "Legally Blonde"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Legally Blonde"
    },
    {
        "index": 441,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " The Park City, UT-based company Skullcandy specializes in what items usually worn on or near the skull?",
        "answers": [
            "earrings",
            "sunglasses",
            "hair clips",
            "headphones"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " headphones"
    },
    {
        "index": 442,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Popular in Britain, what classic artery-clogging dish consists of sausages in Yorkshire pudding batter, usually served with gravy?",
        "answers": [
            "frog on the log",
            "toad in the hole",
            "newt in the boat",
            "lizard on the grass"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " toad in the hole"
    },
    {
        "index": 443,
        "date": "5/18/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " In 2016 the boundaries of the South China Sea were clarified after a prolonged legal battle between China and what country?",
        "answers": [
            "Thailand",
            "the Philippines",
            "Sri Lanka",
            "South Korea"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the Philippines"
    },
    {
        "index": 444,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Mathematician Blaise Pascal is widely credited with creating an early version of what casino game while he was attempting to design a perpetual motion machine?",
        "answers": [
            "craps",
            "roulette",
            "baccarat",
            "keno"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " roulette"
    },
    {
        "index": 445,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " What artist titled his first four solo albums, in order",
        "answers": [
            "Paul McCartney",
            "Kanye West",
            "Ed Sheeran",
            "Peter Gabriel"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Peter Gabriel"
    },
    {
        "index": 446,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In classic TV ads for Head & Shoulders, a character responds with \"Bingo!\" when a friend says, \"But you don't have\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "migraines",
            "cerebral gigantism",
            "dandruff",
            "weakness in your trapezius"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dandruff"
    },
    {
        "index": 447,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Ironically, in 2016 which of these people was pulled over for speeding while on his way to Texas Motor Speedway?",
        "answers": [
            "Floyd Mayweather",
            "Kobe Bryant",
            "Dale Earnhardt, Jr.",
            "Novak Djokovic"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Dale Earnhardt, Jr."
    },
    {
        "index": 448,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " According to Otis - the world's largest manufacturer of people-moving products - for safety reasons, which of these should people NOT do on an escalator?",
        "answers": [
            "blink",
            "walk",
            "hold the handrails",
            "breathe"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " walk"
    },
    {
        "index": 449,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " What steamy sign of affection is popularly thought to have been brought back to the English-speaking world by soldiers returning from Europe after WWI?",
        "answers": [
            "Pakistani hug",
            "French kiss",
            "Nigerian cuddle",
            "Mexican back rub"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " French kiss"
    },
    {
        "index": 450,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " According to the Bureau of Labor Statistics, only 2.5% of Americans are doing it at 6 PM, but 95.1% are doing it at 3 AM. What is it?",
        "answers": [
            "betting on dog races",
            "eating Double Stuf Oreos",
            "sleeping",
            "trying on swimsuits"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " sleeping"
    },
    {
        "index": 451,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Before doing actual hands-on work with Habitat for Humanity, what did President Jimmy Carter have built for his daughter Amy on the White House grounds?",
        "answers": [
            "tree house",
            "outhouse",
            "a NASCAR racetrack",
            "igloo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " tree house"
    },
    {
        "index": 452,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of these is a word meaning \"foolish things\" and NOT a sign over a theater, a French nobleman or the frontman of the '90s hip-hop group the Funky Bunch?",
        "answers": [
            "marquis",
            "marquee",
            "Marky Mark",
            "malarky"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " malarky"
    },
    {
        "index": 453,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " As you might guess from their names, Santa Fe Grande and Devil's Tongue are two common varieties of what?",
        "answers": [
            "cherry tomatoes",
            "hot peppers",
            "baby carrots",
            "purple kale"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " hot peppers"
    },
    {
        "index": 454,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which director has helmed two blockbuster films whose titles can be defined as \"the incarnation of a Hindu deity\" and \"having great magnitude, force, or power\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Steven Spielberg",
            "George Lucas",
            "James Cameron",
            "Tim Burton"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " James Cameron"
    },
    {
        "index": 455,
        "date": "5/11/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " As Rihanna could probably tell you, Bridgetown is the capital of what Caribbean nation?",
        "answers": [
            "The Bahamas",
            "Barbados",
            "Haiti",
            "Dominican Republic"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Barbados"
    },
    {
        "index": 456,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " On December 26th, 2016, a location of what fast food chain made news by letting customers trade in an unwanted Christmas gift for a free Whopper?",
        "answers": [
            "Burger King",
            "Taco Bell",
            "Subway",
            "McDonald's"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Burger King"
    },
    {
        "index": 457,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In 2017, wrestling fans mourned the retirement of Mark Calaway, who'd spent 30 years in the ring grappling under what ominous occupational nickname?",
        "answers": [
            "The Florist",
            "The Beautician",
            "The Assistant Manager",
            "The Undertaker"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Undertaker"
    },
    {
        "index": 458,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In 1985, rocker Robert Palmer warned us that we might as well face it, and he was right - researchers now claim that humans can literally be what?",
        "answers": [
            "hungry like the wolf",
            "addicted to love",
            "footloose",
            "too sexy for their shirt"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " addicted to love"
    },
    {
        "index": 459,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " When he created the ASPCA in 1866, New York City's Henry Bergh was most concerned with helping what animals, which he saw mistreated on a daily basis?",
        "answers": [
            "geese",
            "rabbits",
            "horses",
            "kangaroos"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " horses"
    },
    {
        "index": 460,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Of the following famous Millers, who's the author of a number of well-known books that were at one time banned in the U.S. for explicit sexual content?",
        "answers": [
            "Glenn Miller",
            "Bode Miller",
            "Henry Miller",
            "Sienna Miller"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Henry Miller"
    },
    {
        "index": 461,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " One cup of water, 2 tablespoons of liquid detergent, 1 tablespoon of glycerin, and 1/2 teaspoon of sugar is RealSimple.com's recipe for what?",
        "answers": [
            "paste",
            "a hiccups remedy",
            "slime",
            "bubbles"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bubbles"
    },
    {
        "index": 462,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these words is NOT used in the slogan of \"Survivor\"?",
        "answers": [
            "outwit",
            "outplay",
            "outlast",
            "outhouse"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " outhouse"
    },
    {
        "index": 463,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Sold under the brand name Kybella, deoxycholic acid is a prescription drug designed to help users eliminate what \"extra\" body part?",
        "answers": [
            "double chin",
            "third kidney",
            "eleventh finger",
            "thirty-fourth vertebra"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " double chin"
    },
    {
        "index": 464,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " A recent comprehensive study on the health consequences of caffeine determined that it's okay to drink up to how much coffee per day?",
        "answers": [
            "4 cups",
            "4 gallons",
            "4 urns",
            "4 barrels"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 4 cups"
    },
    {
        "index": 465,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Notorious for their treacherous methods of holding onto power, a famous motto of the Borgia family was \"Aut Caesar, aut nihil,\" which means what in English?",
        "answers": [
            "Bring me a Caesar salad, now!",
            "Either Caesar or nothing",
            "That Sid Caesar is hilarious",
            "Does Little Caesars deliver in Rome?"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Either Caesar or nothing"
    },
    {
        "index": 466,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Often seen on certain camping supplies, a \"lumen\" is a measure of what?",
        "answers": [
            "loudness",
            "sourness",
            "hairiness",
            "brightness"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " brightness"
    },
    {
        "index": 467,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " You'll have to excuse Spanish-speaking tourists in Oahu if they don't order which common Hawaiian dish, since it's name literally translates to \"crazy booger\"?",
        "answers": [
            "lomi lomi",
            "chichi dango",
            "loco moco",
            "pipikalua"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " loco moco"
    },
    {
        "index": 468,
        "date": "5/4/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Following in Dad's footsteps, which of these world leaders had a father who previously led their country?",
        "answers": [
            "Benjamin Netanyahu",
            "Angela Merkel",
            "Justin Trudeau",
            "Vladimir Putin"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Justin Trudeau"
    },
    {
        "index": 469,
        "date": "4/27/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Though he fell just short, Joe DiMaggio said what company approached him about a possible bonus if his 56-game hitting streak went one more game?",
        "answers": [
            "Chrysler",
            "Wrigley's",
            "Gillette",
            "Heinz"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Heinz"
    },
    {
        "index": 470,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Until it was revised in 2017, Utah law required all businesses to use partitions called \"Zion curtains\" to prevent customers from seeing what being prepared?",
        "answers": [
            "tacos",
            "cocktails",
            "donuts",
            "pizza"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cocktails"
    },
    {
        "index": 471,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In 1939, Harvard student Lothrop Withington, Jr. started a national college craze when he swallowed a what to win a bet?",
        "answers": [
            "goldfish",
            "flagpole",
            "phone booth",
            "Hula Hoop"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " goldfish"
    },
    {
        "index": 472,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " On an alrline flight, which of the following is specifically designed to last a minimum of 10 minutes?",
        "answers": [
            "the kicking of your seat by the kid behind you",
            "the air flow through your oxygen mask",
            "the flight attendants' negative attitude",
            "your struggle to open a bag of peanuts"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the air flow through your oxygen mask"
    },
    {
        "index": 473,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Six-time NBA champion Michael Jordan once astutely noted that \"There is no 'I' in team, but there is in\" what word?",
        "answers": [
            "win",
            "airball",
            "technical foul",
            "athletic supporter"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " win"
    },
    {
        "index": 474,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Which cartoon dad is NOT known for generally wearing a white shirt?",
        "answers": [
            "Homer Simpson",
            "George Jetson",
            "Peter Griffin",
            "Fred Flintstone"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Fred Flintstone"
    },
    {
        "index": 475,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " What international, Muslim food law-compliant franchise began in 1990 as a cart run by three friends at the corner of 53rd and 6th in NYC?",
        "answers": [
            "The Kapu Dudes",
            "The Halal Guys",
            "The Namaste Boys",
            "The Kosher Kids"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Halal Guys"
    },
    {
        "index": 476,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " What famous American anthropologist is said to have once quipped, \"Always remember that you are absolutely unique. Just like everyone else\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Margaret Mitchell",
            "Margaret Mead",
            "Margaret Court",
            "Margaret Truman"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Margaret Mead"
    },
    {
        "index": 477,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Which \"Star Wars\" character's first name contains the name of a type of decorative sash worn with a Japanese kimono?",
        "answers": [
            "Anakin Skywalker",
            "Boba Fett",
            "Darth Vader",
            "Obi-Wan Kenobi"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Obi-Wan Kenobi"
    },
    {
        "index": 478,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " According to the U.S. Census Population Clock, of every 100 people in the world, about how many are residents of China, the world's most populous nation?",
        "answers": [
            "5",
            "10",
            "20",
            "25"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 20"
    },
    {
        "index": 479,
        "date": "4/20/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Practically neighbors, the Circle of Willis and the Canal of Schlemm are both located where?",
        "answers": [
            "in the night sky",
            "in the Grand Canyon",
            "in a carburetor",
            "in the human head"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " in the human head"
    },
    {
        "index": 480,
        "date": "4/13/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " After studying cosmetology, who worked as a beautician until his song \"Maybelline\" became his first hit rock-and-roll single?",
        "answers": [
            "Chuck Berry",
            "Muddy Waters",
            "Bo Diddley",
            "Little Richard"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Chuck Berry"
    },
    {
        "index": 481,
        "date": "3/16/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Fittingly, what Roman deity is often regarded as the god of beginnings?",
        "answers": [
            "Februus",
            "Maia",
            "Mars",
            "Janus"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Janus"
    },
    {
        "index": 482,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " If you want to preserve fresh herbs, The Pioneer Woman cooking blog recommends freezing them in ice cube trays filled with what common type of oil?",
        "answers": [
            "motor oil",
            "olive oil",
            "midnight oil",
            "humpback whale oil"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " olive oil"
    },
    {
        "index": 483,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In 2016, a contestant covered with 43 insect bites won the \"tastiest girl\" competition at what bizarre annual event held in the Ural Mountains?",
        "answers": [
            "Russian Mosquito Festival",
            "Dutch Butterfly Convention",
            "Chilean Ladybug Fair",
            "Filipino Cricket Jubilee"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Russian Mosquito Festival"
    },
    {
        "index": 484,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Showing propaganda videos as in-flight entertainment, what country's state-owned airline Air Koryo was named by Skytrax as the world's worst?",
        "answers": [
            "Switzerland",
            "North Korea",
            "Norway",
            "Australia"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " North Korea"
    },
    {
        "index": 485,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Ironically, which of the following English words can be found within the Italian word for \"goodbye\"?",
        "answers": [
            "greet",
            "enter",
            "arrive",
            "meet"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " arrive"
    },
    {
        "index": 486,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " The \"MTrain Tour,\" \"That Bass Tour\" and \"The Untouchable Tour\" were all headlined by what Grammy-winning artist known for her retro singing style?",
        "answers": [
            "Meghan Trainor",
            "Selena Gomez",
            "Rihanna",
            "Carrie Underwood"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Meghan Trainor"
    },
    {
        "index": 487,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " The fear of palindromes is appropriately known as what \"phobia\"?",
        "answers": [
            "mysophobia",
            "astraphobia",
            "aibohphobia",
            "cynophobia"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " aibohphobia"
    },
    {
        "index": 488,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " While the .dog domain recently became available for canine lovers to use, the .cat domain has already been taken by residents of a region in which country?",
        "answers": [
            "France",
            "Germany",
            "England",
            "Spain"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Spain"
    },
    {
        "index": 489,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " A person who feels revitalized after surviving a hardship is often said to have \"a\" what \"on life\"?",
        "answers": [
            "new lease",
            "upgraded membership",
            "increased credit limit",
            "revised prenup"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " new lease"
    },
    {
        "index": 490,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " The namesake of a popular variety of tea, who served as UK prime minister from 1830 to 1834?",
        "answers": [
            "Earl Gray",
            "Baron von Herbal Chai",
            "Prince Oolong",
            "The Duke of Snapple"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Earl Gray"
    },
    {
        "index": 491,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " What classification of shorebirds that includes herons, egrets and storks shares its name with a type of fishing equipment?",
        "answers": [
            "hooks",
            "reels",
            "nets",
            "waders"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " waders"
    },
    {
        "index": 492,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " In 1959, 21-year-old Joan Knoerzer and 21-year-old Jayne Knoerzer began appearing in ads for which brand of gum?",
        "answers": [
            "Juicy Fruit",
            "Big Red",
            "Orbit",
            "Doublemint"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Doublemint"
    },
    {
        "index": 493,
        "date": "3/9/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " According to Mirriam-Webster.com, what synonym for friend comes from the Latin for \"bread,\" because it once referred to someone with whom you shared a meal?",
        "answers": [
            "chum",
            "cohort",
            "companion",
            "comrade"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " companion"
    },
    {
        "index": 494,
        "date": "2/23/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Used in the NFL, a Wilson football is composed of all but which of the following?",
        "answers": [
            "four equally-sized leather panels",
            "an air bladder",
            "a 46-to-50-inch-long lace",
            "a human foot"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a human foot"
    },
    {
        "index": 495,
        "date": "2/23/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Making it easy for any officer to release the suspect if necessary, most police handcuffs in the U.S. use identical what?",
        "answers": [
            "keys",
            "padlock combinations",
            "passwords",
            "eyeball scanners"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " keys"
    },
    {
        "index": 496,
        "date": "2/23/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " According to Parenting.com, what's the term for a smaller version of a baby shower that these days is sometimes thrown for the parents of a 2nd-born (or later) child?",
        "answers": [
            "baby sprinkle",
            "baby hailstorm",
            "baby flash flood",
            "baby sea squall"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " baby sprinkle"
    },
    {
        "index": 497,
        "date": "2/23/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Tom Cruise recently announced that \"Maverick\" will be the subtitle of the long-awaited sequel to which of his iconic '80s hits?",
        "answers": [
            "Risky Business",
            "Cocktail",
            "Rain Man",
            "Top Gun"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Top Gun"
    },
    {
        "index": 498,
        "date": "2/23/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which of these is the birth name of the participant in the famous Gunfight at the OK Corral who was a graduate of a dental college in Pennsylvania?",
        "answers": [
            "Wyatt Earp",
            "Tom McLaury",
            "Ike Clanton",
            "John Holliday"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " John Holliday"
    },
    {
        "index": 499,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " To prove to the public that the structure was safe, in 1884 P.T. Barnum led what across the newly constructed Brooklyn Bridge?",
        "answers": [
            "19 clowns",
            "20 sea lions",
            "21 elephants",
            "22 bearded ladies"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 21 elephants"
    },
    {
        "index": 500,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " According to NextDoor.com, in the U.S. in 2016, Rocky was fittingly the most common name given to what breed of dog?",
        "answers": [
            "beagle",
            "boxer",
            "chihuahua",
            "German shepherd"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " boxer"
    },
    {
        "index": 501,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Credit expert John Ulzheimer says having credit cards that you're not using boosts your credit score because it shows what?",
        "answers": [
            "you misplace things",
            "you're wasteful",
            "you've never mastered the \"swipe\" motion",
            "you can exercise self-control"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " you can exercise self-control"
    },
    {
        "index": 502,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " With many toasters, you can increase the heating time on one side of a slot while decreasing it on the other side if you press the button labeled what?",
        "answers": [
            "bagel",
            "omelette",
            "bran muffin",
            "oatmeal"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bagel"
    },
    {
        "index": 503,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Fittingly, the media company POW! Entertainment was co-founded by what now-94-year-old legend?",
        "answers": [
            "Spike Lee",
            "Harper Lee",
            "Stan Lee",
            "Robert E. Lee"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Stan Lee"
    },
    {
        "index": 504,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " What is missing from this sequence of U.S. postal abbreviations, alphabetized by the names of their states",
        "answers": [
            "MO",
            "MS",
            "MT",
            "MA"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " MA"
    },
    {
        "index": 505,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " According to EmilyPost.com, in which of the following situations is it acceptable for a man to leave his baseball cap on?",
        "answers": [
            "when he's on an elevator",
            "when he's at the table eating dinner",
            "when the National Anthem is played",
            "when he's in someone's home"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " when he's on an elevator"
    },
    {
        "index": 506,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " With one type dating back to antiquity and the other only a few hundred years old, the two major classifications of beer are ale and what?",
        "answers": [
            "stout",
            "malt",
            "pilsner",
            "lager"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " lager"
    },
    {
        "index": 507,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " On his TV specials, magician David Copperfield has performed all but which of these \"feats\"?",
        "answers": [
            "making the Statue of Liberty disappear",
            "walking through the Great Wall of China",
            "escaping from Alcatraz",
            "teleporting into Fort Knox"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " teleporting into Fort Knox"
    },
    {
        "index": 508,
        "date": "2/16/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " A business establishment known in Australia as an \"opportunity shop\" is called what in the United States?",
        "answers": [
            "a convenience store",
            "a pawn shop",
            "a singles bar",
            "a thrift shop"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a thrift shop"
    },
    {
        "index": 509,
        "date": "2/9/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these is NOT one of the three branches of the U.S. federal government?",
        "answers": [
            "executive",
            "legislative",
            "judicial",
            "olive"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " olive"
    },
    {
        "index": 510,
        "date": "2/9/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " The number of protons in the nucleus of an atom of a chemical element is equal to its what?",
        "answers": [
            "phone number",
            "lucky number",
            "atomic number",
            "Social Security number"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " atomic number"
    },
    {
        "index": 511,
        "date": "2/9/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " What classic fortune-telling toy was originally developed as a promotional product for the Brunswick Billiards company?",
        "answers": [
            "Magic 8-Ball",
            "Vanishing Cue Stick",
            "Krazy Korner Pocket",
            "Baby's First Triangle Rack"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Magic 8-Ball"
    },
    {
        "index": 512,
        "date": "2/9/2018",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " Argentina is greater in area than Belgium. Belgium has more people than Canada. Canada has more islands than Denmark. How many of those statements are true?",
        "answers": [
            "none of the above",
            "one of the above",
            "two of the above",
            "all of the above"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " two of the above"
    },
    {
        "index": 513,
        "date": "2/2/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " While it's impossible for Nero to have fiddled while Rome burned, as the fiddle was invented much later, legend has it that he did play a what?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "kazoo",
            "lyre",
            "double neck electric guitar",
            "Yamaha keyboard"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " lyre"
    },
    {
        "index": 514,
        "date": "2/2/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " The title of a song in the classic 1954 film \"A Star is Born,\" the phrase \"Born in a Trunk\" means that your parents were what?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "elephants",
            "squirrels",
            "human traffickers",
            "actors"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " actors"
    },
    {
        "index": 515,
        "date": "2/2/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In Las Vegas in 1957, while wearing a bikini resembling a mushroom cloud, Lee Merlin was crowned what?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Miss Roulette Wheel",
            "Miss Slot Machine",
            "Miss Atomic Bomb",
            "Miss Neon Lights"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Miss Atomic Bomb"
    },
    {
        "index": 516,
        "date": "2/2/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " In 1974, while partying to celebrate discovering a 3-million-year old fossil, a group of scientists settled on naming her \"Lucy\" after one of what band's songs?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Led Zeppelin",
            "The Doors",
            "The Beatles",
            "Crosby, Stills & Nash"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Beatles"
    },
    {
        "index": 517,
        "date": "2/2/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " NJ woman Alexa Seary says she's constantly being told by co-workers to \"do this\" and \"do that,\" thanks to her name sounding like two popular what?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "children's games",
            "cartoon characters",
            "virtual assistants",
            "fast food chains"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " virtual assistants"
    },
    {
        "index": 518,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " A popular 1970s film opens with one elderly character saying \"I'm Statler\" before another says \"I'm Waldorf. We're here to heckle\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "Jaws",
            "Grease",
            "The Muppet Movie",
            "Saturday Night Fever"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Muppet Movie"
    },
    {
        "index": 519,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Not just a kitchen appliance, which of these is also a term defined as \"a person who introduces the speakers at a formal occasion\"?",
        "answers": [
            "salad spinner",
            "toastmaster",
            "miracle blender",
            "FryDaddy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " toastmaster"
    },
    {
        "index": 520,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " As its germ-fighting alcohol means there's little risk of infection, what did the NY Times call \"an effective tool\" to keep surgeons from cutting the wrong body part?",
        "answers": [
            "a Sharpie marker",
            "a rubber band",
            "a Post-it note",
            "a flashing neon sign"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a Sharpie marker"
    },
    {
        "index": 521,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " When asylum-seeking Edward Snowden was stuck in the Moscow airport in 2013, his attorney brought him what fitting Russian novel to help pass the time?",
        "answers": [
            "Crime and Punishment",
            "Sense and Sensibility",
            "Beezus and Ramona",
            "Marley & Me"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Crime and Punishment"
    },
    {
        "index": 522,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " According to The Smithsonian, what deep-fried sweet was first brought to Manhattan by the Dutch, who called them olykoeks - literally \"oily cakes\"?",
        "answers": [
            "doughnuts",
            "crepes",
            "Whoopie pies",
            "brownies"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " doughnuts"
    },
    {
        "index": 523,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which of these characters is the only one who typically wears pants?",
        "answers": [
            "Bugs Bunny",
            "Donald Duck",
            "Winnie the Pooh",
            "Mickey Mouse"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "index": 524,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Spanning fifty miles across the Continental Divide, what Montana park features the incredibly scenic Going-to-the-Sun Road?",
        "answers": [
            "Arches National Park",
            "Glacier National Park",
            "Zion National Park",
            "Badlands National Park"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Glacier National Park"
    },
    {
        "index": 525,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " What critically acclaimed R&B artist earned kudos for her acting skills in the critically acclaimed 2016 movies \"Moonlight\" and \"Hidden Figures\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Solange",
            "Jennifer Hudson",
            "Janelle Monae",
            "Erykah Badu"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Janelle Monae"
    },
    {
        "index": 526,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " There's no love for southpaws in what sport, which in the 1970s began banning athletes from competing left-handed for safety reasons?",
        "answers": [
            "javelin throw",
            "ice hockey",
            "polo",
            "racquetball"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " polo"
    },
    {
        "index": 527,
        "date": "1/26/2018",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " If the Scottish duo The Proclaimers had used the metric system instead, they would have sung what in their song \"I'm Gonna be (500 Miles)\"?",
        "answers": [
            "\"I would walk 563.3 km\"",
            "\"I would walk 643.7 km\"",
            "\"I would walk 724.2 km\"",
            "\"I would walk 804.7 km\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"I would walk 804.7 km\""
    },
    {
        "index": 528,
        "date": "1/19/2018",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Celebrating its 50th anniversary in 2017, George Balanchine's ballet triptych \"Jewels\" includes acts with all but which of these names?",
        "answers": [
            "emeralds",
            "rubies",
            "diamonds",
            "tacos"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " tacos"
    },
    {
        "index": 529,
        "date": "1/19/2018",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " A Google Survey conducted by Mic.com found most 18-to-34-year-olds don't meet their significant other via a dating app, but instead meet them through what?",
        "answers": [
            "an arranged marriage",
            "mutual friends",
            "their prison work release program",
            "\"The Bachelor\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " mutual friends"
    },
    {
        "index": 530,
        "date": "1/19/2018",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " FDR advisor Harry Hopkins is considered the chief architect of the landmark federal economic reforms commonly known as what?",
        "answers": [
            "The Big Deal",
            "The New Deal",
            "The Real Deal",
            "The Combo Meal Deal"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The New Deal"
    },
    {
        "index": 531,
        "date": "1/19/2018",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " In 2005, Nepalese couple Moni Mulepati and Pem Dorjee Sherpa became the first people ever to get married where?",
        "answers": [
            "in outer space",
            "underwater",
            "on top of Mount Everest",
            "on television"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " on top of Mount Everest"
    },
    {
        "index": 532,
        "date": "1/19/2018",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Coincidentally, what star who's battled LeBron James in the NBA Finals 3 years in a row was born in the very same Akron, OH, hospital, 3 years after LeBron was?",
        "answers": [
            "Kawhi Leonard",
            "Russell Westbrook",
            "Stephen Curry",
            "James Harden"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Stephen Curry"
    },
    {
        "index": 533,
        "date": "1/19/2018",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Of the 12 stars on tbeir flag, who says the number \"has nothing to do with\" the number of members, \"though the circle is a symbol of unity\"?",
        "answers": [
            "NATO",
            "United Nations",
            "United Arab Emirates",
            "European Union"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " European Union"
    },
    {
        "index": 534,
        "date": "12/22/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Predating Lara Croft by 3,000 years, National Geographic noted that what crime is \"as old as the PHaraohs\" and has recently worsened in Egypt and Syria?",
        "answers": [
            "tomb raiding",
            "telemarketing fraud",
            "car theft",
            "computer hacking"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "tomb raiding"
    },
    {
        "index": 535,
        "date": "12/22/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Horses have a system of ligaments, tendons and muscles known as a \"stay apparatus,\" which allows them to do what?",
        "answers": [
            "sleep while standing",
            "eat while running",
            "whinny while rolling",
            "kick while jumping"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "sleep while standing"
    },
    {
        "index": 536,
        "date": "12/22/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Ironically not true about the word itself, what adjective describes a word that is spelled the way it sounds?",
        "answers": [
            "funetic",
            "phonetic",
            "fahnetic",
            "phanetique"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "phonetic"
    },
    {
        "index": 537,
        "date": "12/22/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " What novel has been called a more realistic version of \"The Coral Island,\" a book where boys get stranded on an island, but everything works out in the end?",
        "answers": [
            "Last of the Mohicans",
            "Lord of the Flies",
            "Call of the Wild",
            "Oliver Twist"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Lord of the Flies"
    },
    {
        "index": 538,
        "date": "12/15/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " With some even banning a specific sunscreen brand, SportFishingMag.com says fishermen have long believed it's bad luck to have what fruit on board?",
        "answers": [
            "grapes",
            "apples",
            "bananas",
            "cherries"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bananas"
    },
    {
        "index": 539,
        "date": "12/15/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Blamed on its high cost of living, what state has, by far, the largest percentage of adults still living with their parents?",
        "answers": [
            "Montana",
            "New Jersey",
            "Nebraska",
            "Tennessee"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "New Jersey"
    },
    {
        "index": 540,
        "date": "12/15/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " A Jewish practice that involves people gathering to sit on low stools or boxes, \"sitting shiva,\" by definition, occurs when?",
        "answers": [
            "before a birth",
            "before a bar mitzvah",
            "after a death",
            "during Passover"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "after a death"
    },
    {
        "index": 541,
        "date": "12/15/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Though it began in the mid-19th century partly as a telegraph delivery company, today American District Telegraph is the #1 company by revenue in which business?",
        "answers": [
            "credit card processing",
            "voting machines",
            "security monitoring",
            "electronic billboards"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "security monitoring"
    },
    {
        "index": 542,
        "date": "12/1/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Ever since King Charles I barged in there one day in 1642, it's been a tradition that the reigning UK monarch is not allowed to enter which location?",
        "answers": [
            "the \"Today\" show's studio",
            "the House of Commons",
            "a Medieval Times restaurant",
            "a WNBA locker room"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the House of Commons"
    },
    {
        "index": 543,
        "date": "12/1/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to the New York Times, which of these conditions tends to be most severe when one is traveling east?",
        "answers": [
            "ingrown toenails",
            "hiccups",
            "jet lag",
            "homesickness"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " jet lag"
    },
    {
        "index": 544,
        "date": "12/1/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " After a bloody battle in the film \"Gladiator,\" Russell Crowe's Maximus looks up at the spectators and asks which question?",
        "answers": [
            "\"Anyone know who won the Mets game\"?",
            "\"Are you not entertained?\"",
            "\"Got milk?\"",
            "\"Is this thing on?\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"Are you not entertained?\""
    },
    {
        "index": 545,
        "date": "12/1/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Including 1976's \"A Pink Crustacean Tour\" and 2003's \"Tiki Time Tour,\" which performer has toured every year for the past 40 years?",
        "answers": [
            "Jimmy Buffett",
            "Barbra Streisand",
            "Kenny Rogers",
            "Tina Turner"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Jimmy Buffett"
    },
    {
        "index": 546,
        "date": "12/1/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Fittingly, Nintendo honors its legendary mustachioed plumber on what date each year?",
        "answers": [
            "Mar10",
            "Apr30",
            "Sep20",
            "Dec31"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Mar10"
    },
    {
        "index": 547,
        "date": "12/1/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " According to NASA, to break free of Earth's gravity, a rocket must reach an escape velocity of 11.2 km per second -- which is about what in miles per hour?",
        "answers": [
            "15,000 mph",
            "20,000 mph",
            "25,000 mph",
            "30,000 mph"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 25,000 mph"
    },
    {
        "index": 548,
        "date": "12/1/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " What key behind-the-scenes role in U.S. history was played by Stanley A. Dunham?",
        "answers": [
            "rescued William H. Taft from his bathtub",
            "gave Abraham Lincoln his theater tickets",
            "gave birth to Barack Obama",
            "made George Washington's wooden teeth"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "gave birth to Barack Obama"
    },
    {
        "index": 549,
        "date": "11/24/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " While the majority of America's gold reserve is stored at Ft. Knox, some of it is also kept in all but which of the following locations?",
        "answers": [
            "New York Federal Reserve",
            "U.S. Mint in Denver",
            "West Point",
            "Oprah's couch cushions"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Oprah's couch cushions"
    },
    {
        "index": 550,
        "date": "11/24/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to a recent study, people who own which of these pets walk 2,760 more steps per day than those who don't?",
        "answers": [
            "hamster",
            "dog",
            "parrot",
            "snake"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dog"
    },
    {
        "index": 551,
        "date": "11/24/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Registered by a Washington state rope company in 1884, the oldest active trademark in the U.S. features what Biblical strongman defeating a lion?",
        "answers": [
            "Atlas",
            "Hercules",
            "Samson",
            "Thor"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Samson"
    },
    {
        "index": 552,
        "date": "11/24/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Founded in 1904, what private club based in New York City raises money for charity by holding \"roasts\" of such members as Jack Black and Betty White?",
        "answers": [
            "New York Yacht Club",
            "21 Club",
            "Yale Club",
            "Friars Club"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Friars Club"
    },
    {
        "index": 553,
        "date": "11/24/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " According to Merriam-Webster, which of these words has three different three-letter English words -- spelled out without interruption -- somewhere within it?",
        "answers": [
            "begin",
            "initiate",
            "activate",
            "launch"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " activate"
    },
    {
        "index": 554,
        "date": "11/24/2017",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Which of these is the name of a type of contraction that affects pregnant women, and NOT a winner of \"American Idol\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Trent Harmon",
            "Braxton Hicks",
            "David Cook",
            "Lee DeWyze"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Braxton Hicks"
    },
    {
        "index": 555,
        "date": "11/24/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " In the classic 1939 film \"The Wizard of Oz,\" the Wicked Witch of the West sports a large wart on which part of her face?",
        "answers": [
            "her nose",
            "her chin",
            "her cheek",
            "her forehead"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " her chin"
    },
    {
        "index": 556,
        "date": "11/24/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " While it's now Speaker of the House, what position -- held by men like Dean Rusk -- was next in line for the presidency after the Vice President from 1886 to 1947?",
        "answers": [
            "Attorney General",
            "Secretary of Defense",
            "Secretary of State",
            "Secretary of the Treasury"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Secretary of State"
    },
    {
        "index": 557,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Thought to have inspired the name of a Dr. Seuss character, the French word \"grincheux\" means what in English?",
        "answers": [
            "generous",
            "gigantic",
            "grumpy",
            "garlicky"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " grumpy"
    },
    {
        "index": 558,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Causing fierce debate, an \"A\" was recently added to the school curriculum acronym STEM to make it STEAM. What does the A represent?",
        "answers": [
            "acupuncture",
            "arts",
            "alchemy",
            "animal training"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " arts"
    },
    {
        "index": 559,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " As \"Schoolhouse Rock!\" tells us",
        "answers": [
            "nouns",
            "verbs",
            "adjectives",
            "curse words"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " nouns"
    },
    {
        "index": 560,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Inspired by the term for a baby kangaroo or koala, Outback Steakhouse doesn't offer its young diners a Kids Menu, but a what?",
        "answers": [
            "Hatchling Menu",
            "Joey Menu",
            "Whelp Menu",
            "Pup Menu"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Joey Menu"
    },
    {
        "index": 561,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " The answer to which of the following equations is NOT 1?",
        "answers": [
            "64-32-16-8-4-2-1",
            "100 + (1-100)",
            "1+1-1+1-1+1-1+1-1+1-1",
            "1+2-3+4-5+6-7+8-9"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 1+2-3+4-5+6-7+8-9"
    },
    {
        "index": 562,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " After Stephen Douglas accused him in a debate of being two-faced, who is said to have replied, \"Honestly, if I were two-faced, would I be showing you this one?\"",
        "answers": [
            "Ulysses S. Grant",
            "Abraham Lincoln",
            "Theodore Roosevelt",
            "Andrew Jackson"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Abraham Lincoln"
    },
    {
        "index": 563,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " \"Because you've incited the formation of lachrymal agent syn-Propanethial S-oxide\" is an explanation for why you do which of these things?",
        "answers": [
            "get a headache after eating ice cream",
            "cry when chopping onions",
            "sneeze when inhaling pepper",
            "pass gas after eating beans"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cry when chopping onions"
    },
    {
        "index": 564,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Three of these choices are definitions of words that can be created by removing the last letter of a U.S. state capital. Which one is NOT?",
        "answers": [
            "a selling of goods at bargain prices",
            "the 8th month of the Gregorian calendar",
            "the last name of Star Wars' Kylo",
            "A white bird used as a peace symbol"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the last name of Star Wars' Kylo"
    },
    {
        "index": 565,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to the Humane Society website, you should mix hydrogen peroxide, baking soda and dishwashing liquid if you want to do what to your dog?",
        "answers": [
            "make him invisible",
            "triple his size overnight",
            "de-skunk him",
            "turn him into a cat"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "de-skunk him"
    },
    {
        "index": 566,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Toys modeled after which movie villain make use of U.S. Trademark #77419252, described as \"the sound...created by breathing through a scuba tank regulator\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Lord Voldemort",
            "Hannibal Lecter",
            "Darth Vader",
            "Freddy Krueger"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Darth Vader"
    },
    {
        "index": 567,
        "date": "11/17/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Which of these numbers, whose square root is 11, equals the world record for the most scoops of ice cream ever balanced on one cone?",
        "answers": [
            "101",
            "111",
            "121",
            "131"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "121"
    },
    {
        "index": 568,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "250,000",
        "question": " Before the length of the game was changed to nine innings in 1857, the original rules of baseball stated that what would determine the winner?",
        "answers": [
            "first team to hit a home run",
            "first team to score 21 runs",
            "highest score after one hour",
            "highest score after all 9 players have batted"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " first team to score 21 runs"
    },
    {
        "index": 569,
        "date": "11/10/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " If your Air Force buddy tells you to \"Check your six,\" what should you do?",
        "answers": [
            "look behind you",
            "examine your zipper",
            "hide your beer",
            "keep an eye on your half-dozen children"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " look behind you"
    },
    {
        "index": 570,
        "date": "11/10/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Safety.com says if you want to deter burglars from robbing your home, you're better off getting a small dog instead of a big dog, because small dogs what?",
        "answers": [
            "kill the burglar with cuteness",
            "can make a citizen's arrest",
            "bark uncontrollably at visitors",
            "know karate"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bark uncontrollably at visitors"
    },
    {
        "index": 571,
        "date": "11/10/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Though it'd probably drive its employees insane today, in Amazon.com's early days, what happened in the office every time a sale was made?",
        "answers": [
            "a bell rang",
            "1000 doves were released in the break room",
            "a robot dumped Gatorade on everybody",
            "Jeff Bezos removed an article of clothing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a bell rang"
    },
    {
        "index": 572,
        "date": "11/10/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Dragging the overall GPA down, the person who finishes in the bottom of their class at the U.S. Naval Acadamy is aptly nicknamed the what?",
        "answers": [
            "boatswain",
            "quartermaster",
            "anchorman",
            "gunner's mate"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " anchorman"
    },
    {
        "index": 573,
        "date": "11/10/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Which variety of pepper usually doesn't contain capsaicin, and therefore is not spicy?",
        "answers": [
            "jalapeño pepper",
            "cayenne pepper",
            "bell pepper",
            "chili pepper"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bell pepper"
    },
    {
        "index": 574,
        "date": "11/10/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Despite being his fierce rival in the late '70s and early '80s, Björn Borg was a guest at what athlete's wedding to singer Patty Smythe in 1997?",
        "answers": [
            "Wayne Gretzsky",
            "John McEnroe",
            "Jack Nicklaus",
            "Greg LeMond"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " John McEnroe"
    },
    {
        "index": 575,
        "date": "11/10/2017",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " To spur tourism, in 1966 Chile renamed its Isla Más a Tierra after what Daniel Defoe novel, inspired by the true story of a man stranded there?",
        "answers": [
            "Robinson Crusoe Island",
            "Billy Budd Island",
            "Doctor Zhivago Island",
            "David Copperfield Island"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Robinson Crusoe Island"
    },
    {
        "index": 576,
        "date": "11/10/2017",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Which branch of the military boasts the most members who've risen to the rank of Commander-in-Chief, also known as President of the United States?",
        "answers": [
            "Army",
            "Navy",
            "Air Force",
            "Marines"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Army"
    },
    {
        "index": 577,
        "date": "11/10/2017",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " Your corpus callosum is what connects the two halves of which of these together?",
        "answers": [
            "heart",
            "brain",
            "lungs",
            "kidneys"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "brain"
    },
    {
        "index": 578,
        "date": "11/3/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " What is a mentee?",
        "answers": [
            "a tiny breath-freshening candy",
            "a gender-specific golf item",
            "the plural of manatee",
            "one who is mentored"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " one who is mentored"
    },
    {
        "index": 579,
        "date": "11/3/2017",
        "prize": "100,000",
        "question": " Before fingerprinting became widespread, law enforcement relied heavily on the Bertillon System, which identified criminals how?",
        "answers": [
            "by measuring various body parts",
            "by recording their voices",
            "by measuring exact weight",
            "by taking hair samples"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "by measuring various body parts"
    },
    {
        "index": 580,
        "date": "11/3/2017",
        "prize": "250,000",
        "question": " One of the longest words in the Bible, Mahershalalhashbaz is the name of a character in which book?",
        "answers": [
            "Exodus",
            "Job",
            "Isaiah",
            "Judges"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Isaiah"
    },
    {
        "index": 581,
        "date": "11/3/2017",
        "prize": "500,000",
        "question": " Saying they didn't have room for it, in 1956 New York's Museum of Modern Art rejected a free Andy Warhol drawing of what?",
        "answers": [
            "an ice cream cone",
            "a shoe",
            "a telephone booth",
            "a dog"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "a shoe"
    },
    {
        "index": 582,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " What band formed after the two frontmen ran into each other on a train platform in Kent in October 1961, both on their way to college classes in London?",
        "answers": [
            "ABBA",
            "Lynyrd Skynyrd",
            "The Rolling Stones",
            "The Bee Gees"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Rolling Stones"
    },
    {
        "index": 583,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Said to be the world's heaviest building at over 700,000 tons, Romania's Palace of the Parliament contains all but which of the following?",
        "answers": [
            "1 million cubic meters of marble",
            "220,000 square meters of carpeting",
            "145,000 royal sumo wrestlers",
            "480 chandeliers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 145,000 royal sumo wrestlers"
    },
    {
        "index": 584,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of these is not a noble gas on the periodic table of elements, but rather a brand of water-softening and beauty products?",
        "answers": [
            "Argon",
            "Radon",
            "Xenon",
            "Calgon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Calgon"
    },
    {
        "index": 585,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Otherwise known to turn brown very quickly, you can extend the life of what Mexican staple by keeping it chilled in a container topped with a small amount of water?",
        "answers": [
            "pâté",
            "guacamole",
            "Cheez Whiz",
            "fluffernutter"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " guacamole"
    },
    {
        "index": 586,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Fittingly, considering its name is thought to come from the French for \"to sleep,\" which member of the rodent family spends up to 75% of its short life in slumber?",
        "answers": [
            "chinchilla",
            "dormouse",
            "lemming",
            "beaver"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dormouse"
    },
    {
        "index": 587,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Wife of a publishing heir, what Florida socialite-turned-designer became known as the Queen of Prep for her iconic colorful shirt dresses?",
        "answers": [
            "Betsy Vanderbilt",
            "Nan Rockefeller",
            "Gwendolyn du Pont",
            "Lilly Pulitzer"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Lilly Pulitzer"
    },
    {
        "index": 588,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Which of these terms has NOT appeared in the title of a movie starring Tom Cruise?",
        "answers": [
            "rain",
            "sun",
            "thunder",
            "sky"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " sun"
    },
    {
        "index": 589,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Though today his photo's featured on the world's most valuable baseball card, who had the dubious distinction of striking out to end the first World Series in 1903?",
        "answers": [
            "Honus Wagner",
            "Rogers Hornsby",
            "Ty Cobb",
            "Lou Gehrig"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Honus Wagner"
    },
    {
        "index": 590,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Mentored by Wynton Marsalis, jazz musician and Julliard graduate Jon Batiste is the leader of what \"Late Show with Stephen Colbert\" house band?",
        "answers": [
            "Stay Cool",
            "Stay Human",
            "Stay Up Late",
            "Stay Tuned"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Stay Human"
    },
    {
        "index": 591,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Victorious in the election of 1824, the only US president-and-vice-president ticket to share the same first name were called what?",
        "answers": [
            "John",
            "William",
            "James",
            "Thomas"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " John"
    },
    {
        "index": 592,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " According to a 2017 Guardian article based on WHO data, what country leads the world by being home to 10 of its 20 most polluted cities?",
        "answers": [
            "Mexico",
            "India",
            "Russia",
            "China"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " India"
    },
    {
        "index": 593,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "100,000",
        "question": " According to the Social Security Administration, which of these has been ranked among the top 1000 newborn baby girl names for the year exactly once, in 2001?",
        "answers": [
            "Beyoncé",
            "Aaliyah",
            "Paris",
            "Hermione"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Beyoncé"
    },
    {
        "index": 594,
        "date": "10/27/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Socrates is famously attributed as saying, \"I am the wisest man alive, for I know one thing, and that is that\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "everyone loves my deviled eggs",
            "I know nothing",
            "the Mets are going all the way this year",
            "I can make"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " I know nothing"
    },
    {
        "index": 595,
        "date": "10/27/2017",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " In 2012, a plaque was put up in Hyde Park, Chicago, marking Barack and Michelle Obama's first kiss, which took place in 1989 just outside what establishment?",
        "answers": [
            "Baskin-Robbins",
            "Barnes & Noble",
            "Pizza Hut",
            "AMC movie theater"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Baskin-Robbins"
    },
    {
        "index": 596,
        "date": "10/20/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these is NOT one of the body parts you might be instructed to place on a colored dot in the classic game of Twister?",
        "answers": [
            "left foot",
            "right foot",
            "left hand",
            "right kidney"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " right kidney"
    },
    {
        "index": 597,
        "date": "10/20/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " What New York attorney headed west in 1884 to check the legal titles on some mineral claims, and ended up the namesake of a beloved national monument?",
        "answers": [
            "Charles E. Rushmore",
            "Guyzer O'Faithful",
            "Saul T. Lake",
            "Graham Canyon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Charles E. Rushmore"
    },
    {
        "index": 598,
        "date": "10/20/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " What do Americans call the medical device that Australians call a \"humidicrib\"?",
        "answers": [
            "stethoscope",
            "incubator",
            "pacemaker",
            "catheter"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " incubator"
    },
    {
        "index": 599,
        "date": "10/20/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " The word \"marinade\" is borrowed from the French word \"mariner,\" which means what?",
        "answers": [
            "to steam",
            "to slice",
            "to burn",
            "to pickle"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " to pickle"
    },
    {
        "index": 600,
        "date": "10/20/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Though a 1990 film version was dismissed as \"paranoid poppycock,\" critics hailed the 2017 Hulu series based on what dystopian Margaret Atwood novel?",
        "answers": [
            "Presumed Innocent",
            "Bright Lights, Big City",
            "The Handmaid's Tale",
            "Bonfire of the Vanities"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Handmaid's Tale"
    },
    {
        "index": 601,
        "date": "10/20/2017",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Given that the Earth is essentially a circle, what is its approximate rate of rotation in terms of degrees?",
        "answers": [
            "5 degrees per hour",
            "15 degrees per hour",
            "30 degrees per hour",
            "60 degrees per hour"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 15 degrees per hour"
    },
    {
        "index": 602,
        "date": "10/20/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Which of these is the name of the backing band for hip-hop legend Grandmaster Flash and NOT the title of a street racing action movie starring Vin Diesel?",
        "answers": [
            "Fast 5",
            "The Furious Five",
            "The Fast and the Furious",
            "Furious 7"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Furious Five"
    },
    {
        "index": 603,
        "date": "10/20/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Innovating fashion by dressing women in separates, what American designer's eponymous sportswear brand founded in 1968 features a lion in its logo?",
        "answers": [
            "Anne Klein",
            "Tom Ford",
            "Liz Claiborne",
            "Isaac Mizrahi"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Anne Klein"
    },
    {
        "index": 604,
        "date": "10/20/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " In competition diving, the 10-meter platform is how much higher than the 3-meter springboard?",
        "answers": [
            "203.5 inches",
            "231.9 inches",
            "275.6 inches",
            "308.7 inches"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "275.6 inches"
    },
    {
        "index": 605,
        "date": "10/6/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In high school, a whiz kid like you will probably take AP classes. What does \"AP\" stand for?",
        "answers": [
            "advanced placement",
            "apple pie",
            "animal planet",
            "Amy Poehler"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " advanced placement"
    },
    {
        "index": 606,
        "date": "10/6/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of these actual appetizingly-named Crayola colors is NOT a shade of orange?",
        "answers": [
            "vivid tangerine",
            "cotton candy",
            "mango tango",
            "macaroni & cheese"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cotton candy"
    },
    {
        "index": 607,
        "date": "10/6/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " With the exception of Doc, all of the dwarfs in Snow White & the Seven Dwarfs have names that are what part of speech?",
        "answers": [
            "verbs",
            "prepositions",
            "adjectives",
            "conjunctions"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " adjectives"
    },
    {
        "index": 608,
        "date": "10/6/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " While they were all ultimately rejected, at one point which device's suggested names included CPG (for Cyber Playground) and EHQ (for Entertainment Headquarters)?",
        "answers": [
            "Segway scooter",
            "Xbox",
            "Beats headphones",
            "fidget spinner"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Xbox"
    },
    {
        "index": 609,
        "date": "10/6/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which of these elements contains the name of another element within it?",
        "answers": [
            "rutherfordium",
            "mercury",
            "platinum",
            "phosphorus"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " platinum"
    },
    {
        "index": 610,
        "date": "10/6/2017",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Showing that Hannibal's legendary journey really could have been done, British explorer John Hoyt crossed the Alps in 1959, led by what animal?",
        "answers": [
            "Bengal tiger",
            "elephant",
            "hippopotamus",
            "grizzly bear"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " elephant"
    },
    {
        "index": 611,
        "date": "10/6/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " One trick to curing insomnia is to distract yourself by counting backwards from 300 to 0 by 3's, during which you'd count all but which of these numbers?",
        "answers": [
            "267",
            "201",
            "163",
            "96"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 163"
    },
    {
        "index": 612,
        "date": "10/6/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Which of the following scales categorizes the likelihood of asteroids impacting Earth?",
        "answers": [
            "Beaufort scale",
            "Torino scale",
            "Saffir-Simpson scale",
            "Fujita scale"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Torino scale"
    },
    {
        "index": 613,
        "date": "10/6/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " This question might seem atrocious, but in \"Mary Poppins\", how many letters are in the famously long word that starts with \"super\" and ends with \"docious\"?",
        "answers": [
            "28",
            "31",
            "34",
            "37"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 34"
    },
    {
        "index": 614,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Someone working in which of the following occupations typically has a tip jar?",
        "answers": [
            "mall security guard",
            "jackhammer operator",
            "barista",
            "judge"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " barista"
    },
    {
        "index": 615,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " One of the highest honors a Garden State native can receive, all but which of these are names of rest stops on the New Jersey Turnpike?",
        "answers": [
            "Thomas Edison Service Area",
            "Woodrow Wilson Service Area",
            "Walt Whitman Service Area",
            "Nicole \"Snookie\" Polizzo Service Area"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Nicole \"Snookie\" Polizzo Service Area"
    },
    {
        "index": 616,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Only discovered in 1961 and thought to be possessed by fewer than 100 people on Earth, Rh-null is an extremely rare what?",
        "answers": [
            "British sports car",
            "Van Gogh painting",
            "Aerosmith album",
            "blood disorder"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " blood disorder"
    },
    {
        "index": 617,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " In the name of the airline QANTAS, what does the \"Q\" stand for?",
        "answers": [
            "Queensland",
            "Quebec",
            "Qatar",
            "Quemoy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Queensland"
    },
    {
        "index": 618,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " With Cameron seemingly losing herself in Seurat's pointilism, what '80s movie did Smithsonian say \"perfectly illustrates the power of art museums\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Rage",
            "Sixteen Candles",
            "Say Anything",
            "Ferris Bueller's Day Off"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Ferris Bueller's Day Off"
    },
    {
        "index": 619,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Of what relation to you is your mother's sister's daughter's daughter's sister's mother?",
        "answers": [
            "first cousin",
            "niece",
            "aunt",
            "second cousin once removed"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " first cousin"
    },
    {
        "index": 620,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " After creating her award-winning web series \"The Misadventures of Awkward Black Girl\", Issa Rae went on to star on what acclaimed HBO series?",
        "answers": [
            "Divorce",
            "The Leftovers",
            "Insecure",
            "Westworld"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Insecure"
    },
    {
        "index": 621,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Since it takes the Earth just over 365 days to orbit the sun, which calendar makes up for it by periodically adding a \"leap month\" called \"Adar Alef\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Hindu calendar",
            "Hebrew calendar",
            "Inuit calendar",
            "Islamic calendar"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Hebrew calendar"
    },
    {
        "index": 622,
        "date": "9/29/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " The state of Alaska says that when building a birdhouse, you should NOT add which feature, because it may give predators better access to eggs?",
        "answers": [
            "a perch",
            "wicker patio furniture",
            "vinyl siding",
            "a hot tub"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a perch"
    },
    {
        "index": 623,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " From which WikiHow article can you learn techniques such as pulling on an invisible rope, climbing an invisible ladder, and leaning on an invisible pole?",
        "answers": [
            "How to Impress Your Girlfriend's Parents",
            "How to Nail a Job Interview",
            "How to Get Out of Jury Duty",
            "How to Mime"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " How to Mime"
    },
    {
        "index": 624,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " What pro football team was founded in 1959 by Barron Hilton, a businessman who had fittingly started a credit card company just a few years earlier?",
        "answers": [
            "Tennessee Titans",
            "Oakland Raiders",
            "New Orleans Saints",
            "San Diego Chargers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " San Diego Chargers"
    },
    {
        "index": 625,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " Signed into law in 1968, what was the last federal holiday to be established before Martin Luther King Day was created in 1983?",
        "answers": [
            "Labor Day",
            "Thanksgiving",
            "Veterans Day",
            "Columbus Day"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Columbus Day"
    },
    {
        "index": 626,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "100,000",
        "question": " Over David Letterman's 33 years in late-night TV, which of these people appeared the most times as a guest on his shows?",
        "answers": [
            "Tom Brokaw",
            "Marv Albert",
            "Regis Philbin",
            "Jack Hanna"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Regis Philbin"
    },
    {
        "index": 627,
        "date": "9/22/2017",
        "prize": "250,000",
        "question": " Causing the audience to erupt into a standing ovation, Apple's Macintosh \"spoke\" during its 1984 debut, saying \"Hello, I'm Macintosh\" followed by what?",
        "answers": [
            "\"So this is what the future looks like.\"",
            "\"Let me start by complimenting your tie.\"",
            "\"It sure is great to get out of that box.\"",
            "\"Let's make your dreams come true.\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"It sure is great to get out of that box.\""
    },
    {
        "index": 628,
        "date": "2/17/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these is a type of dumpling used in a Chinese soup and NOT a type of particle analyzed in physics?",
        "answers": [
            "photon",
            "gluon",
            "lepton",
            "wonton"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " wonton"
    },
    {
        "index": 629,
        "date": "2/17/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " ICYMI, according to UrbanDictionary.com, the popular internet abbreviation \"ICYMI\" stands for what?",
        "answers": [
            "In Case You Missed It",
            "I Challenge Your Monkey's Intelligence",
            "Ice Cream? Yum! May I?",
            "I'm Carpooling with Your Mambo Instructor"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " In Case You Missed It"
    },
    {
        "index": 630,
        "date": "2/17/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Despite dog mushing being recognized as its state sport back in 1972, what 49th state didn't adopt the malamute as its state dog until 2010?",
        "answers": [
            "Maine",
            "Alaska",
            "Oregon",
            "New Mexico"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Alaska"
    },
    {
        "index": 631,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " A thousand thousands is equal to what?",
        "answers": [
            "one million",
            "ten million",
            "one hundred million",
            "one billion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " one million"
    },
    {
        "index": 632,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In what classic children's counting game are the hands used to represent root vegetables?",
        "answers": [
            "One Potato, Two Potato",
            "Duck, Duck, Omelette",
            "Tic-Tac-Tuna",
            "Truth or Doughnuts"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " One Potato, Two Potato"
    },
    {
        "index": 633,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Meaning \"dead from laughter,\" mort de rire, abbreviated MDR, is a way of texting what in French?",
        "answers": [
            "IMHO",
            "BRB",
            "LOL",
            "TTYL"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " LOL"
    },
    {
        "index": 634,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Mathematically, which of the following statements is false?",
        "answers": [
            "0 x 0 = 0",
            "1 x 1 = 1",
            "√2 x √2 = 2",
            "pi x pi = pi"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " pi x pi = pi"
    },
    {
        "index": 635,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Not one solitary word in this question can be classified as what part of speech?",
        "answers": [
            "verb",
            "adjective",
            "preposition",
            "interjection"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " interjection"
    },
    {
        "index": 636,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Although he's a pachyderm, Dr. Seuss' Horton the Elephant behaves similarly to monotremes like the platypus in that he is a mammal that does what?",
        "answers": [
            "walks on two legs",
            "lives underground",
            "hatches eggs",
            "flies short distances"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " hatches eggs"
    },
    {
        "index": 637,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " What living legend shares its name with the French explorer who is credited with naming Canada",
        "answers": [
            "Cartier",
            "Hermès",
            "Chanel",
            "Baccarat"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Cartier"
    },
    {
        "index": 638,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Traveling through outer space, light waves travel at approximately what constant speed?",
        "answers": [
            "186,000 miles per second",
            "186,000 miles per minute",
            "186,000 miles per hour",
            "186,000 miles per day"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 186,000 miles per second"
    },
    {
        "index": 639,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "10,000 (CTQ)",
        "question": " In 2002, what company released an oven-like device that allows kids to melt down its products and make them into new ones?",
        "answers": [
            "Crayola",
            "Tonka",
            "American Girl",
            "Nintendo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Crayola"
    },
    {
        "index": 640,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Currently holding one of the most important positions in the US government, Loretta Lynch is the 1st African-American woman to serve as what?",
        "answers": [
            "Secretary of Homeland Security",
            "White House Chief of Staff",
            "Attorney-General",
            "Director of the Secret Service"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Attorney-General"
    },
    {
        "index": 641,
        "date": "11/18/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Of the following, who was NOT born in the 19th century?",
        "answers": [
            "C.S. Lewis",
            "Pablo Picasso",
            "Ludwig van Beethoven",
            "Ulysses S. Grant"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Ludwig van Beethoven"
    },
    {
        "index": 642,
        "date": "3/10/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Acording to an article on NationalGeographic.com, in an \"Exorcist-style display,\" owls compensate for their fixed eyes by doing what?",
        "answers": [
            "turning their head 270 degrees",
            "vomiting green goo",
            "hooting in a creepy voice",
            "allying themselves with Satan"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " turning their head 270 degrees"
    },
    {
        "index": 643,
        "date": "3/10/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " \"Swedish\", \"Thai\", and \"hot stone\" are three of the most popular varieties of what?",
        "answers": [
            "necktie",
            "massage",
            "puppet show",
            "banjo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " massage"
    },
    {
        "index": 644,
        "date": "3/10/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Perhaps proving that you get what you pay for, 75% of all cars made by what company founded in 1906 are still on the road today?",
        "answers": [
            "Fiat",
            "Ford",
            "Rolls-Royce",
            "Volkswagon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Rolls-Royce"
    },
    {
        "index": 645,
        "date": "3/10/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Recorded by a native son, what song used in many of Jamaica's tourism campaigns has the New York Times dubbed its \"unofficial national anthem\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Stand By Me",
            "Joy To The World",
            "Imagine",
            "One Love"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " One Love"
    },
    {
        "index": 646,
        "date": "3/10/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Though they all may seem fitting, which of these real phobias is the only one that's correctly matched with the things its sufferers fear?",
        "answers": [
            "cryophobia: fear of whining babies",
            "doraphobia: fear of animated explorers",
            "triskaidekaphobia: fear of Triscuits",
            "zoophobia: fear of animals"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " zoophobia: fear of animals"
    },
    {
        "index": 647,
        "date": "3/10/2017",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Though it's now possible thanks to a 2015 rule change, what US sports league has never seen a game where either team has had a score of 1?",
        "answers": [
            "NBA",
            "NFL",
            "NHL",
            "MLB"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " NFL"
    },
    {
        "index": 648,
        "date": "3/10/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Founded in 2004, which of these companies has a stock ticker symbol that's the same as its name?",
        "answers": [
            "Amazon",
            "YouTube",
            "Boeing",
            "Yelp"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Yelp"
    },
    {
        "index": 649,
        "date": "3/10/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Often called the best medicine, studies do show that laughter reduces the body's production of what stress hormone?",
        "answers": [
            "melatonin",
            "thyroxine",
            "insulin",
            "cortisol"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cortisol"
    },
    {
        "index": 650,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which two factors are considered when determining a person's BMI, or Body Mass Index?",
        "answers": [
            "height & weight",
            "name & address",
            "eye color & hair color",
            "favorite food & ATM PIN number"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " height & weight"
    },
    {
        "index": 651,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of these was the name of the 15th Chief Justice of the United States, and is NOT an item on the menu at Jack-in-the-Box?",
        "answers": [
            "Sourdough Jack",
            "Warren Burger",
            "Supreme Croissant",
            "Monster Taco"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Warren Burger"
    },
    {
        "index": 652,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " With \"members\" going from a 200-degree sauna to the -100 degree outdoors, it's only possible to join the \"300 Club\" a few days out of the year, where?",
        "answers": [
            "in Australia",
            "in Antarctica",
            "in Aruba",
            "in American Samoa"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " in Antarctica"
    },
    {
        "index": 653,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " According to Dole.eu, negative geotropism gives what fruits their shape as they bend to grow upward toward the sun instead of down toward the ground?",
        "answers": [
            "grapes",
            "bananas",
            "avocados",
            "carrots"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bananas"
    },
    {
        "index": 654,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Former world chamption skateboarder Per Welinder is credited for performing stunts in what '80s movie?",
        "answers": [
            "Risky Business",
            "WarGames",
            "Back to the Future",
            "Footloose"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Back to the Future"
    },
    {
        "index": 655,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " When water is poured into a certain anise-flavored liqueur, it changes from clear to milky, a phenomenon known as what?",
        "answers": [
            "kahlua reaction",
            "sake syndrome",
            "ouzo effect",
            "mezcal miracle"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ouzo effect"
    },
    {
        "index": 656,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Despite releasing their seventh consecutive #1 album in 2016, who hasn't had a #1 single on Billboard's Hot 100 chart since 2007's \"Stronger\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Pink",
            "Taylor Swift",
            "Justin Bieber",
            "Kanye West"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Kanye West"
    },
    {
        "index": 657,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Said to be the longest road in Europe at nearly 5,000 miles, the E40 connects Calais, France to Ridder, Kazakhstan, passing through all but which of these cities?",
        "answers": [
            "Aachen, Germany",
            "Katowice, Poland",
            "Kiev, Ukraine",
            "Palermo, Italy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Palermo, Italy"
    },
    {
        "index": 658,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Modern Library's list of the 100 Best Novels includes titles containing all but which of these names of body parts?",
        "answers": [
            "heart",
            "head",
            "arms",
            "feet"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " feet"
    },
    {
        "index": 659,
        "date": "1/20/2017",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " A UCSB study found that aside from a range of grays, dogs perceive the world only in shades of what two colors?",
        "answers": [
            "red and green",
            "orange and red",
            "blue and yellow",
            "violet and green"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " blue and yellow"
    },
    {
        "index": 660,
        "date": "12/23/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Though they are eligible for the \"Gold Whistle Award\" for sports officiating, what league's officials do not use whistles?",
        "answers": [
            "NBA",
            "NFL",
            "MLB",
            "NHL"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " MLB"
    },
    {
        "index": 661,
        "date": "12/23/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " A tagline often heard in monster truck and pro wrestling ads boasts, \"We'll sell you the whole seat, but you'll only need the\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "edge",
            "lumbar support",
            "legs",
            "anchor bolts"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " edge"
    },
    {
        "index": 662,
        "date": "12/23/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " To make cheap wine more tasty, Marie Claire suggests \"hyperaerating\" it by pouring it into your what and running it for 30 seconds?",
        "answers": [
            "vacuum cleaner",
            "blender",
            "toaster",
            "particle accelerator"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " blender"
    },
    {
        "index": 663,
        "date": "12/23/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Originally releasing it in the 1980s, in 2016 Hi-C once again began selling its classic Ecto Cooler flavor, as a tie-in with what movie?",
        "answers": [
            "Finding Dory",
            "X-Men: Apocalypse",
            "Ghostbusters",
            "Independence Day: Resurgence"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Ghostbusters"
    },
    {
        "index": 664,
        "date": "12/23/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Held every spring in New Mexico, the Gathering of Nations attracts people from all across the US and Canada, and bills itself as the country's largest what?",
        "answers": [
            "powwow",
            "comic book convention",
            "rodeo",
            "flea market"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " powwow"
    },
    {
        "index": 665,
        "date": "12/23/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " If you wanted to take a pleasantly verdant stroll, you'd be best off walking where?",
        "answers": [
            "in the snow",
            "through a park",
            "in a city center",
            "along a pier"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " through a park"
    },
    {
        "index": 666,
        "date": "12/23/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Since many were hired en masse after a famous 1981 labor dispute, a flood of retirees may leave what profession alarmingly short-staffed?",
        "answers": [
            "coal miners",
            "air traffic controllers",
            "MLB umpires",
            "UPS drivers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " air traffic controllers"
    },
    {
        "index": 667,
        "date": "12/23/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Which of the following classic books has a title character whose last name is \"Woodhouse\"?",
        "answers": [
            "\"Rebecca\" by Daphne Du Maurier",
            "\"Matilda\" by Roald Dahl",
            "\"Heidi\" by Johann Spyri",
            "\"Emma\" by Jane Austen"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"Emma\" by Jane Austen"
    },
    {
        "index": 668,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " The Hindu holiday Diwali is known as \"the festival of lights\", a phrase which also describes which of these holidays?",
        "answers": [
            "Mardi Gras",
            "Ramadan",
            "Hanukkah",
            "Kwanzaa"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Hanukkah"
    },
    {
        "index": 669,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these will you NOT find on Money magazine's list of \"11 Ways to Save Money at the Movies This Summer\"?",
        "answers": [
            "go during off times",
            "eat beforehand",
            "stick to 2D",
            "wear a gray wig to get a senior discount"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " wear a gray wig to get a senior discount"
    },
    {
        "index": 670,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Formerly called the King's Highway, Philadelphia's Frankford Avenue is home to America's oldest continually used what, built in 1697?",
        "answers": [
            "bridge",
            "electric vehicle charging station",
            "rest stop vending machine",
            "drive-thru car wash"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bridge"
    },
    {
        "index": 671,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " The Chinese tradition of Yum Chu, or drinking tea while eating different varieties of small dishes is better known in the US by what time-worn phrase?",
        "answers": [
            "tai chi",
            "gung ho",
            "dim sum",
            "feng shui"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dim sum"
    },
    {
        "index": 672,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Students of UT-Austin were probably feeling \"alright, alright, alright\" when what fellow Longhorn signed on to co-teach a film class in 2016?",
        "answers": [
            "Ben Affleck",
            "Robert Downey, Jr.",
            "Matthew McConaughey",
            "Edward Norton"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Matthew McConaughey"
    },
    {
        "index": 673,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " What medical journal claims to feature \"the best in peer-reviewed, cutting edge original research\" in \"thoracic surgery\" and \"related disciplines\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Chest Journal",
            "Hand Journal",
            "Brain Journal",
            "Knee Journal"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Chest Journal"
    },
    {
        "index": 674,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Playing off a misheard lyric in \"Blank Space\", what series of novels features the book \"The Secrets of the Starbucks Lovers\"?",
        "answers": [
            "50 Shades of Beyoncé",
            "Taylor Swift: Girl Detective",
            "The Berenstein Biebers",
            "Adele in Wonderland"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Taylor Swift: Girl Detective"
    },
    {
        "index": 675,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " According to a common kitchen tip, home chefs can remove the scent of onion or garlic from their hands simply by rubbing them on what for 10 seconds?",
        "answers": [
            "linoleum floor",
            "granite coutertop",
            "stainless steel faucet",
            "wood veneer cabinet door"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " stainless steel faucet"
    },
    {
        "index": 676,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Besides Elizabeth, what are the 3 names that belonged to a reigning king or queen of England in the 20th century?",
        "answers": [
            "Anne, Henry, Edward",
            "James, Victoria, Henry",
            "Edward, George, Anne",
            "George, Victoria, Edward"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " George, Victoria, Edward"
    },
    {
        "index": 677,
        "date": "12/9/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Slightly wider than an American bill and much taller, the largest euro note features color-changing purple ink, a counterfeit-resistant hologram, and is worth what?",
        "answers": [
            "€100",
            "€200",
            "€500",
            "€1000"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " €500"
    },
    {
        "index": 678,
        "date": "11/11/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Someone who makes a lot of money while doing little work for it is commonly said to be riding a what?",
        "answers": [
            "freight train",
            "gravy train",
            "bridal train",
            "soul train"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " gravy train"
    },
    {
        "index": 679,
        "date": "11/11/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Largely due to France ending the practice of military conscription, reduced demand has left the country with only one supplier of traditional what?",
        "answers": [
            "croissants",
            "paintings",
            "berets",
            "wines"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " berets"
    },
    {
        "index": 680,
        "date": "11/11/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In 2016, NPR experienced a minute of dead air after a \"junior journalist\" pressed the wrong button, a mishap that occurred on what special day?",
        "answers": [
            "St. Patrick's Day",
            "Arbor Day",
            "Take Your Child to Work Day",
            "New Year's Day"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Take Your Child to Work Day"
    },
    {
        "index": 681,
        "date": "11/11/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " What 2016 Broadway musical employs a \"pie consultant\" who makes a fresh pie before each performance to send an authentic aroma through the theater?",
        "answers": [
            "The Book of Mormon",
            "School of Rock",
            "Waitress",
            "The Lion King"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Waitress"
    },
    {
        "index": 682,
        "date": "11/11/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Researchers have recently made major advances in their study of the gene NEK-1, thanks to donations from the Ice Bucket Challenge, created to help fight what?",
        "answers": [
            "diabetes",
            "ALS",
            "leukemia",
            "autism"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ALS"
    },
    {
        "index": 683,
        "date": "11/11/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Partly due to its banker villain, what movie did the House Un-American Activities Committee suspect of being Communist propaganda when it was first released?",
        "answers": [
            "Pinocchio",
            "Casablanca",
            "The Graduate",
            "It's a Wonderful Life"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " It's a Wonderful Life"
    },
    {
        "index": 684,
        "date": "11/11/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " If you travel outside the United States, it may be helpful to know that 37 degrees Celsius is considered what?",
        "answers": [
            "freezing point of water",
            "boiling point of water",
            "normal body temperature",
            "room temperature"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " normal body temperature"
    },
    {
        "index": 685,
        "date": "11/11/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Five hundred fifty-five feet tall and weighing over 80,000 tons, what was briefly the world's tallest structure before being surpassed by the Eiffel Tower?",
        "answers": [
            "Washington Monument",
            "Gateway Arch",
            "Golden Gate Bridge",
            "Statue of Liberty"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Washington Monument"
    },
    {
        "index": 686,
        "date": "11/4/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " PiedPiper.com is a tech company website that is really an advertisement for what HBO show?",
        "answers": [
            "Silicon Valley",
            "Veep",
            "Game of Thrones",
            "Girls"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Silicon Valley"
    },
    {
        "index": 687,
        "date": "11/4/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " After Andrew Stanton finished an hour-long pitch, Pixar boss John Lassiter greenlit what movie, saying, \"you had me at 'fish'\"?",
        "answers": [
            "The Incredibles",
            "Monsters, Inc.",
            "Finding Nemo",
            "Toy Story"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Finding Nemo"
    },
    {
        "index": 688,
        "date": "11/4/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " After nearly a decade of asking \"Can you hear me now?,\" in 2016 actor Paul Marcerelli jumped to the competition, becoming a spokesman for what company?",
        "answers": [
            "Burger King",
            "Chevrolet",
            "Sprint",
            "Pepsi"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Sprint"
    },
    {
        "index": 689,
        "date": "11/4/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Because its mayor thinks parents have let things get out of control, Belleville, IL is one of many towns to ban what holiday tradition for kids beyond the 8th grade?",
        "answers": [
            "trick-or-treating",
            "decorating Christmas trees",
            "coloring Easter eggs",
            "pledging allegiance on the 4th of July"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " trick-or-treating"
    },
    {
        "index": 690,
        "date": "11/4/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " \"Unfortunately, yes\" says WebMD in response to a question about whether what virus-induced skin condition is contageous?",
        "answers": [
            "moles",
            "acne",
            "razor burn",
            "warts"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " warts"
    },
    {
        "index": 691,
        "date": "11/4/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which of the following is neither a famous martial artist, nor a famous director, nor the former star of TVs \"Dawson's Creek\"?",
        "answers": [
            "James Van Der Beek",
            "Gus Van Sant",
            "Jean-Claude Van Damme",
            "Abraham Van Helsing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Abraham Van Helsing"
    },
    {
        "index": 692,
        "date": "11/4/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " With many of its 8 million residents already shunning certain meats and shellfish, what country now reportedly has the world's most vegans per capita?",
        "answers": [
            "Japan",
            "Israel",
            "Indonesia",
            "Iran"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Israel"
    },
    {
        "index": 693,
        "date": "11/4/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Released in 1971 and clocking in at about 8-1/2 minutes, a song by which of these acts is the longest #1 hit of all time?",
        "answers": [
            "Pink Floyd",
            "The Beatles",
            "Don McLean",
            "Bob Dylan"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Don McLean"
    },
    {
        "index": 694,
        "date": "10/28/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of the following comes in varieties including inground, above ground and Olympic-sized?",
        "answers": [
            "caskets",
            "couches",
            "swimming pools",
            "bidets"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " swimming pools"
    },
    {
        "index": 695,
        "date": "10/28/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Due to slumping sales during the Vietnam War, what toy got a \"makeover\" in 1969, being re-released with \"life-like hair and [a] beard\"?",
        "answers": [
            "GI Joe",
            "Tickle Me Elmo",
            "Gumby",
            "American Girl doll"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " GI Joe"
    },
    {
        "index": 696,
        "date": "10/28/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In a recent Gallup survey of honesty and ethics in various professons, which of these ranked just as low as telemarketers and car salesmen?",
        "answers": [
            "elementary school teachers",
            "anesthesiologists",
            "members of Congress",
            "librarians"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " members of Congress"
    },
    {
        "index": 697,
        "date": "10/28/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " According to the Washington Post, in 2015 the US had a record 4,144 what, breaking the previous record of 4,131 set back in 1873?",
        "answers": [
            "living Civil War veterans",
            "breweries",
            "telegraph operators",
            "spittoon manufacturers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " breweries"
    },
    {
        "index": 698,
        "date": "10/28/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Mentioned in the Queen song \"Bohemian Rhapsody,\" what stock character from Italian theater is usually portrayed as a conceited, boastful clown?",
        "answers": [
            "Capitano",
            "Dottore",
            "Arlecchino",
            "Scaramouche"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Scaramouche"
    },
    {
        "index": 699,
        "date": "10/28/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " What low-cost gym attempts to quiet loud grunters with flashing blue lights and a piercing siren known as the \"Lunk Alarm\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Crunch",
            "Gold's Gym",
            "Planet Fitness",
            "Equinox"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Planet Fitness"
    },
    {
        "index": 700,
        "date": "10/28/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " What is the three-letter abbreviation for the degenerative brain disease found in many football players and boxers who've suffered repeated concussions?",
        "answers": [
            "AST",
            "CTE",
            "DNL",
            "SCP"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " CTE"
    },
    {
        "index": 701,
        "date": "10/28/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Hardcore foodies can likely tell the difference between an Island Creek, a Hama Hama and a European Flat, as they're all varieties of what?",
        "answers": [
            "mushroom",
            "pheasant",
            "foie gras",
            "oyster"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " oyster"
    },
    {
        "index": 702,
        "date": "10/21/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Raising the flag on your mailbox indicates what to your letter carrier?",
        "answers": [
            "the mailbox is in distress",
            "a famous piece of mail has died",
            "there's outgoing mail inside",
            "you'd like help licking envelopes"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " there's outgoing mail inside"
    },
    {
        "index": 703,
        "date": "10/21/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " If you select the \"Tribute to Elvis\" package at Las Vegas' Little White Wedding Chapel, you get to recite your vows while seated in what vehicle?",
        "answers": [
            "a blue rickshaw",
            "a silver subway car",
            "a pink Cadillac",
            "a rainbow-colored blimp"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a pink Cadillac"
    },
    {
        "index": 704,
        "date": "10/21/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " To help its early European immigrants prepare for their citizenship exams, Northeast Minneapolis named a stretch of its streets sequentially after what?",
        "answers": [
            "mythological creatures",
            "US presidents",
            "fruits and vegetables",
            "Oscar-winning actors"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " US presidents"
    },
    {
        "index": 705,
        "date": "10/21/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Known as \"the Jewish Mark Twain,\" Sholem Aleichem's stories were the basis for what Broadway musical, originally called \"The Old Country\"?",
        "answers": [
            "The Phantom of the Opera",
            "Fiddler on the Roof",
            "A Chorus Line",
            "Hair"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Fiddler on the Roof"
    },
    {
        "index": 706,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " While they've had a wider variety of automobiles in the past, who today offers only four models - the 200, the 300, the Pacifica, and the Town and Country?",
        "answers": [
            "Buick",
            "Dodge",
            "Jeep",
            "Chrysler"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Chrysler"
    },
    {
        "index": 707,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Also known as \"Ferberization,\" the \"CIO\" method for getting babies to sleep on their own suggests that parents let their children do what?",
        "answers": [
            "cry it out",
            "crochet it out",
            "canoe it out",
            "cha-cha it out"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cry it out"
    },
    {
        "index": 708,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In 2013, the Coca-Cola company made headlines for allegedly firing a veteran delivery driver who committed what disloyal act while on break?",
        "answers": [
            "eating a Big Mac",
            "drinking a Pepsi",
            "using a PC",
            "switching to AT&T"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " drinking a Pepsi"
    },
    {
        "index": 709,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Attended by seafood lovers every year, what Ocean City, NJ pageant's past winners have included Crabopatra, Crabunzel and Crabahontas?",
        "answers": [
            "Miss Crustacean",
            "World's Sexiest Mollusk",
            "All-American Orca",
            "Scallop of the Year"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Miss Crustacean"
    },
    {
        "index": 710,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " The first and most-often sung verse of what patriotic song begins and ends with a question?",
        "answers": [
            "You're a Grand Old Flag",
            "My Country 'Tis of Thee",
            "Star Spangled Banner",
            "America the Beautiful"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Star Spangled Banner"
    },
    {
        "index": 711,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Starring Priyanka Chopra as Alex Parrish, the ABC thriller \"Quantico\" is named for the Virginia city where which of the following is located?",
        "answers": [
            "the FBI Academy",
            "Secret Service headquarters",
            "CIA headquarters",
            "the U.S. Naval Academy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the FBI Academy"
    },
    {
        "index": 712,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " The Oxford Dictionary defines room temperature, in metric terms, as \"a comfortable ambient temperature, generally taken as about\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "5℃",
            "20℃",
            "35℃",
            "50℃"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 20℃"
    },
    {
        "index": 713,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Letting people take pictures with it while holding a fake leg, the Visitors Center in Fargo, ND, has a replica of what infamous movie prop?",
        "answers": [
            "a bulldozer",
            "a wood chipper",
            "a riding mower",
            "a combine harvester"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a wood chipper"
    },
    {
        "index": 714,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " The name of what country's capital contains the name of its official state religion?",
        "answers": [
            "Kenya",
            "Brazil",
            "Pakistan",
            "Japan"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Pakistan"
    },
    {
        "index": 715,
        "date": "10/14/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " All of these musicians appeared on the 1985 charity single \"We Are the World\". For which of them has that been their only #1 hit on Billboard's Hot 100 chart?",
        "answers": [
            "Billy Joel",
            "Stevie Wonder",
            "Cyndi Lauper",
            "Bruce Springsteen"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Bruce Springsteen"
    },
    {
        "index": 716,
        "date": "10/7/2016",
        "prize": "1,000",
        "question": " Which of these words would you NOT find in an edition of the best-selling cookbook \"The Joy of Cooking\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Garbanzo",
            "Gazpacho",
            "Gorgonzola",
            "Gonzaga"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Gonzaga"
    },
    {
        "index": 717,
        "date": "10/7/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Inspiring other states to follow suit, North Carolina saw what jump 16% the year after it introduced the first \"Click It or Ticket\" campaign in 1993?",
        "answers": [
            "seat belt use",
            "retractible pen sales",
            "the number of Internet pop-up ads",
            "enrollment in African language classes"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " seat belt use"
    },
    {
        "index": 718,
        "date": "10/7/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Violating his Hindu beliefs, Brittanica says that Mohandas Gandhi's \"most shocking\" teenage behavior was what?",
        "answers": [
            "making prank calls",
            "doing keg stands",
            "eating meat",
            "sexting"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " eating meat"
    },
    {
        "index": 719,
        "date": "10/7/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " According to WebMD, if the answer is \"yes,\" the victim will not be able to respond verbally when you ask them, \"Are you\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "dizzy",
            "having a leg cramp",
            "choking",
            "experiencing a midlife crisis"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " choking"
    },
    {
        "index": 720,
        "date": "10/7/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " In what Olympic race do competitors travel as fast as they can while facing backwards?",
        "answers": [
            "racewalking",
            "downhill skiing",
            "luge",
            "rowing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " rowing"
    },
    {
        "index": 721,
        "date": "10/7/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which of these hit songs was performed by LeAnn Rimes and NOT by a band whose name rhymes?",
        "answers": [
            "Blame it on the Rain",
            "Dead Man's Party",
            "Free Bird",
            "How Do I Know"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " How Do I Know"
    },
    {
        "index": 722,
        "date": "10/7/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " The 2010 book \"The Disappearing Spoon\" recounts the CIA's alleged plan to kill Fidel Castro by putting what poisonous element where?",
        "answers": [
            "thallium in his socks",
            "magnesium in his underwear",
            "barium in his hat",
            "lithium in his handkerchief"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " thallium in his socks"
    },
    {
        "index": 723,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Opened in 1923, the Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland claims that its historic building is \"home to one of -- if not the\" largest what \"in the world\"?",
        "answers": [
            "vault doors",
            "trap doors",
            "screen doors",
            "doggie doors"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " vault doors"
    },
    {
        "index": 724,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " A secret \"the beauty industry doesn't want you to know,\" Reader's Digest says the main difference between designer and drugstore cosmetics is what?",
        "answers": [
            "the quality of the ingredients",
            "how good they look",
            "how long they last",
            "their packaging"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " their packaging"
    },
    {
        "index": 725,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " What word can describe someone from Arizona's capital AND the members of an ancient Mediterranean civilization?",
        "answers": [
            "Phoenicians",
            "Tusconians [NOTE: spelled thus on the show rather than \"Tucsonians\"]",
            "Flagstaffians",
            "Yuman beings"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Phoenicians"
    },
    {
        "index": 726,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Named for a phenomenon studied in chaos theory, what 2004 Ashton Kutcher thriller featured the tagline \"Change one thing, change everything\"?",
        "answers": [
            "The Worm Phenomenon",
            "The Blowfish Principle",
            "The Wombat Conjecture",
            "The Butterfly Effect"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Butterfly Effect"
    },
    {
        "index": 727,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Declining the help of experts in a native martial art, on a 1979 visit to Japan, Margaret Thatcher rejected an offer to be protected by 20 people called what?",
        "answers": [
            "\"kung fu mistresses\"",
            "\"karate ladies\"",
            "\"caponeia maidens\"",
            "\"taekwondo women\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"karate ladies\""
    },
    {
        "index": 728,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " With mentions in more than 20 books of the Old Testament, what is thought to be one of the earliest cultivated foods?",
        "answers": [
            "parsley",
            "figs",
            "bananas",
            "potatoes"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " figs"
    },
    {
        "index": 729,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " On its list of top places to retire, Kiplinger's magazine includes Oxford, MS -- home of \"football\", \"food\" and what Pulitzer Prize-winning author?",
        "answers": [
            "Robert Frost",
            "F. Scott Fitzgerald",
            "William Faulkner",
            "Edna Ferber"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " William Faulkner"
    },
    {
        "index": 730,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " What is \"Big Willie Style\"?",
        "answers": [
            "a film about Willie Mays",
            "a fashion line by Bill Blass",
            "an album by Will Smith",
            "a biography of Bill Clinton"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " an album by Will Smith"
    },
    {
        "index": 731,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " The opposite of ambidextrous, someone who's equally clumsy with both hands is known as what?",
        "answers": [
            "ambimalevolent",
            "ambisinister",
            "ambiatrocious",
            "ambicorrupt"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ambisinister"
    },
    {
        "index": 732,
        "date": "9/30/2016",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " Since it has the smallest effect on circadian rhythms and melatonin production, what color bulb does the Harvard Health Letter recommend using in night lights?",
        "answers": [
            "orange",
            "green",
            "red",
            "blue"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " red"
    },
    {
        "index": 733,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " BB King is one of countless blues musicians who have started a song with what classic phrase?",
        "answers": [
            "did laundry last night",
            "took a bath today",
            "I woke up this morning",
            "ate chili at lunch"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " I woke up this morning"
    },
    {
        "index": 734,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Jimmy Carter, Alice Walker and Kanye West are all on Biography.com's list of \"Famous People Born\" where?",
        "answers": [
            "in a Costco",
            "in Victorian England",
            "in a test tube",
            "in Georgia"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " in Georgia"
    },
    {
        "index": 735,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Promising to find an eco-friendly solution, drugstore chain CVS admitted in 2016 that customers have been \"very concerned with the length of our\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "Twizzlers",
            "receipts",
            "pharmacists' chest hair",
            "store greeters' hugs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " receipts"
    },
    {
        "index": 736,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Which of these is a Spanish-language version of a popular sitcom and NOT a Spanish-language version of a popular game show?",
        "answers": [
            "El Precio Juste",
            "La Rolota de la Fortuna",
            "Familia Moderna",
            "Quien Quiere Ser Millionario"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Familia Moderna"
    },
    {
        "index": 737,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Since it's butted up against a vital organ, your left what is smaller than your right one?",
        "answers": [
            "eye",
            "foot",
            "lung",
            "ear"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " lung"
    },
    {
        "index": 738,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Pioneering a new type of ink that uses smaller molecules, Harlem-based Ephemeral recently introduced a tattoo that fittingly does what?",
        "answers": [
            "grows larger over time",
            "glows in the dark",
            "releases a fragrance",
            "fades away after a year"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " fades away after a year"
    },
    {
        "index": 739,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Known for their hit sont \"Magic Carpet Ride,\" what band gots its name from the title of a work by Swiss-German novelist Hermann Hesse?",
        "answers": [
            "Lynyrd Skynyrd",
            "Blue Öyster Cult",
            "Steppenwolf",
            "The Byrds"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Steppenwolf"
    },
    {
        "index": 740,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Earning a personal commendation from First Lady Dolley Madison, on May 5, 1809 Mary Kies became the first American woman to do what?",
        "answers": [
            "be elected to Congress",
            "receive a patent",
            "serve as an Army general",
            "use a telephone"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " receive a patent"
    },
    {
        "index": 741,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " When a ban was lifted recently, Ireland became the first European country since the late 1990s allowed to export what to the United States?",
        "answers": [
            "mobile telephones",
            "beef",
            "clothing",
            "liquor"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " beef"
    },
    {
        "index": 742,
        "date": "9/23/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " On Forbes' list of the world's highest-paid athletes of 2016, the top 5 include players in all but which of these sports?",
        "answers": [
            "basketball",
            "soccer",
            "tennis",
            "football"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " football"
    },
    {
        "index": 743,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In a classic 1966 song, John Denver laments that he's leaving how?",
        "answers": [
            "\"on a jet plane\"",
            "\"with a jet pack\"",
            "\"on a jet ski\"",
            "\"in a VW Jetta\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"on a jet plane\""
    },
    {
        "index": 744,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Appropriately celebrated on October 4th, Ten-Four Day is an unofficial holiday honoring who?",
        "answers": [
            "short-order cooks",
            "ham radio operators",
            "arsonists",
            "Bavarian princes"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ham radio operators"
    },
    {
        "index": 745,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " What sarcastic term coined in reference to the JFK assassination investigation contains the name of a popular kitchen appliance?",
        "answers": [
            "Sunbeam Toaster Conspiracy",
            "Magic Bullet Theory",
            "Mr. Coffee Hypothesis",
            "Kenmore Diswasher Supposition"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Magic Bullet Theory"
    },
    {
        "index": 746,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " As he did in 2011 and 2014, when Novak Djokovic won Wimbledon in 2015, he literally tasted victory by eating some of the court's what?",
        "answers": [
            "clay",
            "wood",
            "grass",
            "asphalt"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " grass"
    },
    {
        "index": 747,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Essentially dyeing your skin from within, MyTan Bronze Tanning Pills provide a \"healthy glow\" without the sun, thanks to high doses of what?",
        "answers": [
            "riboflavin",
            "beta-carotene",
            "folic acid",
            "iron"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " beta-carotene"
    },
    {
        "index": 748,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " What TV personality also dispenses advice as an author in her books \"Don't Pee on My Leg and Tell Me It's Raining\" and \"Beauty Fades, Dumb is Forever\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Suze Orman",
            "Rachael Ray",
            "Rachel Maddow",
            "Judge Judy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Judge Judy"
    },
    {
        "index": 749,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Which of these is prominently featured in the logo of the American Cetacean Society?",
        "answers": [
            "a whale tail",
            "an eagle talon",
            "a monkey paw",
            "a T. Rex tooth"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a whale tail"
    },
    {
        "index": 750,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " In the game of pool, the number 1 ball is typically colored solid what?",
        "answers": [
            "yellow",
            "green",
            "red",
            "orange"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " yellow"
    },
    {
        "index": 751,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " If Vladimir Putin asks for poutine, he wants what country's specialty of french fries covered in gravy and cheese curds?",
        "answers": [
            "Morocco",
            "Canada",
            "Haiti",
            "Belgium"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Canada"
    },
    {
        "index": 752,
        "date": "9/16/2016",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " When \"Star Wars\" was released in 1977, what was the first sentence in the famous \"opening crawl\"?",
        "answers": [
            "The galaxy is in peril.",
            "It is a period of civil war.",
            "A darkness is encroaching.",
            "An evil empire spreads."
        ],
        "correct_answer": " It is a period of civil war."
    },
    {
        "index": 753,
        "date": "6/3/2016",
        "prize": "1,000",
        "question": " The name of what NBA team reflects the weather conditions experienced in its city roughly 85 percent of the year?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Seattle Drizzles",
            "Phoenix Suns",
            "Denver Snow Squalls",
            "San Francisco Low Pressure Fronts"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Phoenix Suns"
    },
    {
        "index": 754,
        "date": "6/3/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Using the border fence that separates the town as a net, for years Neco, Arizona famously played Neco, Mexico, in a game of what?",
        "answers": [
            "volleyball",
            "golf",
            "kickball",
            "Chinese checkers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " volleyball"
    },
    {
        "index": 755,
        "date": "6/3/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Despite what you may have heard, the USDA says you can \"shield\" your food with a small sheet of what to prevent overcooking in the microwave?",
        "answers": [
            "aluminum foil",
            "kryptonite",
            "lead paint",
            "enriched uranium"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " aluminum foil"
    },
    {
        "index": 756,
        "date": "6/3/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " During a visit to the Bavarian Alps in 2015, President Obama joked to the traditionally dressed locals, \"I forgot to bring my\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "dashiki",
            "lederhosen",
            "hakama",
            "serape"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " lederhosen"
    },
    {
        "index": 757,
        "date": "6/3/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " What wrestler was once drafted for France's peacetime army, but ended up not joining because they didn't have beds big enough for him?",
        "answers": [
            "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage",
            "\"Stone Cold\" Steve Austin",
            "André the Giant",
            "The Rock"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " André the Giant"
    },
    {
        "index": 758,
        "date": "6/3/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " What common prescription drug was named after a chemist's wife Marguerite, who frequently took the stimulant before playing tennis?",
        "answers": [
            "Ambien",
            "Prozac",
            "Dramamine",
            "Ritalin"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Ritalin"
    },
    {
        "index": 759,
        "date": "6/3/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " In one of his earliest parodies, Weird Al riffed on a 1979 hit with the lyrics, \"Oooh I think the toast is done, the toast is done, top it off with a little of\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "my grilled swordfish",
            "my string cheese",
            "my bologna",
            "my Greek salad"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " my bologna"
    },
    {
        "index": 760,
        "date": "6/3/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " When their acronyms are fully written out, all but which of the following end up having a redundant word in them?",
        "answers": [
            "ATM machine",
            "PIN number",
            "LCD display",
            "DVR remote"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " DVR remote"
    },
    {
        "index": 761,
        "date": "6/3/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Which human body part is the hardest?",
        "answers": [
            "fingernails",
            "tooth enamel",
            "bone",
            "hair"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " tooth enamel"
    },
    {
        "index": 762,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In a piece about cities whose nicknames \"totally get it wrong,\" the Huffington Post suggests Denver should drop a word and be called what instead?",
        "answers": [
            "the city that sleeps",
            "the high city",
            "the easy",
            "the city of love"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the high city"
    },
    {
        "index": 763,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Given the offerings at the beloved restaurant chain, the \"E\" in Chuck E. Cheese's fittingly stands for what?",
        "answers": [
            "entertainment",
            "elderly",
            "exhausting",
            "European"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " entertainment"
    },
    {
        "index": 764,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " If your baby's a fussy eater, it could be because some studies have found that infants have more what than adults?",
        "answers": [
            "stomach ulcers",
            "taste buds",
            "fillings",
            "religious dietary restrictions"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " taste buds"
    },
    {
        "index": 765,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Since \"Hollywood is the only way that the public learns about\" them, what organization had its entertainment industry liaison consult on the movie \"Argo\"?",
        "answers": [
            "EPA",
            "IRS",
            "CDC",
            "CIA"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " CIA"
    },
    {
        "index": 766,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Ernest Hemingway's sparse writing style, where many of the themes are left under the surface, was famously called what?",
        "answers": [
            "lightning principle",
            "iceberg theory",
            "tornado concept",
            "rainbow approach"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " iceberg theory"
    },
    {
        "index": 767,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Including the line \"Pray for peace, people everywhere\", which of these Christmas carols was inspired by the 1962 Cuban Missile Crisis?",
        "answers": [
            "O Christmas Tree",
            "Do You Hear What I Hear?",
            "Deck the Halls",
            "The Little Drummer Boy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Do You Hear What I Hear?"
    },
    {
        "index": 768,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Because it's separated by mountains and water, which state's capital is generally reached from the rest of the state only by airplane or boat?",
        "answers": [
            "Alaska",
            "Washington",
            "Rhode Island",
            "Maine"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Alaska"
    },
    {
        "index": 769,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " With adherents ranging from Richard Nixon to Judi Densch, Quakers are formally known as \"The Religious\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "Community of Companions",
            "Society of Friends",
            "Membership of Colleagues",
            "Nation of Brothers"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Society of Friends"
    },
    {
        "index": 770,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Featuring people like Edna Lewis, Joyce Chen and James Beard, in 2014 the USPS released a series of Forever stamps depicting what?",
        "answers": [
            "pioneers of physics",
            "labor organizers",
            "children's book authors",
            "celebrity chefs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " celebrity chefs"
    },
    {
        "index": 771,
        "date": "5/27/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " San Antonio Spurs player Boris Diaw shares his \"33\" jersey number with the international calling code of his native country. Where was he born?",
        "answers": [
            "Belarus",
            "Italy",
            "France",
            "Latvia"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " France"
    },
    {
        "index": 772,
        "date": "5/20/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " \"3.14159265358979323846264338327950258\" is a hand-cramping inscription found on the grave of Ludolph van Couler, a famous Dutch what?",
        "answers": [
            "mathematician",
            "fishmonger",
            "composer",
            "blacksmith"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " mathematician"
    },
    {
        "index": 773,
        "date": "5/20/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Named for the noise it makes, what popular parenting device is said to engage a baby's \"natural calming cycle\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Baby Buzzer",
            "Baby Shusher",
            "Baby Clanger",
            "Baby Honker"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Baby Shusher"
    },
    {
        "index": 774,
        "date": "5/20/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Coincidentally, what Marvel Comics character debuted in a 1966 issue just months before the political party of the same name?",
        "answers": [
            "Vegetarian",
            "Puerto Rico Socialist",
            "Black Panther",
            "Modern Whig"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Black Panther"
    },
    {
        "index": 775,
        "date": "5/20/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " What apt nickname did NASA give the newly discovered celestial body 2012 VP 113?",
        "answers": [
            "Boehner",
            "Scalia",
            "Biden",
            "Kerry"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Biden"
    },
    {
        "index": 776,
        "date": "5/20/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Often erroneously reported to have been named Thelma Ursula Beatrice Eleanor (or \"T.U.B.E.\"), in 1924 a baby girl was born on which of the following?",
        "answers": [
            "the Chicago \"L\"",
            "the Paris Metro",
            "the New York City Subway",
            "the London Underground"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the London Underground"
    },
    {
        "index": 777,
        "date": "5/20/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " When they toured in 2015, which band's lineup featured only one of its original members, singer Mike Love?",
        "answers": [
            "the Beach Boys",
            "the Rolling Stones",
            "Fleetwood Mac",
            "Aerosmith"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the Beach Boys"
    },
    {
        "index": 778,
        "date": "5/20/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " At a Japanese restaurant, your tuna sushi would technically be sashimi - not sushi - if you ordered it without which ingredient?",
        "answers": [
            "wasabi sauce",
            "seaweed",
            "tuna",
            "rice"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " rice"
    },
    {
        "index": 779,
        "date": "5/20/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Killing an estimated 8,000 of 40,000 residents in a thriving coastal community, the deadliest hurricane in US history struck what city in 1900?",
        "answers": [
            "New Orleans, LA",
            "Miami, FL",
            "Galveston, TX",
            "Charleston, SC"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Galveston, TX"
    },
    {
        "index": 780,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "1,000",
        "question": " Which term is defined by Mirriam-Webster as \"not including anything extra\" and by Urban Dictionary as being \"obscenely obvious behavior\" and dress?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "basement",
            "basic",
            "basil",
            "bassist"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " basic"
    },
    {
        "index": 781,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " The FDA says that after losing electricity, a full freezer will keep an adequate temperature for 48 hours as long as what?",
        "answers": [
            "you don't look at it",
            "you pray before it",
            "the door remains closed",
            "you turn it upside down"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the door remains closed"
    },
    {
        "index": 782,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " At 1",
        "answers": [
            "playing Boggle",
            "juggling",
            "cleaning goggles",
            "being jiggled"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " juggling"
    },
    {
        "index": 783,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " According to Merriam-Webster, which of the following names of animals is NOT both a noun and a verb?",
        "answers": [
            "seal",
            "snake",
            "giraffe",
            "bear"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " giraffe"
    },
    {
        "index": 784,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " With a clunky engine that made \"the sound of virginity,\" Jon Stewart says his first car was what widely disparaged model named for a mythical creature?",
        "answers": [
            "AMC Gremlin",
            "Ford Goblin",
            "Chrysler Ogre",
            "GMC Sasquatch"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " AMC Gremlin"
    },
    {
        "index": 785,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Reacting to the news that it will finally end after 15 seasons, Season 1 co-host tweeted \"I knew\" what \"would never last without me\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Survivor",
            "Big Brother",
            "The Amazing Race",
            "American Idol"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " American Idol"
    },
    {
        "index": 786,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " As it's nearly impossible due to high winds and thin air, National Geographic says fighter pilot Didier Delsalle is the only person to land a helicopter where?",
        "answers": [
            "the summit of Mt. Everest",
            "the floor of the Grand Canyon",
            "the South Pole",
            "The Sahara Desert"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the summit of Mt. Everest"
    },
    {
        "index": 787,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Fifty-year-old Sandra Bullock is the oldest person ever to grace the cover of People's \"Most Beautiful\" issue. Who was the youngest, in 1998, at age 23?",
        "answers": [
            "Halle Berry",
            "Matthew McConaughey",
            "Leonardo DiCaprio",
            "Scarlett Johansson"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Leonardo DiCaprio"
    },
    {
        "index": 788,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Now one of the world's most well-known electronics companies, which of these began in the 1930s as an export business selling dried Korean fish?",
        "answers": [
            "Canon",
            "Sony",
            "Samsung",
            "Toshiba"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Samsung"
    },
    {
        "index": 789,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Held in Las Vegas, what annual conference and trade show features such events as the Freestyle Dough-Tossing finals?",
        "answers": [
            "International Pizza Expo",
            "US Sundae Fest",
            "World Series of Nachos",
            "Corn Dog-Con"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " International Pizza Expo"
    },
    {
        "index": 790,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to the Huffington Post, all but which of these are among the \"Top 10 Lies Told by Internet Daters\"?",
        "answers": [
            "how much money you make",
            "how tall you are",
            "how much you weigh",
            "how many squirrels you can juggle"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " how many squirrels you can juggle"
    },
    {
        "index": 791,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Being a brand spokesman with an ample supply, Justin Bieber says he never uses the same what twice?",
        "answers": [
            "Lambourghini sports car",
            "Rolex watch",
            "Calvin Klein underwear",
            "Gulfstream private jet"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Calvin Klein underwear"
    },
    {
        "index": 792,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " \"Lying on a beach/Sun beams down from the bright sky/I am happy here\" would be an especially appropriate thing to say where?",
        "answers": [
            "Limerick, Louisiana",
            "Couplet, Colorado",
            "Sonnet, South Dakota",
            "Haiku, Hawaii"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Haiku, Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "index": 793,
        "date": "4/29/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Cape Cod, Country French, Craftsman and Ranch are all common styles of what?",
        "answers": [
            "ladies' hats",
            "home architecture",
            "salad dressings",
            "ballroom dances"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " home architecture"
    },
    {
        "index": 794,
        "date": "4/22/2016",
        "prize": "1,000",
        "question": " When used to grade pencils, the letters \"H\" and \"B\" stand for what two words?",
        "answers": [
            "heaviness and brightness",
            "harshness and breakability",
            "hardness and blackness",
            "height and boldness"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " hardness and blackness"
    },
    {
        "index": 795,
        "date": "4/22/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Though he's keeping the black-and-white stripes, what McDonald's mascot has been recently made over as a fedora-clad suburban dad with stubble?",
        "answers": [
            "Hamburglar",
            "Ronald McDonald",
            "Grimace",
            "Mayor McCheese"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Hamburglar"
    },
    {
        "index": 796,
        "date": "4/22/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of the following two-syllable words can be made into a one-syllable word by adding the letters \"sh\" to the beginning?",
        "answers": [
            "lakeside",
            "written",
            "artist",
            "rugged"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " rugged"
    },
    {
        "index": 797,
        "date": "4/22/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Helaeomyea petrolei,\" a species of fly from CA, is known to develop in pools of what dark liquid, where it feeds on insects that get trapped there?",
        "answers": [
            "vodka",
            "crude oil",
            "rain water",
            "Cheez Whiz"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " crude oil"
    },
    {
        "index": 798,
        "date": "4/22/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Already a \"Semi Pro\" basketball player on the big screen, who spent a wild day at 2015 spring training by playing for ten different baseball teams?",
        "answers": [
            "Steve Carell",
            "Vince Vaughn",
            "Will Ferrell",
            "Ben Stiller"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Will Ferrell"
    },
    {
        "index": 799,
        "date": "4/22/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Where would you most llikely be given a \"scratch test\"?",
        "answers": [
            "a computer repair store",
            "the DMV",
            "an allergist's office",
            "a shoe store"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " an allergist's office"
    },
    {
        "index": 800,
        "date": "4/22/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " With their pieces faded and stragetically tattered, what expensive brand of jeans takes its name from a peddler of used goods?",
        "answers": [
            "Dust and Dirt",
            "Rag and Bone",
            "Bags and Scraps",
            "Mop and Box"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Rag and Bone"
    },
    {
        "index": 801,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Marrying model Sofia Hellqvist in 2015, the well-chiseled Prince Carl Philip of Sweden was fittingly dubbed a what by People magazine?",
        "answers": [
            "hünk",
            "schlüb",
            "lüser",
            "chümp"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " hünk"
    },
    {
        "index": 802,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " The \"Family Plan,\" \"Even More Family Plan\" and \"Simply Everything Plus Plan\" were options in a Portlandia sketch that parodied whose offerings?",
        "answers": [
            "landscaping companies",
            "cell phone providers",
            "sports bars",
            "tattoo parlors"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cell phone providers"
    },
    {
        "index": 803,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " While it's now taken on a different meaning, which term was originally the name for a period of daily prayer taking place 6 hours after dawn?",
        "answers": [
            "tweet",
            "sext",
            "status update",
            "snapchat"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " sext"
    },
    {
        "index": 804,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " The non-commercial exchange of messages using electromagnetic oscillations is often referred to as what?",
        "answers": [
            "ham radio",
            "beef television",
            "brisket satellite",
            "venison Morse code"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ham radio"
    },
    {
        "index": 805,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Referring to the drips that run down the side of the glass, a wine with high alcohol content is often said to have what?",
        "answers": [
            "legs",
            "a six-pack",
            "killer biceps",
            "junk in the trunk"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " legs"
    },
    {
        "index": 806,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " \"Two words",
        "answers": [
            "put on 100 pounds",
            "grow a handlebar mustache",
            "go gray",
            "start slouching"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " go gray"
    },
    {
        "index": 807,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " The name of what kind of thoroughfare is derived from the former practice of puttnig a spiked barrier across a road to deter invaders?",
        "answers": [
            "boulevard",
            "turnpike",
            "parkway",
            "interstate"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " turnpike"
    },
    {
        "index": 808,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Puzzling scientists, cryptophasia occurs when a private language develops between whom?",
        "answers": [
            "twins",
            "co-workers",
            "spouses",
            "teammates"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " twins"
    },
    {
        "index": 809,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " The famed TV detective Columbo was reportedly based on Dostoyevsky's famed literary detective Porfiry Petrovich, a character in which novel?",
        "answers": [
            "Crime and Punishment",
            "Lolita",
            "War and Peace",
            "Anna Karenina"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Crime and Punishment"
    },
    {
        "index": 810,
        "date": "4/15/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " As it's the only one of three nations to not have a female head of state, Forbes' 2015 list of the world's most powerful women did NOT include the leader of what?",
        "answers": [
            "South Korea",
            "Brazil",
            "Chile",
            "France"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " France"
    },
    {
        "index": 811,
        "date": "3/18/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " While \"there's no certain way to stop it,\" the Mayo Clinic recommends gargling ice water or holding your breath to fight singultus, commonly known as what?",
        "answers": [
            "the Black Plague",
            "hiccups",
            "leprosy",
            "smallpox"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " hiccups"
    },
    {
        "index": 812,
        "date": "3/18/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to his Presidential library, upon entering the world in 1924, Jimmy Carter became the first president to be borh how?",
        "answers": [
            "in the US",
            "with a silver spoon in his mouth",
            "in a hospital",
            "to be wild"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " in a hospital"
    },
    {
        "index": 813,
        "date": "3/18/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Invented during the Great Depression, rock road ice cream is traditionally what flavor combined with nuts and marshmallows?",
        "answers": [
            "strawberry",
            "pistachio",
            "chocolate",
            "mint"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " chocolate"
    },
    {
        "index": 814,
        "date": "3/18/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Urging people not to resort to trapping to solve problems of \"flooding and tree damage,\" the Humane Society has a webpage with what title?",
        "answers": [
            "\"How to Handle Hamsters\"",
            "\"The Best Way to Deal with Deer\"",
            "\"Coming to Terms with Flying Squirrels\"",
            "\"What to Do About Beavers\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"What to Do About Beavers\""
    },
    {
        "index": 815,
        "date": "3/18/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Depicted on a commemorative version issued in 1893, the first woman to appear on a US stamp was a 15th-century ruler of what?",
        "answers": [
            "Spain",
            "France",
            "England",
            "Portugal"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Spain"
    },
    {
        "index": 816,
        "date": "3/18/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " What artist once compared the pocket watches in one of his most famous paintings to the sight of Camembert cheese melting in the sun?",
        "answers": [
            "Andy Warhol",
            "Pablo Picasso",
            "Jackson Pollock",
            "Salvador Dali"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Salvador Dali"
    },
    {
        "index": 817,
        "date": "3/18/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " The shortest NBA player at 5'3\", '90s basketball star Muggsey Bogues is, according to IMDb, roughly the same height as which actress?",
        "answers": [
            "Natalie Portman",
            "Charlize Theron",
            "Julia Roberts",
            "Emma Watson"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Natalie Portman"
    },
    {
        "index": 818,
        "date": "3/11/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Because he says he wants to make as few non-business decisions as possible, Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg often wears a simple what?",
        "answers": [
            "three-piece white linen suit",
            "gray T-shirt",
            "pink cashmere sweater",
            "green spandex onesie"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " gray T-shirt"
    },
    {
        "index": 819,
        "date": "3/11/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " A home proudcts brand once marked their trash bags with the famous slogan, \"Don't get mad, get\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "anger management therapy",
            "Glad",
            "a massage",
            "a lawyer"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Glad"
    },
    {
        "index": 820,
        "date": "3/11/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Though its \"Rock\" is more famous, what tiny British territory has an airport with a busy four-lane road running through its only runway?",
        "answers": [
            "Monaco",
            "Guam",
            "Gibraltar",
            "Liechtenstein"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Gibraltar"
    },
    {
        "index": 821,
        "date": "3/11/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Shape magazine says the Kardashians and Meghan Trainor are partly responsible for what cosmetic surgery nearly doubling in popularity between 2013 and 2014?",
        "answers": [
            "butt implants",
            "breast reduction",
            "tummy tuck",
            "nose job"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " butt implants"
    },
    {
        "index": 822,
        "date": "3/11/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " In 2009, Australia was hit by a giant what, over 600 miles across, that gave the Sydney skies an unusual blood red hue?",
        "answers": [
            "hailstorm",
            "hurricane",
            "dust storm",
            "tsunami"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dust storm"
    },
    {
        "index": 823,
        "date": "3/11/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Despite the rich heritage of a city that shares its name with a famous wine, Iran's strict laws forbidding alcohol make it illegal to drink what?",
        "answers": [
            "riesling in Riesling",
            "burgundy in Burgundy",
            "shiraz in Shiraz",
            "gewurtztramier in Gewurtztramier"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " shiraz in Shiraz"
    },
    {
        "index": 824,
        "date": "3/11/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Long before Google, Socrates was quoted as sying what \"would create forgetfulness\" because people \"will not use their memories\"?",
        "answers": [
            "theater",
            "writing",
            "the abacus",
            "music"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " writing"
    },
    {
        "index": 825,
        "date": "3/11/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Which of these politicians is a quadrigenarian?",
        "answers": [
            "Bobby Jindal",
            "Charlie Rangel",
            "Dianne Feinstein",
            "Nancy Pelosi"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Bobby Jindal"
    },
    {
        "index": 826,
        "date": "3/11/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Born in \"big\" Havana, Cuba, in 1956, what actor got a star on the Miami Walk of Fame in Little Havana in 2014?",
        "answers": [
            "Andy Garcia",
            "Benecio Del Toro",
            "Javier Bardem",
            "John Leguizano"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Andy Garcia"
    },
    {
        "index": 827,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " If you were to translate it into Spanish, which of the following daytime TV shows would be known as \"La Vista\"?",
        "answers": [
            "The Doctors",
            "The View",
            "The Talk",
            "LIVE with Kelly & Michael"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The View"
    },
    {
        "index": 828,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In an exhibition game in 2010, Michigan State University ended what basketball team's impressive 1,270-game winning streak?",
        "answers": [
            "Los Angeles Lakers",
            "Miami Heat",
            "Harlem Globetrotters",
            "San Antonio Spurs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Harlem Globetrotters"
    },
    {
        "index": 829,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Bringing new meaning to the term \"relativity,\" what famous physicist's second wife was also his cousin?",
        "answers": [
            "Albert Einstein",
            "Rene Descartes",
            "Thomas Edison",
            "Jonas Salk"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Albert Einstein"
    },
    {
        "index": 830,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Good-naturedly known as \"the greatest Sin of all,\" Jaime Sin was a beloved Filipino Catholic whose title was appropriately what?",
        "answers": [
            "Officer Sin",
            "Dr. Sin",
            "Professor Sin",
            "Cardinal Sin"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Cardinal Sin"
    },
    {
        "index": 831,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Though it may sound like a great way to relax, experts say pregnant women should avoid what due to the risk of hyperthermia?",
        "answers": [
            "getting a massage",
            "playing Candy Crush Saga",
            "using a hot tub",
            "reading a romance novel"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " using a hot tub"
    },
    {
        "index": 832,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Believing it encourages consumers to spend now rather than later, thus stimulating the economy, many economists say a little what is actually good?",
        "answers": [
            "inflation",
            "counterfeiting",
            "insider trading",
            "tax fraud"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " inflation"
    },
    {
        "index": 833,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Located in Osceola County, what town is often the target of bad puns about displays of personal affection?",
        "answers": [
            "Hugayoo, KS",
            "Kissimmee, FL",
            "Handholda, OR",
            "Shouldarubb, CA"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Kissimmee, FL"
    },
    {
        "index": 834,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " To prevent incidents like the one in \"Ferris Bueller's Day Off,\" new Corvettes come with an optional hidden camera that can be used in \"what\" mode?",
        "answers": [
            "car wash attendant mode",
            "meter maid mode",
            "mechanic mode",
            "valet mode"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " valet mode"
    },
    {
        "index": 835,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Named by Out magazine as the world's most powerful gay man, Tim Cook is famous for being what?",
        "answers": [
            "a successful movie producer",
            "the founder of TMZ",
            "the CEO of Apple",
            "the White House chief counsel"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " the CEO of Apple"
    },
    {
        "index": 836,
        "date": "3/4/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Upon opening, Disneyland's Tomorrowland was designed to reprsent what fantastic time - then 31 distant years away?",
        "answers": [
            "1971",
            "1986",
            "1999",
            "2021"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 1986"
    },
    {
        "index": 837,
        "date": "2/26/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " In \"Groundhog Day,\" Ned Ryerson sells Bill Murray's character \"fire, life, auto\" and \"health with the optional death and dismemberment plan,\" acting as his what?",
        "answers": [
            "stockbroker",
            "realtor",
            "attorney",
            "insurance agent"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " insurance agent"
    },
    {
        "index": 838,
        "date": "2/26/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " A 1972 box office smash, what film featured a 15th-century African vampire terrorizing modern day Los Angeles?",
        "answers": [
            "Blackenstein",
            "Blacula",
            "Dr. Blackyll and Mr. Hyde",
            "Love Blacktually"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Blacula"
    },
    {
        "index": 839,
        "date": "2/26/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In the Oscar-winning movie \"Rain Man,\" Dustin Hoffman's character famously claims that he is an \"excellent\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "reader",
            "driver",
            "swimmer",
            "runner"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " driver"
    },
    {
        "index": 840,
        "date": "2/26/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Which of these classic films can a person buy on DVD to watch a lead actor whose initials are DVD?",
        "answers": [
            "Breakfast at Tiffany's",
            "The Wizard of Oz",
            "Mary Poppins",
            "Some Like It Hot"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Mary Poppins"
    },
    {
        "index": 841,
        "date": "2/26/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Nicolas Cage, Lindsay Lohan, Leonardo DiCaprio and Jean-Claude Van Damme have all played which of the following in a movie?",
        "answers": [
            "British royalty",
            "FBI agents",
            "identical twins",
            "paraplegics"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "identical twins"
    },
    {
        "index": 842,
        "date": "2/26/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Which Marvel film ends with the protagonist saying the movie's title, just before the credits?",
        "answers": [
            "Iron Man",
            "The Incredible Hulk",
            "Captain America: The First Avenger",
            "Thor"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Iron Man"
    },
    {
        "index": 843,
        "date": "2/26/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " While adapting the book for film, Alfred Hitchcock reportedly had his assistant buy up copies of what 1959 novel so as to keep the plot a surprise?",
        "answers": [
            "Vertigo",
            "The Birds",
            "Psycho",
            "Rear Window"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Psycho"
    },
    {
        "index": 844,
        "date": "2/26/2016",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": " With much of the action taking place in Japan, what James Bond movie gets its title from a work by 17th century Japanese poet Matsumo Becho?",
        "answers": [
            "A View to a Kill",
            "Tomorrow Never Dies",
            "You Only Live Twice",
            "Live and Let Die"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "You Only Live Twice"
    },
    {
        "index": 845,
        "date": "2/26/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " \"The Unexpected Virtue of Ignorance\", the subtitle of 2015 Best Picture \"Birdman,\" is seen in the film in what form?",
        "answers": [
            "a newspaper headline",
            "the title of a play",
            "a suicide note",
            "a fortune cookie"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "a newspaper headline"
    },
    {
        "index": 846,
        "date": "2/12/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " A reminder of what they should avoid, what rhyming phrase is often used to teach kids how to stay safe when they're by themselves?",
        "answers": [
            "stranger danger",
            "whisk risk",
            "quartet threat",
            "tennis menace"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " stranger danger"
    },
    {
        "index": 847,
        "date": "2/12/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Featuring helpful hints from a sensei, what popular smartphone app lets you slice through watermelons with a virtual sword?",
        "answers": [
            "Candy Crush Saga",
            "Doodle Jump",
            "Fruit Ninja",
            "Words with Friends"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Fruit Ninja"
    },
    {
        "index": 848,
        "date": "2/12/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Look at the following words, and tell me which is a preposition?",
        "answers": [
            "piece",
            "of",
            "cake",
            "right?"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " of"
    },
    {
        "index": 849,
        "date": "2/12/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Columbia.edu gives information about a New York City university, but you can learn about a South American country by changing .edu to .com and doing what?",
        "answers": [
            "changing the C to a K",
            "changing the U to an O",
            "changing the B to a P",
            "changing the I to a Y"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " changing the U to an O"
    },
    {
        "index": 850,
        "date": "2/12/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Better known as a silversmith, who do some consider to be America's first forensic dentist, as he famously used his knowledge of teeth to identify a fallen soldier?",
        "answers": [
            "Benjamin Franklin",
            "John Adams",
            "Alexander Hamilton",
            "Paul Revere"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Paul Revere"
    },
    {
        "index": 851,
        "date": "2/12/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " In the game Battleship, a player has 2 grids of holes, each consisting of columns 1-10 and rows A-J. Counting both grids, how many total holes does each player have?",
        "answers": [
            "50",
            "100",
            "200",
            "400"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 200"
    },
    {
        "index": 852,
        "date": "2/12/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Corresponding with the planets named for them, Mars was Jupiter's son, who in turn was Saturn's sun, who in turn was the son of Caelus, also known as whom?",
        "answers": [
            "Mercury",
            "Venus",
            "Uranus",
            "Neptune"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Uranus"
    },
    {
        "index": 853,
        "date": "2/12/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Though they're not close geographically, what two US state capitals end with the same eight letters?",
        "answers": [
            "Utah and New York",
            "Missouri and Nevada",
            "Delaware and Colorado",
            "Illinois and Florida"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Missouri and Nevada"
    },
    {
        "index": 854,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " A tax haven and playground for the rich, the Caribbean island of Antigua and Barbuda lives up to its reputation by having what as one of its national sports?",
        "answers": [
            "extreme thrift shopping",
            "team dumpster diving",
            "sailboat racing",
            "synchronized ramen eating"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " sailboat racing"
    },
    {
        "index": 855,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Throwing in a bunch of number 2s along with the regular O-shaped pieces, in late 1999 General Mills released what \"once in a lifetime\" cereal?",
        "answers": [
            "Calculus Crunch",
            "Millenios",
            "Frosted Mathy-Wheats",
            "Raisin Algebran"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Millenios"
    },
    {
        "index": 856,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Gloria Steinem once described a Liberated Woman as one who has \"sex before marriage and\" what \"afterward\"?",
        "answers": [
            "a bunch of cats",
            "credit card debt",
            "a job",
            "a model railroading club"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a job"
    },
    {
        "index": 857,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " According to DefensiveDriving.com, you can get your windshield to defrost faster in the morning by parking your car facing what direction?",
        "answers": [
            "north",
            "east",
            "south",
            "west"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " east"
    },
    {
        "index": 858,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Having a lawyer and a forestry scientist as two of its founding directors, the anti-nuclear Don't Make a Wave Committee later morphed into what?",
        "answers": [
            "The Salvation Army",
            "UNICEF",
            "Greenpeace",
            "Doctors Without Borders"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Greenpeace"
    },
    {
        "index": 859,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Which statement is true about the music videos for Iggy Azalea's \"Fancy,\" Britney Spears' \"Baby One More Time\" and Nirvana's \"Smells Like Teen Spirit\"?",
        "answers": [
            "they take place in schools",
            "they're in black and white",
            "they're animated",
            "no people appear in them"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " they take place in schools"
    },
    {
        "index": 860,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Based on the lunar calendar, in which country is the Tet holiday celebrated not only as New Year's but traditionally also as everyone's birthday?",
        "answers": [
            "Cambodia",
            "Japan",
            "South Korea",
            "Vietnam"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Vietnam"
    },
    {
        "index": 861,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " According to IMDB.com, of the many \"Tony\" roles Tony Danza has played on TV, which did he play on his first series, \"Taxi\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Tony Micelli",
            "Tony Banta",
            "Tony Canetti",
            "Tony DiMeo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Tony Banta"
    },
    {
        "index": 862,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " According to Johns Hopkins Medicine, about 90% of Asian-Americans and 75% of African-Americans and Mexican-Americans have which genetic trait?",
        "answers": [
            "dimples",
            "lactose intolerance",
            "double-jointedness",
            "red/green colorblindness"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " lactose intolerance"
    },
    {
        "index": 863,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " A famous Wild West town allegedly got its name when people kept telling prospector Ed Schiefflein that his what is all he'd find there?",
        "answers": [
            "Tombstone, Arizona",
            "Inner Child, Colorado",
            "Long Lost Cousin, Utah",
            "True Calling, New Mexico"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Tombstone, Arizona"
    },
    {
        "index": 864,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Offering a sweet fix without the risk of salmonella, the company DO sells ready-to-eat what in flavors such as \"Snickerdoodle\" and \"Oatmeal M&M\"?",
        "answers": [
            "cookie dough",
            "pizza dough",
            "rye bread dough",
            "hot dog bun dough"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cookie dough"
    },
    {
        "index": 865,
        "date": "5/6/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In her memoir \"A Fine Romance,\" Candice Bergen describes what iconic TV character she portrayed as \"Mike Wallace in a dress\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Blanche Devereaux",
            "Murphy Brown",
            "Carol Brady",
            "Winnie Cooper"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Murphy Brown"
    },
    {
        "index": 866,
        "date": "12/25/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " As the book \"US History for Dummies\" notes, what \"exotic\" fruit drew larger crowds than the telephone at the 1876 Centennial Exhibition?",
        "answers": [
            "apple",
            "orange",
            "banana",
            "blueberry"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " banana"
    },
    {
        "index": 867,
        "date": "12/25/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " In her yearly TV special, who has Barbara Walters named as one of her \"Most Fascinating People of the Year\" on four occasions - in 1993, 2003, 2012, and 2013?",
        "answers": [
            "Steve Jobs",
            "J.K. Rowling",
            "Hillary Clinton",
            "Prince William"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Hillary Clinton"
    },
    {
        "index": 868,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Including such stars as Mike Ditka, Walter Payton and Mike Singletary, what NFL franchise has the most members in the Pro Football Hall of Fame?",
        "answers": [
            "San Francisco 49ers",
            "Chicago Bears",
            "Dallas Cowboys",
            "Cleveland Browns"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Chicago Bears"
    },
    {
        "index": 869,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " \"You could be perceived as greedy\" and \"your children might not learn the value of money\" were on a Business Insider list of the downsides of what?",
        "answers": [
            "getting sleep",
            "getting rich",
            "getting drunk",
            "getting chin implants"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " getting rich"
    },
    {
        "index": 870,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Which of these is the name of a photographer who took famous photos of Abraham Lincoln and NOT a member of \"The Brady Bunch\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Greg Brady",
            "Mathew Brady",
            "Peter Brady",
            "Bobby Brady"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Mathew Brady"
    },
    {
        "index": 871,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " To the likely chagrin of public health advocates, a popular electronics-based habit led Oxford Dictionaries to select what as its 2014 Word of the Year?",
        "answers": [
            "swipe",
            "filter",
            "earbud",
            "vape"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " vape"
    },
    {
        "index": 872,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " What military branch's official song features the lines \"Valley Forge, Custer's ranks, San Juan Hill and Patton's tanks\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Army",
            "Navy",
            "Air Force",
            "Marines"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Army"
    },
    {
        "index": 873,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " After allowing competitors to freely copy its patented 3-point seatbelt's design, a certain automaker coined the slogan \"there's a little\" what \"in every car\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Volvo",
            "Audi",
            "Cadillac",
            "Nissan"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Volvo"
    },
    {
        "index": 874,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "7,000",
        "question": " Reportedly coined by White House aide Arthur Schlesinger, \"Operation Castration\" was a nickname for the 1961 attempt to overthrow what nation's leader?",
        "answers": [
            "the USSR",
            "China",
            "Vietnam",
            "Cuba"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Cuba"
    },
    {
        "index": 875,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " The show \"Mythbusters\" has deemed it \"Plausible\" that you could raise a sunken ship from the ocean floor by filling it with what?",
        "answers": [
            "Alka-Selzer tablets",
            "cotton",
            "ping-pong balls",
            "rubber bands"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " ping-pong balls"
    },
    {
        "index": 876,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " While America WAS ready for it at the time, what 2001 hit is, to date, the last-ever song by a girl group to top the Billboard Top 100 charts?",
        "answers": [
            "Wannabe by the Spice Girls",
            "Bootylicious by Destiny's Child",
            "Walk Like an Egyptian by The Bangles",
            "Waterfalls by TLC"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Bootylicious by Destiny's Child"
    },
    {
        "index": 877,
        "date": "12/18/2015",
        "prize": "250,000",
        "question": " All but which of the following actually existed, according to a book listing the \"100 Biggests Branding Mistakes of All Time\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Ivory chewing gum",
            "BIC pantyhose",
            "Smith & Wesson bicycles",
            "Life Savers soda"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Ivory chewing gum"
    },
    {
        "index": 878,
        "date": "12/11/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Some people believe that a pack of nauseated airborne buzzards were to blame for what freak event that made headlines in 1876?",
        "answers": [
            "Delaware Twig-nado",
            "Pennsylvania Seashell Swarm",
            "Kentucky Meat Shower",
            "Ohio Rock Storm"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Kentucky Meat Shower"
    },
    {
        "index": 879,
        "date": "12/11/2015",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Catering to women, a major retail chain operates hundreds of stores across the US with what name?",
        "answers": [
            "Lady Office Depot",
            "Lady PetSmart",
            "Lady Foot Locker",
            "Lady Outback Steakhouse"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Lady Foot Locker"
    },
    {
        "index": 880,
        "date": "12/11/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " According to OxfordDictionaries.com, \"a person or thing that is spectacularly unsuccessful or disordered\" is commonly called a what?",
        "answers": [
            "tepid shambles",
            "hot mess",
            "lukewarm disarray",
            "room temperature chaos"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " hot mess"
    },
    {
        "index": 881,
        "date": "12/11/2015",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Though it's not clear if real pirates ever actually spoke it, National Geographic says stereotypical \"pirate talk\" first became popularized thanks to what Disney film?",
        "answers": [
            "The Little Mermaid",
            "20,000 Leagues Under the Sea",
            "Treasure Island",
            "High School Musical 3"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Treasure Island"
    },
    {
        "index": 882,
        "date": "12/11/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Because he was born in Johannesburg, TIME once called Dave Matthews \"perhaps the only white pop star...who could legitimately claim to be\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "Asian-American",
            "South American",
            "Native American",
            "African-American"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " African-American"
    },
    {
        "index": 883,
        "date": "12/11/2015",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " According to WebMD, it's normal to have between 10 and 40 melanocytic nevi by adulthood, which are more commonly known as what?",
        "answers": [
            "teeth",
            "moles",
            "fingers",
            "black hairs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " moles"
    },
    {
        "index": 884,
        "date": "12/11/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Most commonly made from grapes, which of the following alcoholic beverages derives its name from a Dutch word meaning \"burnt wine\"?",
        "answers": [
            "brandy",
            "bourbon",
            "liqueur",
            "tequila"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "brandy"
    },
    {
        "index": 885,
        "date": "12/11/2015",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Expanding your options beyond killing your stepdad, the \"Choose Your Own Adventure\"-style adaptation of what Shakespeare play has over 100 possible endings?",
        "answers": [
            "Macbeth",
            "King Lear",
            "Hamlet",
            "Othello"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Hamlet"
    },
    {
        "index": 886,
        "date": "12/11/2015",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Ruling the Dominican Republic for three decades, what dictator is rumored to have, in one election, received more votes than there were voters?",
        "answers": [
            "Rafael Trujillo",
            "Augusto Pinochet",
            "Simon Bolivar",
            "Fulgencio Batista"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Rafael Trujillo"
    },
    {
        "index": 887,
        "date": "2/5/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " The first time you open Google Maps on a smartphone, you'll probably be informed that the app would like to know what?",
        "answers": [
            "how you handle road rage",
            "where you see yourself in 10 years",
            "your location",
            "your turn-ons and turn-offs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " your location"
    },
    {
        "index": 888,
        "date": "2/5/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " What Mel Brooks classic had its 1974 premiere at Burbank's Prolwich Drive-In Theatre, offering free tickets to moviegoers arriving on horseback?",
        "answers": [
            "The Producers",
            "Young Frankenstein",
            "Spaceballs",
            "Blazing Saddles"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Blazing Saddles"
    },
    {
        "index": 889,
        "date": "2/5/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " In the latest quest for gender equality, an establishment called Tallywackers recently opened in Dallas as an alternative to what restaurant?",
        "answers": [
            "Chili's",
            "Hooters",
            "Applebee's",
            "Buffalo Wild Wings"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Hooters"
    },
    {
        "index": 890,
        "date": "2/5/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Warning that \"your stilettos might get a bit lonely,\" People magazine reports that \"comfort is totally cool again\" thanks to the comeback of what brand?",
        "answers": [
            "Prada",
            "Dolce & Gabbana",
            "Birkenstock",
            "Manolo Blahnik"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Birkenstock"
    },
    {
        "index": 891,
        "date": "2/5/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " For those seeking to expand their vocabulary, \"ostrobogulous,\" \"outré\" and \"zonky\" ae on OxfordDictionaries.com's list of 17 what?",
        "answers": [
            "weird ways to say weird",
            "cute ways to say cute",
            "dumb ways to say dumb",
            "tasty ways to say tasty"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "weird ways to say weird"
    },
    {
        "index": 892,
        "date": "2/5/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " According to the Earth Policy Institute, thanks to healthier eating habits, what recently surpassed beef to become America's most consumed meat?",
        "answers": [
            "salmon",
            "chicken",
            "turkey",
            "pork"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "chicken"
    },
    {
        "index": 893,
        "date": "2/5/2016",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " The International House of Pancakes lived up to its name in 2012 when it opened its first Middle East franchise at the Mall of the Emirates found where?",
        "answers": [
            "Kuwait City",
            "Dubai",
            "Riyadh",
            "Damascus"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Dubai"
    },
    {
        "index": 894,
        "date": "2/5/2016",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": "  According to MedicineNet.com, \"the anatomical juxtaposition of two orbicularis oris muscles in a state of contraction\" is a fancy way of describing a what?</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "High five",
            "Hug",
            "Kiss",
            "Handshake"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Kiss"
    },
    {
        "index": 895,
        "date": "12/4/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " New York Point and American Braille were once competing writing systems for the blind, a conflict known as the \"War of the\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "stars",
            "dots",
            "dashes",
            "squares"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " dots"
    },
    {
        "index": 896,
        "date": "11/27/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " A breakfast staple dating back centuries, which of the following gets its name from an old German word for \"bracelet\"?",
        "answers": [
            "bagel",
            "waffle",
            "biscuit",
            "Pop Tart"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bagel"
    },
    {
        "index": 897,
        "date": "11/27/2015",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Calling to mind a slightly more famous publication, what actual magazine originated as an advertising medium for Canadian cattle breeders?",
        "answers": [
            "N-ews-week",
            "Goats Illustrated",
            "Cowsmopolitan",
            "Good Mousekeeping"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Cowsmopolitan"
    },
    {
        "index": 898,
        "date": "11/27/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Boasting a guest verse from Dr. Dre, what classic '90s R&B hit features Blackstreet singing \"I like the way you work it\"?",
        "answers": [
            "No Diggity",
            "Hardly Any Diggity",
            "A Fair Amount of Diggity",
            "An Overwhelming Surplus of Diggity"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " No Diggity"
    },
    {
        "index": 899,
        "date": "11/27/2015",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Featured on BusinessInsider.com, a survey to determine the most popular pizza topping in each state found that the top choice in every single state was what?",
        "answers": [
            "sausage",
            "pepperoni",
            "mushrooms",
            "anchovies"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " pepperoni"
    },
    {
        "index": 900,
        "date": "11/27/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Which of these slang terms is used to describe a particular vast rural area, located mainly in the Appalachian region?",
        "answers": [
            "Floregon",
            "Pennsyltucky",
            "Texakota",
            "Michikansas"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Pennsyltucky"
    },
    {
        "index": 901,
        "date": "11/27/2015",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Telling him \"I'm now giving you a license to save,\" the UN's Ban Ki-Moon recently named whom as the first global advocate for mine elimination?",
        "answers": [
            "Brad Pitt",
            "Matt Damon",
            "Daniel Craig",
            "Chris Hemsworth"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Daniel Craig"
    },
    {
        "index": 902,
        "date": "11/27/2015",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Fittingly written in perfect poetic meter, what author's will simply stated, \"My Chest of Books divide among my friends\"?",
        "answers": [
            "John Keats",
            "Mark Twain",
            "Charles Dickens",
            "Leo Tolstoy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " John Keats"
    },
    {
        "index": 903,
        "date": "11/27/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Not including the word \"the,\" when referred to by their full titles, which of the following pairs of well-known organizations share a word in their names?",
        "answers": [
            "IBM & BBC",
            "CDC & CNN",
            "NASCAR & NYSE",
            "FEMA & NAACP"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " NASCAR & NYSE"
    },
    {
        "index": 904,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " According to the Book of Genesis, God created the land and seas, and then \"saw that it was\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "quitting time",
            "not zoned correctly",
            "trending on Twitter",
            "good"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " good"
    },
    {
        "index": 905,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " With a stillness that one reviewer called \"masterful,\" The Roots' Questlove recently fulfilled a fantasy by playing a what on \"Law & Order",
        "answers": [
            "doctor",
            "5-year old",
            "corpse",
            "prostitute"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " corpse"
    },
    {
        "index": 906,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " What doggie treat company recently made headlines when it received a cease and desist order from a posh New York department store?",
        "answers": [
            "Wag-Mart",
            "Collar Tree",
            "K-9 Mart",
            "Snaks 5th Avenchew"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Snaks 5th Avenchew"
    },
    {
        "index": 907,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " An acronym for \"middle-aged men in Lycra,\" the word \"MAMIL\" was added to the Oxford Dictionaries in 2014 to describe older enthusiasts of what sport?",
        "answers": [
            "snowshoeing",
            "soccer",
            "bicycling",
            "fencing"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bicycling"
    },
    {
        "index": 908,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of the following statements about US retailers is true?",
        "answers": [
            "Pier 1 Imports sells piers",
            "Foot Locker sells lockers",
            "Staples sells staples",
            "American Eagle Outfitters sells outfits for eagles"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Staples sells staples"
    },
    {
        "index": 909,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " To make sure they don't work overtime, in Queensland, Australia, what native animals can only be cuddled by zoo visitors for 30 minutes a day?",
        "answers": [
            "pandas",
            "koalas",
            "tiger cubs",
            "lemurs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " koalas"
    },
    {
        "index": 910,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Though there's no mention of a Miata, the book \"A History of Zoroastrianism\" identifies that religion's spreme god as \"Ahura\" what?",
        "answers": [
            "Nissan",
            "Mazda",
            "Hyundai",
            "Subaru"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Mazda"
    },
    {
        "index": 911,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Thinking a billionaire weapons manufacturer was \"the kind of character that nobody would like,\" Stan Lee created which Avenger as a dare to himself?",
        "answers": [
            "Iron Man",
            "Captain America",
            "Hulk",
            "Black Widow"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Iron Man"
    },
    {
        "index": 912,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " What show's service consultant sometimes cross-checks facts with cast member Mayim Bialik, who holds a PhD in Neuroscience?",
        "answers": [
            "Criminal Minds",
            "Grey's Anatomy",
            "The Big Bang Theory",
            "NCIS: Los Angeles"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Big Bang Theory"
    },
    {
        "index": 913,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Released in 1984 and weighing almost two pounds, the Motorola DynaTAC 8000X was an early handheld version of what?",
        "answers": [
            "calculator",
            "cell phone",
            "vacuum cleaner",
            "MP3 player"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cell phone"
    },
    {
        "index": 914,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Now known by a somewhat different name, who was born in Athens, Greece as Ariadne-Anna Stassinoupoulos?",
        "answers": [
            "Ann Coulter",
            "Anna Kendrick",
            "Ariana Grande",
            "Arianna Huffington"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Arianna Huffington"
    },
    {
        "index": 915,
        "date": "1/29/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Upon going public, what tech company created its NASDAQ stock symbol by simply cutting off the last two letters of its name?",
        "answers": [
            "Facebook",
            "Google",
            "Twitter",
            "Yahoo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Google"
    },
    {
        "index": 916,
        "date": "11/20/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " In his classic 1993 song, \"It Was a Good Day,\" all but which of the following pleasant things happen to Ice Cube?",
        "answers": [
            "he wins money gambling",
            "he eats Fatburger at two in the morning",
            "he knits with the elderly",
            "he enjoys a drive in his car"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " he knits with the elderly"
    },
    {
        "index": 917,
        "date": "11/20/2015",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of the following types of fires is NOT covered by a specific classification of fire extinguisher?",
        "answers": [
            "kitchen fire",
            "electrical fire",
            "gas fire",
            "Arcade Fire"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Arcade Fire"
    },
    {
        "index": 918,
        "date": "11/20/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Possibly because they're worried they'll eat their way out of their boxes, UPS does not allow customers to ship which of the following animals?",
        "answers": [
            "termites",
            "frogs",
            "snails",
            "butterflies"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " termites"
    },
    {
        "index": 919,
        "date": "11/20/2015",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " On Esquire's list of \"25 Skills Every Man Should Know,\" what was the first and only tip for how to \"Buy a Woman Clothing\"?",
        "answers": [
            "by a size larger to allow for shrinkage",
            "always pick vertical stripes",
            "check eBay for big savings",
            "Don't"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Don't"
    },
    {
        "index": 920,
        "date": "11/20/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Becase they create few crumbs that float away in zero gravity, which of the following are on the official food list for NASA astronauts in space?",
        "answers": [
            "bagels",
            "croissants",
            "tortillas",
            "biscuits"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " tortillas"
    },
    {
        "index": 921,
        "date": "11/20/2015",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Helping decode \"Anaconda\" and \"Starships,\" what feature of a popular recording artist's phone app explains the meaning of her many creative slang terms?",
        "answers": [
            "Gagalossary",
            "Ciarapedia",
            "Nictionary",
            "Rihalmanac"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Nictionary"
    },
    {
        "index": 922,
        "date": "11/20/2015",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": " Lucky for the 49th state, the US never executed its Cold War-era plan to trade part of Alaska to what country, so it could build bases in Greenland?",
        "answers": [
            "Denmark",
            "Sweden",
            "Russia",
            "Iceland"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "index": 923,
        "date": "1/22/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of the following is a classic John Coltrane jazz album and NOT something you'd see on the Taco Bell menu?",
        "answers": [
            "A Burrito Supreme",
            "A Taco Supreme",
            "A Chalupa Supreme",
            "A Love Supreme"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " A Love Supreme"
    },
    {
        "index": 924,
        "date": "1/22/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " The USPS says that which of the following items \"don't work and that if you mail them, you may be committing a federal crime\"?",
        "answers": [
            "birth announcements",
            "sympathy cards",
            "thank-you notes",
            "chain letters"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " chain letters"
    },
    {
        "index": 925,
        "date": "1/22/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " The African cicada can thank its mating habits for the fact that it holds what Guinness World Record among all insects?",
        "answers": [
            "fastest",
            "strongest",
            "loudest",
            "hippest"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " loudest"
    },
    {
        "index": 926,
        "date": "1/22/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Countering The Perfect Body campaign by Victoria's Secret, in 2015 plus-size retailer Lane Bryant unveiled its own ads featuring what slogan?",
        "answers": [
            "#I'm no mermaid",
            "#I'm no angel",
            "#I'm no princess",
            "#I'm no swan"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " #I'm no angel"
    },
    {
        "index": 927,
        "date": "1/22/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " In order to counteract an abundance of sebum created by our sebaceous glands, we use which of the following products?",
        "answers": [
            "shampoo",
            "eyedrops",
            "aspirin",
            "toothpaste"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " shampoo"
    },
    {
        "index": 928,
        "date": "1/22/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Named for a famous mathematician, what ancient device is sometimes still used to move liquids uphill?",
        "answers": [
            "Archimedes' screw",
            "Pythagoras' bucket",
            "Ptolemy's fulcrum",
            "Euclid's spoon"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes' screw"
    },
    {
        "index": 929,
        "date": "1/22/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Bugatti's test driver says that while it's possible, he's never exceeded 270 mph in the Veyron Grand Sport Vitesse because tests show it would cause what?",
        "answers": [
            "the engine to catch fire",
            "the windshield to shatter",
            "the tires to explode",
            "the muffler to fly off"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "the tires to explode"
    },
    {
        "index": 930,
        "date": "11/13/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Featuring the lyric \"Aww, aww, baby. Yeah, ooh yeah,\" which of the following was \"dropped\" by singer Tom Jones on his 1999 album Reload?",
        "answers": [
            "\"Atomic Bomb\"",
            "\"Stink Bomb\"",
            "\"Sex Bomb\"",
            "\"Lip Balm\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"Sex Bomb\""
    },
    {
        "index": 931,
        "date": "11/13/2015",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Letting you wear cutoffs in your cubicle, many workplaces relax their dress code on a day commonly known as what?",
        "answers": [
            "easygoing Wednesday",
            "casual Friday",
            "relaxed Thursday",
            "topless Tuesday"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " casual Friday"
    },
    {
        "index": 932,
        "date": "11/13/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " First published in the 1970s, what popular foreign comic features a crime-fighting superhero with a maple leaf on his forehead?",
        "answers": [
            "Captain Canuck",
            "Admiral Aussie",
            "the Kiwi Avenger",
            "Bosnia & Herzegovina Man"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Captain Canuck"
    },
    {
        "index": 933,
        "date": "11/13/2015",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " A New York magazine article notes that due to increasing 2-wheeled traffic in major cities, there's been a rise in aggression from car drivers, nicknamed what?",
        "answers": [
            "skatehate",
            "snomo-bullying",
            "bikelash",
            "unicycle fury"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " bikelash"
    },
    {
        "index": 934,
        "date": "11/13/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " Calling them \"mythologized, demonized, celebrated\", a Vogue article names the likes of Jessica Chastain and Amy Adams today's what?",
        "answers": [
            "beautiful blondes",
            "gorgeous grays",
            "reigning redheads",
            "marvelous mullets"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " reigning redheads"
    },
    {
        "index": 935,
        "date": "11/13/2015",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Despite its being subject to federal regulation, market research shows that more than half of shoppers think that what label is \"just an excuse to charge more\"?",
        "answers": [
            "hearty",
            "organic",
            "classic",
            "homemade"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " organic"
    },
    {
        "index": 936,
        "date": "11/13/2015",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Until they're at least one week old, kittens generally won't what?",
        "answers": [
            "nurse",
            "open their eyes",
            "meow",
            "have fur"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " open their eyes"
    },
    {
        "index": 937,
        "date": "11/13/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Despite an outcry and a lawsuit from players, the 2015 Women's World Cup was the first one to be played how?",
        "answers": [
            "in the winter",
            "with a new, smaller ball",
            "on artificial turf",
            "with mandatory faceguards"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " on artificial turf"
    },
    {
        "index": 938,
        "date": "11/13/2015",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Lending its name to the Golden Gate Bridge, the Golden Gate Strait was named for its resemblance to a harbor at what \"golden gate\" to the East?",
        "answers": [
            "Athens, Greece",
            "Cairo, Egypt",
            "Venice, Italy",
            "Istanbul, Turkey"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Istanbul, Turkey"
    },
    {
        "index": 939,
        "date": "11/6/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Since a fruit-and-rum cocktail shares its name with a small Cuban town, when you're in Cuba, it's possible to drink what?",
        "answers": [
            "a martini in Martini",
            "a margarita in Margarita",
            "a daiquiri in Daiquiri",
            "a cosmo in Cosmo"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a daiquiri in Daiquiri"
    },
    {
        "index": 940,
        "date": "11/6/2015",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Not actually a plant, which of the following are you least likely to encounter in the lawn and garden department?",
        "answers": [
            "Japanese holly",
            "lily of the valley",
            "oakleaf hydrangea",
            "Iggy Azelea"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Iggy Azelea"
    },
    {
        "index": 941,
        "date": "11/6/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Weighing such factors as an affinity for soap operas and La-Z-Boy retailers per capita, a 2015 study on Estately.com found that Ohio has the country's most what?",
        "answers": [
            "celebrity chefs",
            "professional wrestlers",
            "couch potatoes",
            "astronauts"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " couch potatoes"
    },
    {
        "index": 942,
        "date": "11/6/2015",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Lacking the fame of his counterpart, Jack Jouette's 40-mile ride to save Thomas Jefferson from capture by the British in 1781 led him to be called the who \"of the South\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Alexander Hamilton",
            "Paul Revere",
            "Benjamin Franklin",
            "John Hancock"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Paul Revere"
    },
    {
        "index": 943,
        "date": "11/6/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " The punnily-named Ted Nudegent starred in \"Austin Powers\" as Mr. Bigglesworth, a hairless what that sat on Dr. Evil's lap?",
        "answers": [
            "dog",
            "rat",
            "cat",
            "hamster"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " cat"
    },
    {
        "index": 944,
        "date": "11/6/2015",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " Which of the following is named after a wealthy American because of the incredible buttery richness of the sauce it's served with?",
        "answers": [
            "oysters Rockefeller",
            "beef Wellington",
            "bananas Foster",
            "peach Melba"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " oysters Rockefeller"
    },
    {
        "index": 945,
        "date": "11/6/2015",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Of the following pairs of famous names, which one includes two people of the same sex?",
        "answers": [
            "Taylor Lautner and Taylor Swift",
            "Blake Lively and Blake Shelton",
            "Jamie Dornan and Jamie Fox",
            "Glenn Close and Glenn Beck"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Jamie Dornan and Jamie Fox"
    },
    {
        "index": 946,
        "date": "11/6/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " Ubiquitous at weddings, what line dance is set to a 1983 song produced by Bunny Wailer, a former member of Bob Marley's band?",
        "answers": [
            "Boot Scootin' Boogie",
            "Electric Slide",
            "Macarena",
            "Chicken Dance"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Electric Slide"
    },
    {
        "index": 947,
        "date": "11/6/2015",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": " Famous among car fans, the 1995 Honda Civic VX gets what EPA-estimated highway mileage, two more than the 2015 Toyota Prius?",
        "answers": [
            "20 mpg",
            "40 mpg",
            "50 mpg",
            "70 mpg"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 50 mpg"
    },
    {
        "index": 948,
        "date": "10/30/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " While rules prevent US presidents from keeping most gifts from foreign governments, they can keep gifts from US citizens as long as they do what?",
        "answers": [
            "write a long thank-you note",
            "pay any required taxes on them",
            "only use them on July 4",
            "never unwrap them"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " pay any required taxes on them"
    },
    {
        "index": 949,
        "date": "10/30/2015",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " WikiHow's article \"How to Apply Makeup\" says that after washing and moisturizing your face, you should first apply your concealer and next apply your what?",
        "answers": [
            "foundation",
            "vinyl siding",
            "support beams",
            "fiberglass insulation"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " foundation"
    },
    {
        "index": 950,
        "date": "10/30/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Selling \"beans that are a little less perrfect\", ads for what irregular candies tout them as being \"just as good at about half the price\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Starburt",
            "Belly Flops",
            "Mr. Badbars",
            "Reese's Pieces of Junk"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Belly Flops"
    },
    {
        "index": 951,
        "date": "10/30/2015",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Considered even harder to win than the American version, the \"Two Thousand Guineas\", \"The Derby\" and the \"St. Leger\" make up the British what?",
        "answers": [
            "Triple Crown of Horse Racing",
            "World Series of Eating Championships",
            "Super Bowl of Gymnastics Competitions",
            "Grand Slam of Quilting Bees"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Triple Crown of Horse Racing"
    },
    {
        "index": 952,
        "date": "10/30/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": " What sequel to Louisa May Alcott's most famous work is subtitled \"Life at Plumfield with Jo's Boys\"?",
        "answers": [
            "Little House in the Suburbs",
            "To Resurrect a Mockingbird",
            "Little Men",
            "Uncle Tom's 4th Floor Walkup"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Little Men"
    },
    {
        "index": 953,
        "date": "10/30/2015",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " What singer's rendition of \"The Star Spangled Banner\" at Super Bowl XXV became a Top 10 Billboard hit?",
        "answers": [
            "Paula Abdul",
            "Mariah Carey",
            "Whitney Houston",
            "Janet Jackson"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Whitney Houston"
    },
    {
        "index": 954,
        "date": "10/30/2015",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": " Currently written in their English language versions, which of these countries' names can be changed to its native name by replacing just one letter with another?",
        "answers": [
            "Spain",
            "Brazil",
            "Germany",
            "Italy"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Brazil"
    },
    {
        "index": 955,
        "date": "10/30/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": " According to Lifehacker.com, you can rid your inbox of large amounts of spam by searching for and deleting all the messages with what word?",
        "answers": [
            "hello",
            "reply",
            "unsubscribe",
            "attachment"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " unsubscribe"
    },
    {
        "index": 956,
        "date": "1/8/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": " Which of these is neither Fonzie's catchphrase nor a body of water nor the 1st name of Twisted Sister's frontman?",
        "answers": [
            "Ayyyy!",
            "Bee",
            "Sea",
            "Dee"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Bee"
    },
    {
        "index": 957,
        "date": "1/8/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": " Sharing its name with something you might wear while you're there, what chain of resorts geared toward couples also owns the Beaches family resort franchise?",
        "answers": [
            "Sunglasses",
            "Sandals",
            "Hats",
            "Bikinis"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Sandals"
    },
    {
        "index": 958,
        "date": "1/8/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": " Since they're no longer printed on physical paper, if you want what you'll have to go to treasurydirect.gov and get one digitally?",
        "answers": [
            "savings bond",
            "birth certificate",
            "motor vehicle title",
            "marriage license"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " savings bond"
    },
    {
        "index": 959,
        "date": "1/8/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": " The wishbone, superstitiously thought to bring luck, is composed of a chicken's what?",
        "answers": [
            "humerus",
            "clavicle",
            "femur",
            "ribs"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " clavicle"
    },
    {
        "index": 960,
        "date": "1/1/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": "</strong> A blend of passion fruit, orange and guava, POG juice was created in what U.S. state?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "South Carolina",
            "Hawaii",
            "Florida",
            "California"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "index": 961,
        "date": "1/1/2016",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": "</strong> Perhaps because you've already learned to live with someone, an Ohio State study suggests you may be less likely to get divorced if you have a lot of what?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "credit cards",
            "furniture",
            "siblings",
            "tweets"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " siblings"
    },
    {
        "index": 962,
        "date": "1/1/2016",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": "</strong>  Explaining why he was a vegetarian, TV's famously kindhearted Mister Rogers once said, \"I don't want to eat anything that has\" what?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "seeds",
            "a mother",
            "gluten",
            "calories"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a mother"
    },
    {
        "index": 963,
        "date": "1/1/2016",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": "</strong> Fittingly located in Minnesota, Big Ole, standing 28 feet tall with blonde hair and a shield, is the largest statue of a what in the United States?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Viking",
            "cheerleader",
            "cowboy",
            "exterminator"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Viking"
    },
    {
        "index": 964,
        "date": "1/1/2016",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": "</strong> Introducing a two-color scheme with tan shirts and olive pants, Oscar de la Renta was commissioned in 1978 to update the uniforms for whom?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Delta Air Lines pilots",
            "UPS workers",
            "Federal prison inmates",
            "Boy Scouts of America"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Boy Scouts of America"
    },
    {
        "index": 965,
        "date": "1/1/2016",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": "</strong> You are unlikely to see a Tesla Model S with which standard automobile feature, because it has no use for one?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "bumper",
            "steering wheel",
            "suspension",
            "exhaust pipe"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " exhaust pipe"
    },
    {
        "index": 966,
        "date": "1/1/2016",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": "</strong> With a loud bark and a short stature that makes it hard to find, what breed of dog beloved by Queen Elizabeth II is traditionally used to herd cattle?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "corgi",
            "dachshund",
            "chihuahua",
            "pug"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " corgi"
    },
    {
        "index": 967,
        "date": "1/1/2016",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": "</strong> Providing \"old twists on new tunes,\" the blog Pop Sonnets translates the first line of what disco hit to \"O sweet and noble lad, be not aggrieved\"?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "I Will Survive",
            "Stayin' Alive",
            "Celebration",
            "YMCA"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " YMCA"
    },
    {
        "index": 968,
        "date": "1/1/2016",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": "</strong> Born in Mexico to a Spanish mother and Lebanese father, actress Salma Hayak's first name is derived from the Arabic for what?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "peace",
            "honesty",
            "love",
            "determination"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " peace"
    },
    {
        "index": 969,
        "date": "10/9/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": "</strong> Which of the following is known as the coldest, driest, windiest and highest continent in the world?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Australia",
            "Europe",
            "North America",
            "Antarctica"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Antarctica"
    },
    {
        "index": 970,
        "date": "10/9/2015",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": "</strong> Which of the following is NOT one of the three objects that athletes fight with in the Olympic sport of fencing?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "foil",
            "epee",
            "saber",
            "chain link fence"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " chain link fence"
    },
    {
        "index": 971,
        "date": "10/9/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": "</strong> In the early 20th century, new laws restricted the length of what ladies' accessory, which for suffragettes and other women sometimes doubled as weapons?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "gloves",
            "watches",
            "hatpins",
            "sunglasses"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " hatpins"
    },
    {
        "index": 972,
        "date": "10/9/2015",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": "</strong> Also called \"emotional incontinence,\" Pseudobulbar affect is a disorder marked by sudden uncontrollable outbursts of what?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "yawning or sneezing",
            "crying or laughing",
            "squatting or hopping",
            "growing or shrinking"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " crying or laughing"
    },
    {
        "index": 973,
        "date": "10/9/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": "</strong> Derived from the abbreviation \"U.P,\" \"Yoopers\" are folks from the upper peninsula region of what state?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Michigan",
            "Virginia",
            "Oregon",
            "California"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Michigan"
    },
    {
        "index": 974,
        "date": "10/9/2015",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": "</strong> On the iconic cover of his album \"Born in the U.S.A.,\" what does Bruce Springsteen have tucked into the back pocket of his jeans?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "his passport",
            "a Bible",
            "a U.S. map",
            "a red baseball cap"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a red baseball cap"
    },
    {
        "index": 975,
        "date": "10/9/2015",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": "</strong> \"El Pais,\" the name of Spain's leading daily newspaper, translates to English as what?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "The Country",
            "The World",
            "The News",
            "The Truth"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Country"
    },
    {
        "index": 976,
        "date": "10/9/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": "</strong> In 1986, 27-year old Ron Reagan became the only child of a sitting U.S. president to do what?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "attend an Ivy League university",
            "host Saturday Night Live",
            "win a Grammy",
            "become a U.S. ambassador"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " host Saturday Night Live"
    },
    {
        "index": 977,
        "date": "10/9/2015",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": "</strong> Who is Almu'tasimu Billahi Muhibbuddin Tuanku Alhaj Abdul Halim Mu'adzam Shah Ibni Almarhum Sultan Badlishah?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "a best-selling British novelist",
            "the king of Malaysia",
            "the world's richest man",
            "the CEO of Emirates Airlines"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "the king of Malaysia"
    },
    {
        "index": 978,
        "date": "10/2/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": "</strong> A brand that's been dangling in cars since 1952, the Car-Freshener company sells products with what apt name?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "little seashells",
            "little rocks",
            "little trees",
            "little snowflakes"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " little trees"
    },
    {
        "index": 979,
        "date": "10/2/2015",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": "</strong> Following in her mother's footsteps, in 1935, Irene Joliot-Curie won which of the following?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "the Nobel Prize in chemistry",
            "the Olympic gold medal in fencing",
            "the Grammy award for best new artist",
            "America's next top model"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "the Nobel Prize in chemistry"
    },
    {
        "index": 980,
        "date": "10/2/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": "</strong> Oxford Dictionaries' list of \"10 Awesome Ways to Say Awesome\" includes all but which of the following words?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "bogus",
            "boss",
            "bad",
            "bodacious"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "bogus"
    },
    {
        "index": 981,
        "date": "10/2/2015",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": "</strong> The symbol for which of these elements shares its two letters with a U.S. state's postal abbreviation?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "boron",
            "helium",
            "aluminum",
            "hydrogen"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "aluminum"
    },
    {
        "index": 982,
        "date": "10/2/2015",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": "</strong> Which of these is the scientific name of a real-life \"dragon\" and NOT a character from the TV show \"Game of Thrones\"?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Khal Drogo",
            "Daenerys Targaryen",
            "Varanus Komodoensis",
            "Daario Naharis"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Varanus Komodoensis"
    },
    {
        "index": 983,
        "date": "10/2/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": "</strong> If a hen lays 265 eggs a year, about how long would it take her to lay one million of them?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "3.77 years",
            "37.7 years 377 years 3,770 years",
            "377 years",
            "3,770 years"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "3,770 years"
    },
    {
        "index": 984,
        "date": "10/2/2015",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": "</strong> What classic novel features a character named Vivian Darkbloom, an anagram of the author's name?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Lord of the Flies",
            "Lolita",
            "Catch-22",
            "Animal Farm"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Lolita"
    },
    {
        "index": 985,
        "date": "9/25/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": "</strong> To raise awareness of unusual medical disorders, the first Rare Disease Day was celebrated on what fitting date in 2008?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "January 1st",
            "February 29th",
            "August 8th",
            "December 25th"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "February 29th"
    },
    {
        "index": 986,
        "date": "9/25/2015",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": "</strong> Besides Gerald Ford, since WWII how many presidents have run for a second term in office and lost?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 2"
    },
    {
        "index": 987,
        "date": "9/25/2015",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": "</strong> A Texas resident was recently banned from owning which of these seemingly harmless license plates, because it spells a curse word when turned upside down?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "SN3V3WP3",
            "P3XVOH",
            "HV100W",
            "370H55V"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "370H55V"
    },
    {
        "index": 988,
        "date": "9/25/2015",
        "prize": "50,000",
        "question": "</strong> The word \"infant\" derives from the Latin word \"infans,\" meaning what?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "restful slumbers",
            "unable to speak",
            "hairless beast",
            "always hungry"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " unable to speak"
    },
    {
        "index": 989,
        "date": "9/25/2015",
        "prize": "100,000",
        "question": "</strong> Minutes after Neil Armstrong's famous \"one small step\" line, which of these things did Buzz Aldrin say just before stepping onto the moon himself?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "\"Beautiful view.\"",
            "\"I'm stepping down now.\"",
            "\"Oh my goodness.\"",
            "\"Scientia potentia est.\""
        ],
        "correct_answer": " \"Beautiful view.\""
    },
    {
        "index": 990,
        "date": "9/18/2015",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": "</strong> While it sounds like a rhetorical question you'd hear during an argument, which of these is a TV series that traces a celebrity's family tree?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Who Do You Think You Are?",
            "Oh, So You're Better Than Me?",
            "Is This Some Kind of Joke?",
            "Why Do I Even Bother?"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Who Do You Think You Are?"
    },
    {
        "index": 991,
        "date": "9/18/2015",
        "prize": "1000",
        "question": "</strong> According to HGTV, you can make freshly-painted rooms smell nicer by adding a tablespoon of what to each gallon of paint?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "barbecue sauce",
            "vanilla extract",
            "mustard",
            "hot sauce"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " vanilla extract"
    },
    {
        "index": 992,
        "date": "9/18/2015",
        "prize": "2000",
        "question": "</strong> In a 1936 NY Times article, what job's requirements were listed as",
        "answers": [
            "nun",
            "air hostess",
            "teacher",
            "hairdresser"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " air hostess"
    },
    {
        "index": 993,
        "date": "9/18/2015",
        "prize": "3000",
        "question": "</strong> It's been pointed out that if Katniss and Peeta from what popular book series were a celebrity couple, their nickname might be \"Katpee\" or \"Peenis\"?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Game of Thrones",
            "The Hunger Games",
            "Harry Potter",
            "Twilight"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " The Hunger Games"
    },
    {
        "index": 994,
        "date": "9/18/2015",
        "prize": "5000",
        "question": "</strong> What answer has evolutionary biologist Peter Turchin given to those who ask, \"Why do men now wear pants instead of kilts\"?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "canoes",
            "horses",
            "cannons",
            "plows"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " horses"
    },
    {
        "index": 995,
        "date": "9/18/2015",
        "prize": "7000",
        "question": "</strong> Though one is a measure of volume and the other of weight, in the U.S., a pint and a pound can both be described as what?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "2 liters",
            "1000 grams",
            "16 ounces",
            "50 cubic centimeters"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " 16 ounces"
    },
    {
        "index": 996,
        "date": "9/18/2015",
        "prize": "10,000",
        "question": "</strong> Because parts of the movies were shot there, what Las Vegas hotel often receives requests for the \"Rain Man suite\" or the \"Hangover suite\"?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Bellagio",
            "Flamingo",
            "Mandalay Bay",
            "Caesar's Palace"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Caesar's Palace"
    },
    {
        "index": 997,
        "date": "9/18/2015",
        "prize": "20,000",
        "question": "</strong> In 2014, 17-year-old Pakistani Malala Yousafzai became the youngest person ever awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in recognition of her work for what?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "animal welfare",
            "freedom of the press",
            "nuclear disarmament",
            "education rights"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " education rights"
    },
    {
        "index": 998,
        "date": "9/18/2015",
        "prize": "30,000",
        "question": "</strong> Bearing the motto \"Sic semper tyrannis,\" which state's seal depicts the goddess Virtus standing with one foot on the chest of an enemy?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "South Carolina",
            "Virginia",
            "Massachusetts",
            "Connecticut"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Virginia"
    },
    {
        "index": 999,
        "date": "2/6/2015",
        "prize": "1,000",
        "question": "</strong> A tougher version of its predecessor, in 1998, what board game added characters like Madame Rose, Monsieur Brunette, and Sergeant Gray?<br/>",
        "answers": [
            "Operation: Heart Transplant",
            "Invisible Ink Pictionary",
            "Jenga Skyscraper",
            "Clue: Master Detective"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " Clue: Master Detective"
    },
    {
        "index": 1000,
        "date": "1/31/2014",
        "prize": "1,000 Question",
        "question": "</strong><br/>",
        "answers": [
            "2014 Winter Olympics logo is the first to contain what feature?",
            "a website",
            "an animal",
            "the Olympic rings"
        ],
        "correct_answer": " a website"
    },
    {
        "index": 1001,
        "date": "09/22/2009",
        "prize": "500",
        "question": "On an iPhone, what application is symbolized by a plus sign, a minus sign, a multiplication sign, and an equal sign?",
        "answers": [
            "Calendar",
            "Maps",
            "Calculator",
            "Ex-Boyfriend Counter"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Calculator"
    }
]